[Music]
e
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
TI 12 final day it's starting here in
climate pledge Arena we already have
quite a lot of people filling out the
arena filling out the seats and we are
down to just three teams our top three
teams remaining today in at the end of
it we will have our ti2 champion we will
be seeing all those players lift the
ages for themselves my morning panel has
changed up from the last few days I
still have lacost with me I still have
Reser but this time I have Gunner
joining me hello hello pleasure to be
here on the final day yeah you get to do
the opener and I'm in a little bit of
spoiler you'll be working this first
series with us as well but how how
excited are you you here maybe not as
excited as if you playing but it is the
final day yeah and uh I like to see the
kind of comparisons between the teams I
think gaming has been playing really
fast and I think the other teams have
been playing really long games so going
to be a battle of kind of the Styles
today yeah which Tempo is going to come
out on top and which tempos are we going
to see but what about yourself rzo man I
want to say thank you to you know to to
be here and like welcome to Seattle guys
hiy hey everybody like uh it's it's an
amazing day like I'm really sad that
this is the last day because it's like
it's been such an incredible journey
already like we've seen so many games G
so many clutch games so many like long
games as well but the gaming glader is
like giving us this the fast tempo as
well they're coming with a unique play
style that they came up for this
specific tournament and I'm I'm really
like uh I'm really exciting like how is
it going to like continue doing the same
things like are they going to continue
stomping their teams and like going to
the finals and making the same thing to
lgd and spirit or like you know lgd are
going to come up with something new and
like stop their pressure yeah it's it's
been 3 weeks leading up to this final
day I can't believe how quickly it's
gone the fact that we're down to three
teams lost yeah it feels kind of sad but
also very hyped about what's going to
happen today because we seen we've seen
some of these matchups like the big
story lines coming into this TI the
whole 2023 was pretty much gaming
Gladiators against Team Liquid they had
to face in the lower bracket and
unfortunately one of them had to go home
they're still going to you know stay
here watch the grand finals but uh the
other thing is team spirit just
dominating whenever there's a lot of
money involved a lot of prestige you
know that this team they're going to
speed up they want to be the one you
know cring themselves as a second time
champion at TI I was just looking at yor
games and he's doing this once again
he's playing every game with a new hero
like he hero challenge again old hero
challenge again like the only two Heroes
that had like two repetition was like CK
and mua but other than that he's like
every game new here like troll s ter
blade you name it you know he's going
for this new play like he he doesn't
really like he doesn't like to play the
same Heroes yeah they running back the
style that uh gone in the a lot of
success for TI 10 you know the benefit
of being on the morning panel by the way
the opening the pre-show is that you can
put out who you think is going to win TI
out of these three remaining teams and
you get to look smarter than everyone
else that comes on later in the day so
do you want to give it a go do you want
to say your bold prediction it's a one
in three chance so it's 50% H just
kidding and I I do feel like team spirit
they've showed the best like map
movements their drats are always on
point how they play if you if you're
playing late game against team spirit
and we've seen a lot of these games
going the late game I feel like they're
going to take it but also between the
two teams that we're going to see right
now lgd gaming against gaming Gladiators
I feel you know G they have the upper
hand because they really stepping it up
ever since they played against nine
pandas all of their games are like 20 to
30 minute games pretty much I mean to me
the finals are going to be between
spirit and gaming to be honest yeah I
think I think lgd are not going to
handle the pressure from gaming
Gladiators like it's we had a few gaming
Gladiators fans that year when when you
said that they were going to be making
it to the fin sorry guys sorry to upset
you but yeah I mean uh the the gaming
they're like very good at laning and
it's been lgd struggle for like a long
time so I think uh they're not going to
be able to handle that pressure but for
the finals I think Spirit are like way
more solic very they're very adaptable
and um I'm I think this is the only one
team that who can stop the gaming ler
from like you know doing the same thing
and like because they're also very good
at laning and if you're good at laning
and that that time it doesn't really
work when you're like on even terms I
think there's also a comparison cuz
spirit is probably the best team at
playing from behind in this tournament
no matter how bad the game is they can
still win you feel like they're going to
win even if they're down a lot and so
for gaming a lot of their ways they win
is just early game pressure and just
taking over the game so fast but I think
Spirits probably if there's one team to
beat that' be Spirit okay all right so
we're all kind of putting a lot of eggs
in the Teen Spirit basket they had to be
repeat TI winners but it's a long day
ahead of us we don't know what is going
to happen but we're going to start this
day off with the right turn we got Casey
we're going to catch up with her and
what it's like in the
arena welcome to Grand finals day we
made it there have been people lining up
here since 6:00 a.m. and I only know
that cuz that's what time I arrived so
here they all are coming in we know
there's so many people watching from
home and we thought we'd walk you
through the experience of those
attending here because we want you to
feel like you're here with all of the
energy everybody is walking through the
entrance here tell me more about what
made you decide to come to TI how long
have you been playing DotA I've been
playing DOTA not very long only about
three years what about you three years
I've been playing since like 2012 like
high school beginning of high school oh
God I'm so sorry I didn't know was here
by far sorry sorry we're doing mandatory
entrance interviews as always hello
welcome who I'm being taken over
absolutely thank you what did she ask
you she asked me uh who was going to win
TI who's going to win TI I said team
spirit was going to Wi okay great
mandatory interview over your turn
favorite hero uh Arc Warden uh m
breaking raking bad here get up the
escalator come on hi are you ex yes very
much who's going to win very who's going
to win Quinn that's not a team but okay
all right mandatory entrance interview
mandatory interview
hello we do this every TI say a word uh
good ccnc oh okay nice job these are
always a banger yeah relx keep going
Casey I'm trying to get away from you
good who's going to win Gladiators who's
going to win most likely Spirit who's
going to win GG for the win G who's
going to win GG who's going to win are
you are you who's going to
win win who's going to
[Music]
win howdy slack wor it who's going to
lose TS a that's how you get him that's
how you get him no slack no get no keep
him away from me no
who's going to win could not tell
you now that's the kind of energy we
like team spirit GG team spirit let's
go
all I think that worked yeah those were
very quick interviews Neil mandatory
mandatory what do you reckon their
interview per minute was at that rate I
feel a little bitet at there's like no
uh not a lot of lgd fans were there and
at this moment I'm sure there's a lot of
in the crowd right now can we hear them
guys anyone lgd fans yeah that that's
what I'm talking about give us some I
want to know I want to know gaming
Gladiator fans
though oh they're a little bit louder
and what about team spirit
guys okay I didn't think we were going
to get that loud of team spirit chance
until later we know that they're already
in the grand finals I thought all the
Teen Spirit fans might have been getting
their sleeping getting their gamer hours
going and and they were going to arrive
a little bit later but it was nice to to
know the chaos that casy tsunami slacks
are working hard in The Concourse
getting some more interviews for us but
if you're at home fret not there's also
a lot of content for you guys today that
you get to enjoy here for our final day
of ti2 we are going to have our short
film contest the finalist will be
announced our cosplay contest as well
and then at the very end of the day
we're going to have our last late game
live with uh perion and Jenkins that's
been happening the last two nights as
well so if you guys want
to want to be in the background
Charlotte theater is where I heard it's
been taken place so it' be nice to see
you all down there the short film The
cosplay that will be taking place
between the low bracket finals and the
grand finals so there is action all
throughout the day nothing that you guys
want to miss at all and there's already
been a lot of action cost oh absolutely
we're talking about to DOTA action like
You' even seen like this this whole meta
shift that has been going on ever since
the group stage started where you had
all these tanky midlaners off laners
with the blade M heart and then you had
like some of these strong offlane Duos
with vber plus grimstroke that has risen
at the recent uh stages of the
tournament Tusk bu Dawn breaker and also
some of these untargetable Heroes and
then there's a separate meta that gaming
gladers are playing which is constant
push like they're just going for these
20-minute games picking all these pretty
much Heroes that they've been playing
throughout the whole year just switching
things up a little bit bringing out Chen
which is you know undefeated in their
hand so far and I think this might be
the hero to look out for in this
particular Sero because both of these
teams are undefeated with the hero and
also this is the hero when gaming
Gladiators they lost a chin when they
met in the group stage I just think it's
really scary for non-gaming gladiators
today cuz every other team is so used to
buying Midas going late game and gaming
will you do that so hopefully everyone
did their homework and they're ready to
not lose in 20 minutes like I did to
gaming and they can beat them
it feels so bad when you say it like
that we're like all up game gladies and
then it's the reality like yeah we had
to face that that was our first uh patch
up in the main stage it is what it is it
is what it is re what how do you feel
about the The Meta shift and some new
Heroes that we're seeing mostly at this
main stage I just love when teams are
innovating right uh when they when you
come into the games and you really
expect like what's going to happen lgd I
think they have that like they pulled
the Tinker in the last series against
Spirit it was pretty good game like they
could have won easily it was like
70-minute game again but the gaming
glider they're like they're in
innovating like every game they're
bringing new Heroes like they have this
trick like play style that they invented
but they also like Innova in terms of
Heroes as well because they brought a
hoscar yesterday as well and they
brought the Underlord back from the you
know nobody picked that hero for a long
time so they're like they're thinking
about like they have the structure of
like how they want to play but they're
still like adding on top of it new new
stuff and I'm I'm like for Spirit for
example they're like very solid very
steady but they're not like very
Innovative in that sense the only Magnus
but I mean everybody's playing Magnus
right now it's also collaps Magnus yeah
kind of classic a little bit of cheat in
that there were a lot of teams yesterday
though that had that Innovation too I
remember b boom they brought out the
Dragonite a hero that hadn't been picked
at ti2 yet so we saw yesterday we
started yesterday with six teams we
ended yesterday with three teams if you
missed it luckily for you we have a
little bit of a recap and we get to see
all the highlights of the action that
took place in day two here at climate
pledge arino
to die in the footstep of his own
Fountain yes Ultra kill for Daio will
chasing the dawn breaker ultimate coming
in for the
turn collapse you cannot be
underestimated Team
Liquid versus game in
Gladiators you don't want to give up
this ran celery deep in the corner how
do you get this guy out of here
that's beautiful but immediately the bkb
going off they are doing a lot of damage
the necron is getting low can they
finish and is just cleaning up with
theeler do on through the pit but he
missed the ages Luna Siege it is all the
more dangerous once your tier three is
down and you start getting those bouny
Glades into play trying to pull Dau out
of position almost got him but he pushed
a little bit over to the side instead
Harpoon pulling in the
kuna this one up he has no bkb you got
to remember this going to be D straight
up immediately now liquid left at four
versus is going to stand his Granda
Quint what a hit on through with a
swashb almost finishing up the r is
going to run down Mickey on his first SL
they are absolutely going to be losing
four here meanwhile mid lane they are
fighting this one out Quinn once again
survives on just a little bit of damage
he actually went for that kill you mad
man the block The Shield is just enough
they get celery out of it but Nick he's
going to be in trouble as soon as Z dies
they're going to turn all their
attention over this guy the the he gets
it just on the tip Quinn G is called
gameing GL ators they will bring down
Team Liquid Azure Ray versus b boom
T but FY wait he B back FY does he have
enough to stay alive though the stun is
there a long duration but no he's gone
just like that one gpk stunned for a
little while chalice still there for the
control but he's out of position 3
second stun starts to fall and gone can
they find more but there's the reaper
sight there for a turnar around the
fight it's lasted too long this is where
s shows up takes the down two seconds
done on to S to get the kill but he
transfers it over gets the cheese off in
time the Lotus not sure what it was but
now he's over to the side and S still
living somehow
some he's going to do it triple kill for
gpk can they do it they take him down
gpk trying to
run is too strong
they see gpk decide to jump on him to
start make him less tanky with a Chrono
for the turn and the Deep's being thrown
out and ripping them to Treads they
don't head for the roach they just head
down the lane right now b boom trying to
hold for all their worth but do they
have enough damage do they have enough
to take him down Nightfall he's out of
the base yet again he's die 80 Seconds
gone a aay they lasted long enough and
one death was all it took
team spirit versus
LGT
gaming they're stepping out of the base
here he's able to get the jump get the
back straight away into the fair push
the B fly the take down the bkb go for a
second round trying to escape him with
the in jumps forward drive by with the
Xbox shos out of the game as well Barett
take this game one 76 minutes
the side
of is there he's able to away from the
initial attemp but still drag him back
towards the rest of the team there down
T is coming SP pretty the full back
title there pulling them back the fear
straight down nothing to say the Magnus
will fall drags back sh they fully Focus
the spect the follows there for a double
kill for collapse a spirit they'll lose
your Tor but they make pay they'll find
the third triple kill for
collapse the Chas our planet Ultra kill
23 minutes in for collapse on the
CK gaming
Gladiators verus
aure Theo getting healed from the
sideline from tofu they're going to have
to do a lot more healing than that
they're going to be able to kill off the
edge eventually as chalice is now going
to die and just like that it's a five
versus three so their racks will end up
falling at 18 and2 minutes gaming
Gladiator playing way too fast for a r
to handle oh L's not going to be too
happy with the beginning of this game
holy Jesus those the biggest inner fire
I've ever seen already three kills for
gaming gladi Theus under his tier one
Tower where fall as well a 1K lead at10
seconds the battle begins
that's our three remaining teams there
we sold them lgd gaming Gladiators and
team spirit yesterday we did see liid b
boom and Aur Ray end their TI 12 run
they should be extremely happy with
where they placed because it was a tough
run for themselves tough opponents all
around and that is how our bracket is
shaping up did you guys do your bracket
predictions by the way in the the client
your Oracle you didn't I didn't I never
did how how accurate well
I don't I don't know if I have to
explain the other winners in the finals
I think I had a jur ray reaching top
three but that didn't happen but after
what happened yesterday these guys we
got to give them credit after they lost
first they managed to win against b boom
you know there was some beef going on
some all chat some question marks in the
all chat and after that seems like the
job was done you know they came here to
play they came here to beat the bed boom
and then you know this is the team that
formed pretty much this is the streamer
team when they wanted to you know show
that they can still do it on the main
stage these are the players that don't
receive salaries some of them and they
just wanted to do it for fun they lost
big smiles on their faces and I think we
got to give give credit and big Applause
for what they've managed to do at this
di yeah the other team I wanted to
mention is uh liquid because they're the
the only one who actually managed to
take down games from both gaming and the
spirit so they're like I think for to me
at least they're deserving to be like in
the top three to top four but you know
because the bracket happened to be that
way he they actually eliminated already
so but it's sad it's sad to have have
them go a lot of really good showings I
want to talk about fantastic showings
though enough to break TI records okay
it's been a wild month and so we've had
some oldtime TI records set during this
TI 12 so in a single match these are our
new records that we created this year
throughout the 3 weeks TA 2000 getting
two TI records for himself new as well k
in it's in the same game TA 2000 he did
play nasar and broke those records he's
an insane player usually when we talk
about TA 2000 he was the guy that plays
these Agy carry Heroes but he also
Shines on some of these melee Heroes as
well and also as you've seen Neo Doom
GPM this guy is just a monster I mean
he's been the driving force of the new
lgd as well calling some of these shots
and you know TI 23 23 leers kage on his
Spectre he also broke a couple of
Records in that game as well this guy is
just insane really glad that ver Pro
Show some Top Class DOA at TI I like the
Nightfall one 334 map pings yeah they're
by far the team that pings the most
they're like 600 and everybody then
there's like Talon with 400 and
everybody else that I mean you can
expect this yeah if you play pubz with
Nightfall you know that he loves just
pinging and talking you can know like
you kind of know how he's on a team just
of how much he talks in games and pubs
cuz you always talk more in real games
and pubs so if he talks a lot in pubs
I'm sure his pings are just crazy in a
tournament it's also the most skilled
stat right there on the spot because you
know you have to have a skill to Ping
300 times a game but other St like you
know Naga 1,000 GPM like it's whatever
like it's long game like we all know
that but the pinks it's a skill the the
snaking one was interesting as well very
quickly because it's now no longer the
longest game so it makes more sense if
you had the longest game placing that
many obser awards would make sense but
now no longer the longest game but still
holds that record for this te as the
most observe Awards placed uh look I
don't really have a segue for this one
all I'm going to say is I'm excited to
hear a little bit more about some meta
changes some big heroes that showed up
yesterday and to give us that
information it's
pedge thanks everybody yeah we have a
huge match coming up today uh lgd coming
from the winter bracket they've played
the entire tournament with a unique
style they've been playing up meta they'
bought few hand amitis compared to the
other teams and it rewarded them heavily
they won the vast majority of their
games until yesterday where they
faltered a little bit now and uh one
thing that was trending for them in the
previous matches is they were winning
with Magnus in almost every series that
they played it and surprisingly uh they
didn't ban Spirit breaker uh xia said
that he didn't think the hero was
overpowered now he's a big spammer so
he's probably just biased here but it's
a seventh most banned hero for the
entire tournament so far so the fact
that they finally banned it for the
first time yesterday means that meta is
shifting a little bit and maybe lgd is
feeling less confident in their ideas
now that they're getting some losses and
in terms of the Magnus what had
accomplished they won three of their
last uh series with the Magnus but this
one yesterday was a little bit too tough
they got behind in the laning stage
against team spirit's Farm heavy style
and normally you would think that their
High Tempo play style would be able to
beat that but in every single one of
these clips even though they're getting
successful kills they are still behind
in net worth because team spirit was so
good at playing the map here this is a
clip we saw earlier in one of the uh the
highlight reels but this is a great
moment they killed the enemy carry with
a great RP Magnus has been successful
yesterday in getting these grabs that
are difficult to snag and giving really
solid team fight power but team spirit
was just too good against it so
hopefully for lgd they don't falter from
their ideas and their confidence after
their loss yesterday and we'll see how
they can do against gaming Gladiators
who so far has looked pretty
Unstoppable thank you so much Purge
while we're you know talking about some
other people and hearing from other
people let's hear from slack and Casey I
do believe they're in the crowd
somewhere oh that's right n we are here
for another classic crowd Vibe check in
the morning Casey's volume is up all the
way so I thought I'd really get us some
energy crowd good morning how you doing
Gamers all right you we ready to go talk
to some psychos I'm not going to call
them psychos hi friends hi non psycho
friends first thing I did was I said who
is here with a big group of friends and
what did you guys say we made friends
all day today okay
really then what is his name clay and
what is his name Ryan are those your
actual names
yes all right all right this is so
wholesome hello who want to be camera
scker out my way excuse me hello you
seem excited GG fans over here how you
feeling good really good who's going to
win GG all oh wow how
surprising say something I wouldn't
expect uh North America for the win wow
that was very not a lot of people would
expect that how you doing hello good to
say look at all these signatures he's
got Ary got hit how you feeling great
how you doing I'm good okay got this one
what what and they got this one oh yeah
we're coming back shop is going to take
it
very depressing Stu Casey what's going
on down there what do you got all right
slack it's time for us to do something
we've done every year since ti4 I don't
know if you're ready for this myON give
me your camera oh
yes here I'm giving you my my microphone
I'm sorry but it's time for you to
experience my pain yes and be
interviewed by slacks I'm so sorry come
myON once more every year we have shown
our wonderful camera crew and this year
myON is back on the camera the myON lore
continues my so good to have you the
crowd Lo and they love you again myin oh
my goodness they love you sir we need to
expand our myin lore what is your middle
name Reggie Reggie his middle name it's
reie it's
reie thank you so much myON it's Reggie
because my mom named me that because it
has what what letters two GG's in the
middle
baby thank you
myin my another year another Banger
Casey you're lifting that so well thank
you so much Casey thank you yes
incredible can I have the camera
too who wants to replace
slacks oh that's a hord I think we need
to go I don't know what that is that
means go so back take it back hey what's
up flax thank you so much Casey thank
you as well I loved knowing that uh not
only doing Adam my's middle name but uh
that he's a game of Gladiators fan for a
good reason I I mean he made the their
their days shorter you know they were
long days and he's like you know I want
to get this camera it's pretty heavy but
uh yeah really glad that now we know his
middle name yeah well look we'll see
when gaming Gladiator is are playing
we're going to have schedule you get to
see we already know that they're in the
top three but we're going to see that
they are in the first series here so
they are up against lgd and then
potentially another long day for
themselves up against team spirit if
they do make it through they already had
a marathon of a day yesterday they were
first and fourth Series
yesterday I just hope that daa feels way
better today because he was very sick
yesterday and he still managed to
perform like insanely well he was like
15012 on the Vier game last one and it
was like after for the second series
they already played they're walking
confidently can we see the Raa no oh
yeah you can kind of see him a little
bit in the back there but uh Ace is
leading the charge he's doing all the
signatures uh for the team of gaming
gladiators but lgd this bounce back for
them actually I'm going to change this
let's just talk about all the carries
okay because there's still three teams
left we don't necessarily have to talk
about this exact matchup right now
because we could be seeing any iteration
of the grand finals so we have a car
comparison here we still got Daio left
in the B you already talked about res he
might be feeling a little bit under the
weather despite how good of a
performance he had yesterday there's
still the chance it affects him shirou
is the carry for lgd and then yor of
course being the carry for teen spirit
so this is their hero pool of what they
played at ti2 and their average kills
deaths and assists over the course of
this tournament theal set here is that
they they both like all all of them like
have pretty similar death rate which is
uh kind of insane because yoro like is
playing like longer games with shirro
but but for D it's like the same rate
considering the theay the games are like
finishing like within 20 to 30 minutes
because like this guy he's playing Super
aggressive and he's not afraid like he
he said it multiple times he's not
afraid to die he's just doing whatever
his team is needed and he's he has like
full confidence of like Quinn and Ace
like you know following up and not dying
like and and carrying the game for him
as well you can also see Spirit and lgd
have this 45 46 minute average timing
where gaming you know they're finishing
the games on average a lot quicker and
so so that's kind of where you see yoro
get a lot more kills on average but I
also think it's impressive that he's
managing to die pretty much the same
amount of times with more games or more
time being played in the game yeah we
also had their shortest games 19 29 and
30 minutes respectively so that's
massive G Gladiators getting a 19-minute
win for themselves yeah it's pretty
insane what they can do when they get
the hands on the heroes that they like
to play and they it feels like they they
got the heroes that they wanted in the
last eight games they played because
they wanted to speed things up they're
bringing out these enchantresses this
chin and we've seen Thea you know having
slightly more deaths because this guy is
nuts like I really love to watch this
guy play DotA cuz you mentioned the
vaver game yesterday where he was diving
Tower four minutes in he's on tier 2
Tower he's building earn of Shadows on a
carry something that we've seen only on
Spectre pretty much he wants to keep
this aggression this is the team that
once they realize that you're bleeding
your lanes are bleeding they're not
going to let you go I also like the way
he's walking on the stage like d he he
always feels that you know that love
from the crown he's like putting his
hands up like you know know give me that
love and he he wants to have that
attention right and then I think for G
for the lgd the biggest challenge right
now for this series is going to be like
how strong of the lanes they can get
because this is the team that they're
focusing like on this mid game
strategies and like how their Heroes
synergize well between each other but to
me the most important thing is like how
are they going to get out from the lanes
today I think with uh their draft from
yesterday I'm hoping that lgd kind of
changes things up they picked slow
Heroes I think for Spirit which was fine
the games went really long they had a
tinker yesterday a spectre and I'm
hoping for them to pick faster paced
Heroes kind of adapt maybe they take the
tides the Chens the inches or conas
something that allows them to fight
gaming Gladiators really early on cuz I
think if you're able to contest them and
you drag the game out longer that's how
you have the ability to actually beat
this team how quick is it to make that
adjustment though I think for a caliber
team like lgd they can probably do it a
night uh like an afternoon oh really
that quick okay they have one of the
best coaches in the world they have
xiawei so he's probably cooking
something up right now he's probably
telling the boys what they're going to
do just trust me I'll draft you
something to win and hopefully they win
yeah look they've had a couple days to
see that tempo of gaming Gladiators
we'll see how they do Fair up but before
we do anything else we have to get our
day started so let's do it let's make
some noise everyone it's the final day
of ti2 starting
[Applause]
[Music]
now it is a beacon sounding a c to
greatness that Echoes
worldwide a crucible forging a single
Contender worthy of rising above the
very best and a
celebration Gathering a community of
millions to witness history
unfold it is the
international the final Proving Ground
where the world's finest DOTA teams
assemble to face each other in the alt a
test each Challenger has earned this
honor through hardfought victories in
matchups around the
globe the journey has tested some more
than
others but the favorites and underdogs
all know the road to the ages defies all
prediction and anyone can carve a new
Legacy here
the agis of Champions returns to Seattle
and with it the eyes of the
world three teams compete for ultimate
Glory only one can seize
imortality who will emerge
Victorious the battle begins
it's our final day ti2 at the end of
today at the end of two series we will
be seeing a team lift the ages and I
cannot wait our lower bracket finals is
going to start very soon but first let's
welcome our first team
[Applause]
[Music]
gameing
Gladiators the lower bracket dominators
they have knocked out five teams already
they've been here since the first round
and here they are on the final day
walking to their Booth they're going to
have to win and they're going to have to
face lgd if they want to continue
[Applause]
[Music]
lgd
gaming they face a team of spirit
yesterday it was a tough loss for them
but they have a second life they can go
up against team spirit in the grand
finals again if they do become Victors
in this lower bracket finals but for the
first time in ti2 they're on the edge of
elimination they're going to have to
pull out everything in this best of
three and gunana you talked about what
changes are going to have to happen and
the fact that they are one of the best
coaches to make it happen for them yeah
I really think the draft is going to
play the biggest part both teams already
proved their players are good enough to
just be here and they don't need to do
anything special so it's going to break
down to the draft mostly and we'll see I
think gaming Gladiators have a really
good read on the meta of the tournament
and kind of just breaking it compared to
everyone else playing really fast and
I've really like the way they draft it
seems really hard to beat them in the
draft so I think if lgd can even get an
even draft with a good you know tempo
for the game it'll be they'll be in a
good position mhm look we we pulled all
the extra stops for this lower bracket
finals to help us with the draft as well
we got chiefstick joining us by the way
can we get a round of applause for her
crowd yeah that's what I thought thanks
that hi yeah I just appeared out of
nowhere you really did yeah La Costa is
gone now sorry you just ate him you
consumed him and you're like I'm taking
his spot here and you're going to help
us talk about gaming gladiate is lgd for
the lower bracket Grand finals do you
agree with Gunner that they're able to
make this uh change in tempo for
themselves despite the really rough loss
especially that 76 minute game yesterday
oh my God watching that was
heartbreaking for lgd uh I believe that
they are a super top team obviously
coming this far I think when we saw them
play against azra Ray it was kind of
like uh there that they exampled how
they lost the early game but they really
understood their timings they really
understood uh where they wanted to go
with their team and they the moves that
they pulled off to kind of bring back
and equalize the game and then take the
advantage and win and just close it out
very cleanly without throws like that's
the lgd I want to see coming here smart
disciplined and ready to own yeah but uh
they're not facing that R they're facing
gaming gladers who are RAR making any
mistakes right they're just like very
confident going objective after
objective and if they're not confident
that can break it they're not going to
go for it they're not going to give the
chances so it's it's a very different uh
game we're going to witness here it's
tough to know what is going to be their
win conditions before we see their
drafts but I want to talk about stable
players for them who has been the most
consistent in showing up and I feel for
both these teams it's the off laners
it's Ace it's new for both teams new is
also really new to this team uh he only
came in off to two or three you're
laughing cuz new is new new is new yeah
I thought so I thought you'd have a
little bit of giggle over that one
but yeah he he's quite new to this team
but he slaughtered in perfectly and
there are a lot of games that I saw him
being the an the one that's holding down
the for for them holding those defenses
to allow shirou that time to be able to
build what he needs on his carry I think
the offlaners that are left in this
tournament are very like stable and all
of their like initiation power like
they're doing it very well and very
methodically and uh for new like even
Centaur game yesterday he was carrying
the game so hard on the hero that you
would not expect that to have that much
of an impact so that makes like him
incredible like skilled player that
knows his timing very well and also like
you know he he delivers so this is like
this is the strength of their team like
for sure also during last CH qualifier
last year people were singing his
Praises new and they were saying you
know he's going to be on the best
Chinese team by the next TI and here he
is he's proving himself at TI he's
already top three so I definitely think
that the off liners for both of these
teams are kind of their like rocks where
no matter how the game is going they're
going to win their Lanes they're going
to have a very stable game and always do
their job kind of no matter the draft no
matter the hero out of the situation
yeah I really want to highlight as well
it's not just the off laner it's who
you're laning with the PA Falls I think
new uh prior to this team he played on V
gaming he played with FY now he's
playing with Planet who not as big of a
name known but I think planet is easily
one of the best uh PA four players I've
seen this year playing this guy is
phenomenal um I would hype him up any
chance I got last yesterday I was or two
days ago I was saying I want to see
planet rubic we saw it he owned with it
he's the only guy winning with it really
in this tournament I think planet is
amazing and seeing him and you laying
together have been I mean they've just
been destroying yeah I want to ask a
question off the back of that then
because we talked about the stable off
laners as a mid player Gunner how
important is it to have a stable off
laner that allows your pause for to do
so much or is it not so much for you as
it is important for your safe Lane it
matters honestly for all three lanes if
you win your off Lane it allows the five
to rotate through the gate right now
gank the carry it allows the fours to
check the water runes the power runes at
6 8 minutes and kind of everything I
think if you win your off Lane it almost
wins your other two lanes just for you
and it's really hard these days to just
Stomp the mid and a pure One V one we've
honestly seen it the last two days which
was very surprising that the mid lane
match ups went really bad we saw the
Dragonite vers Puck we saw the void vers
Puck so maybe it's just Puck not the mid
lane but they've kind of had rough times
where the game snowball out of control
but I wouldn't expect that today I think
it's more so going to be mid lane stable
and whether s side Lanes kind of
snowball one way or the other also
concering how important the laning are
right now like if it's really important
to have the Synergy between position
three and four like same as like a safe
Lane and and you you almost like need to
have like those two uh players to be
like a friend because like it was it was
the same for me when I was playing with
Z like we had an incredible incredible
like uh you know working working
together time because like we we
understood each other very well we are
friends and this is like what's
important for for these players as well
like to have that Synergy and like you
know talk talk with about mistakes like
improve on laning and understand each
other without even War sometimes how
would you compare uh Quinn and nothing
to say in the mid lane whether it's hero
pool whether it's the importance their
team places on them how would you
describe them or compare them
G uh they're honestly pretty different
myths I think Quinn when you think of
him you think of him as more either a
spirit or a counter pick like he played
huskar and he plays the necros these
like kind of annoying Heroes that just
you feel it feels really bad to players
and I would say nothing to say outside
of his Tinker I think he's a lot more of
he just plays his good Heroes
uh he's really confident playing just
the same Heroes all the all the time he
plays Ember Pango he plays a lot of
Magnus for a really long time which is
kind of coming back in this tournament
so I think for Quinn you're looking more
for this guy to Snowball the game for
you and win the game for you and nothing
to say to just have a solid game plan
all right we'll see if they're going to
draft around that if we're going to see
any new picks for them or what's going
to be banned as we do have our lower
bracket Grand final game
one G
lgd
gaming versus
game in
Gladiators game one
second Ben bristle is what the audience
is saying how much uh weight would you
put into that one G uh for lgd I think
bristle is one a Gaming's best
strategies especially cuz it's Ace you
allow Ace to get a carrier in the off
Lane that's pretty much his bread and
butter he plays lone he he used to be a
carry so it's not surprising that he's
able to play the carries in the off Lane
win his Lane and just have a stable game
I don't think bristle be is letting
through guys ever ever again I think
that here is way too hard to deal with
and uh you know when AA is B and like
what is the best answer for ug against
this hero so I think one of the big
reasons why bristle is so strong is his
counters are also meta so it ends up
that the Primal Beast gets banned the
Phoenix gets banned the a gets banned
and so all of your responses to bristle
are just banned do the nature of the
draft and so it's just a strong hero now
yeah and the Viper and hoodwin are not
yeah the other ways to break him and
reduce his HP region don't really exist
anymore
so I love what lgd did against Bristol
back when they were playing they had
this Magnus and they always like break
his position because he's always in the
front and they they managed to take him
with the Cur like way back into his own
team and then muera like with extra
damage to to stop that hero it actually
works but and also you don't get damage
from when you're in ulti you don't get
damage from spills but uh yeah it's not
going to be seen anytime soon I see the
ENT and the Chen band here so a lot of
importance placed on taking out what
they deem is seler's most confident and
Broken Heroes but now I see chaos Knight
left in the pool as well which is
another one that has seen ban after ban
after ban and Primal Beast is leing true
to too true I didn't even notice that
one I want to see Primal Beast so bad
yeah yeah I'm begging them to ban CK I
mean they probably just take it they
have first pick I I'm really glad to see
the Chen ban though I think a lot of
teams seem to be kind of disrespecting
game and I think they kind of showed
early on that they're capable of this uh
death ball type lineup let's go Primal
woo all right but they they show that
they can go fast and hard and they're
like super happy to just run you over
and we still see teams picking like Naga
first phase against them it's like you
cannot disrespect G in this way
especially when you leave the Chen in
the pool even to the second phase so lgd
taking that CH out I'm very happy to see
it also the enchantress I think kind of
does the same thing whereas they both
win their Lanes they're very stable
which leads Daio kind of gets to do his
own thing and celer can help Quinn which
is again kind of their bread and butter
and
uh they buy AAS they push Towers really
fast it's kind of everything they want
in one package I also like that ljd
chose to let the Primal be through
because I think for Ace that here is not
really what he's looking for
specifically because he he used to play
like this long Droid Bristol back type
of hero that are more scalable but for
Primal Beast he doesn't he doesn't scale
as much like in terms of like at least
Tower push right like he's not he's not
going to be like the hero who's going to
take all the towers from the lgd so it's
already like I think it's good for lgd
that they don't have that pressure
already starting from the first pick and
I like the Chen and chant just BS for
sure the nice thing with the Primal is
Quinn's been practicing and playing it
quite a bit in his pubs and his games so
it ends up being a flex as well so you
can't just end up just instant picking a
carry counter pick or a mid counter pick
cuz it'll go to both I would say they're
valuing it more as an off laner right
now just due to how kind of the map set
up that the off laners get up get more
Farm than the mids right now and Primal
Beast is here that can Farm really fast
with just trampling over camps and waves
at the same time so it ends up just
becoming a stronger core in the off Lane
if you get away with the lane is that
every team is doing that or more gaming
glad specific when you get your hands on
a primal um I don't know if I can speak
for most teams cuz some teams their off
laners don't play Primal so it ends up
just kind of being forced to Mid but for
gaming I would say right now I'd expect
this to be an off Lane second remain
primal's like weird when it goes off
Lane because it it can be punishable but
there's ways to bring him back into the
game like for example your fork can go
and stack like the triangle and it's
very easy for him to take Stacks with
and you're for this we've seen Primal in
theane abely obliterated but as as hit
that bkb timing it's just his spells do
so much damage just alone like you don't
even need anything more than that bkb
that that's when like games have turned
around and they've made these comebacks
Primal is such a hero not to be
underestimated I mean it's also very
hard to take him down right there's not
a lot of things that that could do that
in this meta I mean I think Mo would be
nice but it's already out of the
question and uh I mean for for Primal
usually pick uh they they they don't
really go for big KBS nowadays they also
go for different item builds like with a
blade mail heart and just create
chaos usually the important thing is
buying uh picking a stun for the safe
Lane you want to pick a Sven a chaos
Knight are the important ones not just
because they have the damage to like out
CS the Primal but mostly because they
have a stun to prevent the trample and
something really interesting with the
Phoenix is Fenix is good in the game
versus Primal with the sunr is doing
percent damage kind of chewing through
primal's Health but in the lane the fire
Spirits don't affect you you don't
attack you're disarmed anyway while
trampling so it ends up actually being a
really comfortable Lane for Primal there
I completely agree with you I think
something like clockwork is way better
than having the things there against the
Primal Primal Lane yeah purely for the
lane it kind of secures you can pick a
range carry then uh the popular carries
versus Primal either melee with stun or
range with kite I'm sure the lgd want to
B this Phenix on the off Lane with the
center for now 10 seconds like at least
that I I would be thinking about that I
guess now for G if they want they have
grimstroke available for them if they do
want to I mean it's just good for any
side lane but if they do want Primal in
the off Lane it's going to especially be
nice there they're probably going to end
up taking their carry which is really
cool from the Centaur pick cuz now if
gaming wants to instantly counter they
can get carry counter pick for the side
of lgd plus the lane counter with the
Primal Beast so it's kind of this weird
position where if you delay your carry
too long you're allowing the Centaur to
be free in the draft and if you pick it
now you open up you know Dao to get
countered in the game which we've seen
him counter pick with the Razer
yesterday where it had a rough game and
I was even worried that he would carry
but he just ended up destroying the game
with how good of a Razer it was I love
this life stealer B I think it's the
only two teams that are actually raiding
this Hero at all because nobody else are
really looking for that one and dich is
like he's known for his life stealer as
well yeah we saw it yesterday in the
Azure Ray Series where bom and the the
strongest thing about the life steer is
that he sits in his Lane for 10 to 12
minutes and you can never kick him out
which really hurts how gaming gliders
wants to play they want to move their
hers around take the towers really fast
and when there's a carrier that's
sitting in the lane and you can never
pressure into them it feels really bad
for how you want to move around the map
yeah and for gaming to to have that Hero
on your safe Lane and not care about
like how to make his gam play better and
like have complete freedom on supports
you know this is what they excel at like
their two supports are usually running
around mid lane and helping uh ccnc to
you know do all this pressure and like
start from the mid lane this is like
what this teams really excel at
the did end up getting picked up by the
way sheep that was one that you were
talking about it's just really powerful
hero I mean you play around this inksell
like Purge of the stuns it makes it so
hard for anyone like you're playing with
a primal already who's just going to
want to go in and Destroy everyone like
this Grim on top of that elevates his uh
like strengths throughout all stages of
the game early mid to late I think the
hero is just to to be given so freely to
gameing I think was 10 was rough for lgd
and now they have a Sor on top of that
to cover their team fight I mean looking
at these three Heroes like I don't I
don't really like it for gladi ear that
much just purely because they're uh
going away from their idea of like
pressuring so much and I think it
benefits lgd because in that game like
the normal game where there's not a lot
of pressure I think this is like their
best chance of like taking the series
down I also think so the way the draft
kind of plays out these days is the
second phase is really hard to ban
Heroes as they only get get one ban for
the side of lgd so they end up picking
the one hero that they think is the best
the lifer and they have to give up the
griin they have to give up anything else
so pretty much the only band you really
get and feel confident about are the
first phase and they chose to take out
pretty much Sal Heroes they take out the
Chen ench which are I think are top two
right now in this tournament and so now
you see him Force the S yeah as you said
I don't really feel too confident with
this just because it's moving into
they're playing into lgd's book I would
say and that is something that has not
really gotten them to where they are
right now in the tournament and the
Shadow Demon is such a great pick up to
stopping this Primal Bas from doing
anything in the mid game like the lane
might be rough a little bit but I mean
looking at their support right they
don't have really good way of stopping
him but in the mid game like against
playing against Purge and the Shadow
Demon as a primal base is actually
impossible yeah the it's also really
good for grimstroke you can Purge ink
swall anytime you see a hero the Primal
surprisingly it purges the charge so he
can't even charge out when he get Purge
exactly uh and the defensive Purge is
really nice for silencer too maybe he
can click it on the Phoenix early in the
fight the Phoenix will get stuff
off we see the cow I mean the cow is
amazing here as well because those two
supports they don't have really a good
mechanic to stop him from charging
neither it's Primal Beast so they're
going to have to think about buying ules
on somebody to be able to stop his
charges but it's still like we've seen
so many times the Spirit Break is just
like going first and the net first like
even after losing his Lane horribly it
doesn't matter as soon as you're buy
like Midas and octarine you just pushing
every wave and then you have this
mechanic of like coming back to the
fights from anywhere else and I think
it's really important in this patch to
have one of those Heroes that can
connect easily to the fight and like
being on the other side of the map so
it's either like Spectre don't breaker
or Spirit breaker that's why those
heroes are seeing more all right so
there's some really quick stuff uh Quinn
played versus Spirit breaker mid because
that's what this is we see the centur so
we know that this will be nothing to say
hero and it was versus n pandas kotaka
and he absolutely destroy the spirit
breaker and as we talked about earlier
Quinn's this type of player who you give
him a counter pick like nek over some
melee strength
and he's going to do some work in the
game I honestly was thinking that they
might put the Primal mid cuz that was
the match up he played versus n pandas
whereas Primal vers Spirit breaker he
solo kill the lane the game ended in 20
something minutes but they picked nekro
which is if anything is a stronger Lane
Now versus Spirit breaker so I would be
really confident now just for the fact
that they have a hero to play around
with Quinn yeah even like despite that I
kind of don't like the supports on lgd I
think that they're both not high on
burst damage they're pretty slow I think
it's much easier for G to make moves
talked about how they like to kind of
crush early I think now with this
winning mid match up I think they can
make much more plays or they can even
just kind of play it chill and wait for
their timings on Primal or whoever and
just make sure that they're playing
defensively where they use Global to
cover any ganks that lgd try and make
yeah it seems like they don't really
think about like going to the mid game
and like how necros might be bit against
porge and like not you know like not
being that tanky core but at the same
time like they're just looking purely on
L and they're like this NE is going to
Stomp the spear break so hard that they
going to like like you know completely
run them over but I'm still worried
because usually their lineups they have
this good Tower damage and this is how
they were able to uh close the games up
so fast but on this lineup specifically
there's no like hero that you know kills
Tower so they need to find some uh
material like Tero blade or something
from Dasia side that actually like helps
them take down objectives in this game a
lot of their success with the Decker
ends up pairing it with other push or
other healing they picked it with Dazzle
offlane in the past where they both just
ball up and they go just end the game
and they probably picked it with tides
and Chens so they don't really have the
draft that you win 20 minutes and you
walk down the lane yet we'll see what
Dau ends up picking but I would say it's
outside of teror Blade that's not really
his heroo he doesn't really pick the
early
game
Alchemist that's one way to up the to me
this game looks like the game one
against liquid where they chose to go
for you know regular lineup and it
didn't really work for them and they
lost that game to to liquid so I think
that like to me it at at least that this
is the game for lgd if they manage to
like get out from the lanes evenly or
like not super stomped and uh you know
going to the mid game I think they have
way better chances I want to trust this
uh spear breaker I think spear breaker
is a crazy hero but I'm too worried
about the mid match up going in the way
for gaming Gladiators so I think that
Quinn will just Stomp the mid lane and
just carry the momentum throughout the
whole game do you think even if uh the
spirit Burger does get shut down in Lane
he's still going to have that disruption
in team fights and will still have an
impact that could car Mar a later game
for lgd if there's one hero I would want
to get crushed on Mid Spirit Break so he
has that going for him that that one
small glimmer of hope yeah I agree with
you guys although that being said I I
really like game's speed that they can
pull up here I think like when Alchemist
gets his blink dagger and they're able
to kind of move around the map and be
really fast about it I think lgd are
going to struggle playing into this
Global uh anything else you guys want to
talk about very quickly especially this
act we've seen it a couple times for Dao
is it going to be that thing that ties
up all together the make a break for
gaming gladies quickly Gana uh yeah I
think the Alchemist Lane is going to be
really stable top and he'll have a
really good time and just they have so
much time to make space for him just
bodies on the map and pressure that
he'll have a good time forarm his
Radiance all right I like it let's see
how much confidence uh gaming Gladiator
coach has in their
draft thank you very much I am standing
by with Cy of a gaming Gladiators who uh
you had a late last late night last
night my man how much which time did you
have to prepare for today as a whole did
you only get to prepare for lgd or did
you prepare for lgd and spirit we only
prepared for lgd we didn't have that
much time as well I also want to get
some sleep it's pretty important but one
game at a time you know so no
preparation for Spirit one game at a
time and you come up with a silencer
what's this guy doing in this draft for
you guys hopefully silenc is
Phoenix I never knew DOTA was just that
simple now you only got to prepare for
lgd but I remember that during the ri
Masters you and I got quite a few
opportunities to interact and you seemed
confident in your lower bracket run it
unfortunately got cut short at Fourth
Place why should I believe you this time
that you're going to make it all the way
I mean this time we already made it to
third right so it's better than last
time so you should just
believe se you ready to watch some
DOTA let's get lower bracket finals
started let's indeed here we go ladies
and gentlemen lgz up against gaming
Gladiators to start off this final day
of the international fog we heard there
from c y coming in with a bit of a
different pick this game on gaming
Gladiators side the silencer could this
be the answer to the Phoenix a hero that
we're seeing time and time again so far
this tournament definitely feels like a
kind of cool pick a very different one
style here very good versus the Phoenix
but also versus these saves that we've
been seeing a lot coming out in this
tournament the Shadow Demon in
particular we've seen so many games
where people just get bailed out of
certain death very difficult if you're
globaled so we'll have to itemization
and stuff of course there's going to be
some demonic cleanses that you can
pre-cast and stuff like that we'll get
all into that as we do have an early
smoke from lgd let's see if they can get
the catch here coming in with the
wraparound trying to enter into gaming
Gladiators jungle but gaming Gladiators
they're hovering around that mid tier
one Tower and a bit of a tough point at
the map for lgd to
strike very unlikely somebody gets
caught out here gaming very prep super
prepared yeah they know this sort of
play is going to be coming out here I'm
looking forward to this one this looks
like it should be a pretty fight heavy
I say thater they kind of Step across
set up with A disruption you looking for
the follow contion there hold him back
doesn't matter you still fight The Who
on to celery celer taken down first BL
Ford if they can find something in
return G me Gladiators the curse upon
you they will at least get the trade
Quinn not able to get the first blood
but still getting that kill as the mid
lane is going to feel pretty good for
him as the necros especially versus that
Spirit breaker in particular too this is
a match up that Quinn could snowball out
of control just like panel was talking
about Planet messing with Thea quite a
bit here he's going to try and make it a
little bit more more Awkward for him on
his way back towards that Top Lane extra
bit of damage coming in and he'll
certainly have money to play with as he
was the one indeed to get that first
Blood lgd Planet not hesitating
whatsoever instantly buys out pretty
much everything I think triple mangoes
purchased up so he's looking to be
pretty aggressive up here a pretty
strong Lane I don't think that we've
seen too much anymore I know the Centaur
a ton but Centaur and Shadow Demon an
old classic very aggressive a lot of
damage if these two start to get a bit
of a level Advantage this Alchemist and
silencer could end up being very
vulnerable against the huge amounts of
burst that these two can come out within
the landing stage gaming Gladiators they
got to be careful up there yeah
absolutely this is probably the lane
where lots of chaos is going to be
happening mid lane I think we already
kind of expect the Quinn should be able
to take advantage of this one massively
versus nothing to say bottom Lane all
this one could also be pretty kill heavy
as well too especially for the side of
gaming already in underneath the tower
shirro in trouble one more slap from Ace
will get the job done Shiro taken down
Ace will lose his life but happily
taking that trade they're getting in and
taking the carry out all this is going
to be bloodthirsty in these side
Lanes overall as well what you sort of
take away from the the carry decisions
from both teams cuz it was quite a quick
pick with the Luna in response of The
Alchemist coming out at the end from uh
from gaming Gladiators do you feel this
was what lgd were going for for anyway
or do you think this was directly
because of the AL being picked I think
it probably could have been something
they were looking for anyway because of
the necros I know shirro he's one of the
few players that I seen that's actually
still doing this like 311 build even in
the early game he's very aggressive
likes him be involved early on so maybe
it's that mixed magical physical damage
they wanted just be able to have versus
the necro as well too and it fits for
kind of this early Style with the Shadow
Demon that can look to brawl and fight
often they probably a couple mixtures of
things that they did want it want with
it also is going to be very good for
this night vision of course too playing
with the spirit breaker playing with
this Luna night vision can be pretty
strong inside of these team fights
so so far looking at the last hit that's
the mid lane as you say as expected the
edge here for Quinn but look at Ace's
last hits right now bottom does get that
kill early on of course but he's only
got three to his name versus Shiro at
the
moment getting to the point already
where you know it's not easy for nothing
to say to sort of approach this midwave
as able to take huge amounts of damage
and favorable trade going the way of of
it's Quinn necros in this one V one Top
Lane Daio he's in a bit of trouble he's
got the concoction cooking up is he able
to throw it out he he holds it for the
the deny all right all right that'll
that'll get the job done he's out of
Lane for a few seconds but at least able
to stop lgd from getting the kill
against him but he is really struggling
on the last hit department so far new
and planted bringing it to him I knew
didn't win yesterday but made some
pretty amazing plays on and look at this
in the mid lane it's getting pretty
nasty Quinn just sort of running nothing
to say right back underneath the tier
two I mean what do you do at this point
in this one V one at the least he can go
back and he can just charge out and
stuff right so he can make moves all
over the match but it's a match up that
knows he's going to inevitably lose but
it is at least a hero that can make
moves around and is probably one of the
best recovery heroes in the game at the
moment so for sure and for gaming
Gladiators they need Quinn to be having
this sort of start in the mid because as
we're seeing on the side Lanes it's not
going quite as well for them yeah they
need somebody to build a rally around
especially The Alchemist is having this
slow of a start for Daio nice attempt
there from planet Trying to Catch the
Wave unable
to level three another big kill threat
that they're going to be able to have up
here on the side of lgd bottom though
Ace Contin to get aggressive and they've
got the inks well stun it'll allow them
to set up to take down while you smile
Gladiators whil they might not be
getting the easiest to farm here for
race down bottom they're finding action
Top Lane Dao it's going to fall pretty
low here to the poisons won't quite die
both new and Planet also getting beaten
down pretty low by zeler if he gets
another one could be a kill as he's
cooking up a concoction one more if
anything he's just going to allow planet
to try and find further connections but
the force there turn toward C in deu
he's stepping up he's got a hoop Stomp
and a double H celery he could be in a
lot of trouble andu will go with the
right clicks alone and takes celery down
backs away Mak sure not to use the
Double H to bring himself too low back
in nothing to say with the rotation
charges forward on towards Dao Dao this
time will not be able to deny himself
Planet gets the kill I mean these two
honestly planed and knew yesterday were
making magic happen again putting a ton
of pressure up here the silencers trying
to dissuade the pressure of course with
those Arcane curses but they're just
waiting patient and as you said there
they understand use the double edge go
for the right clicks very very
calculating in particular really knowing
his limits on this hero playing
aggressively despite his HP being
incredibly low in these situations and
there you see right away it's like yeah
he's losing the mid lane on the spirit
breaker but I think Spirit breaker
Primal Beast probably two of the best
heroes that can just easily make those
rotations get some good connection but
yeah Quinn he definitely will be an
issue that they're going to have to find
some answers and they do have answers to
say this game progresses they've got the
Demonic Purge it's always going to be
able to remove the ghost Tru they've got
this massive amount of magic damage that
comes from Phoenix and potentially from
the Luna he's not going for the beam
build just yet but of course he'll have
those points in later so overall for for
lgd the fact that they know that Quinn's
getting this completely uninterrupted
free Farm in the mid lane you don't
think they're too concerned about that
no I don't think so I mean there's going
to be of course a lot of plays that
happen with these you know Global
silences that can just potentially save
Quinn versus a lot of the burst and
whatnot but they probably feel like they
do have some answers since they have
that mixed magic nothing to say shows in
the mid that's deep they cff the wave U
not quite able to connect with the
initial slow see Quinn should be able to
close in with the the inell buff upon
him he's got the sight ready to drop
down if he feels that the kill is going
to be there he'll drop it and he's got
it quid able to take down nothing to say
10 time up top though dra and a spoted
bother being chased out by lgd
completely surrounded by the three of
them disruption is there to try and mess
up the ability for him to throw
concoction will sell stun and call for
stun to hit onto new but it won't save
Dao as he goes down once again planed
actually even holding the poisons I
think maybe just saving that kill there
for a new some calculation coming in 5
to four action packed early game
I this Top Lane he's sort of been what
knocked out of this Top Lane three times
already Dao it's not getting any easier
for him up here he's got pretty much
nothing right now I mean 2400 gold so
he's similar as that Spirit breaker but
level three only on The Alchemist so
far and soon to be hitting what level
five on you y massive amounts of bur
going to be coming in they've got this
decently sized creep wave pushing
forward in towards them as well so lgd
in a very happy spot in this Top Lane in
particular yeah they're starting to
leave Ace alone down bottom tofu is
trying to rectify what's going on up top
trying help out Daio yeah they hit it
with the scan though lgd so he'll be
knowing to say stay safe to close to the
tower he's unlikely to be caught out by
this
rotation nice attempt there by y Ace
maybe going to force a dive
here oh he actually stops it as well too
very well played but at the same time
why you smile he's down to the low
ground with the Sunray that was so quick
the Sunray but can he get away I don't
know if he can he's going to have a few
spirits to throw down onto Ace loen beam
as well trying to hold Ace back he's
going to continue to run this down
another SP slowing down the attack speed
it's enough to actually allow why SM to
get away meanwhile back on the top side
of the M Dao got taken down once again
this time Quinn turns up wants to try
and make lgd pay for it they will get
Nur return but they won't get nothing to
say just another instance now where Dao
he is not having fun up here he
certainly isn't butu does have to be a
little cautious the one thing about
Centaur playing versus silencer don't
want to die too much giving up that in
can be a problem for the
hers with the burst it's another SC kill
here for win this necro I think that's
what boots travel finished up so his
movement around the map is going to get
faster and faster now looking to
pressure I mean he's going to get good
damage on this Tower here good thing
that y's there to at least drag a little
bit but Quin just starts chasing he's in
under the tower celery he's getting do
by the two of them I don't think
there'll be any TP backup for this poor
old silence C he coming in now but
celery will still fall Planet finishes
off the kill question is if gaming
Gladiators can find some in return drao
is able to step in throw down the
concoction these are Big kills for
gladiators to be picking up same time
down bottom Ace chased upon by nothing
to say and Shir the ulate up in a second
here for the spirit breaker but he can't
quite find the vision nothing to say so
Ace he'll walk out alive once more a
good attempt but just a bit too tanky
see that he actually did put at least
two points in the loosen beam most of
these players haven't going for like the
113 build not able to get the kill but a
good attempt top three cores on the side
of gaming gladers even though Dao is
dying a lot up top he's still doing
pretty decent all things consider
espcially with the fact those kind of
last few deaths on New on that Top Lane
definitely swinging things back in favor
of gaming Gladiators and now can they
hold on to this mid Tower is the
question surrounded another easy kill
here for Quinn to get involved and now
dominating on the necros and he knows
immediately the Shadow Demon was getting
those Stacks up we'll be able to take
them away instantly aggressive posturing
by Gaming Gladiators again playing
around Quinn with this strong start yeah
they can play aggressively around him on
this mid area of the map and at the same
time if lgd look for any moves now the
Sid Lanes with the boots to travel Quinn
he's likely to be there every single
time so whilst lgd got away with those
early kills the whole the the difficulty
it stepped up massively making the moves
for lgd it's no longer easy no and
nobody wants to go mid right they have W
smile here just trying to slow down the
push just thr fire spirits on the wave
but the tower inevitably dropping very
soon Quinn very active a smoke moving
toward top new he shows himself yeah
sc's back up he's ready to look for
another
stack see if new able to play as well
the looks of it sort of avoided one
another you will be able to get around
from this one they'll hit him with the
scam but he's already back to the safety
of his side of the map so you nicely
avoiding that move there it's actually
both scans they used immediately both of
them trying to find him so he's able to
sneak himself away from that at the
least Ace will be able to clean up some
jungle is going down the blade Mail
Route pretty good blade mail game versus
this Luna versus the Phoenix across the
board and very early aggressive words
that we're seeing gaming already placing
down so they're going to have good
information when you're playing versus
something like Spirit breaker if he has
such a hard Lane you know he doesn't
want to return back mid when they get
these deep Wards down you're going to
see these charges coming through so
they're they're going to have a lot of
information to play off in these next
few moments me what do lgd do for the
next move they're going to try and go on
bottom but the global silence comes out
for he's ready to turn goes back in with
the ultimate straight onir the sight
there they've got the burst Quinn turns
up takes him
down as at this point of the game it
feels just so incredibly difficult for
lgd to make any sort of moves but at the
same time they don't want to sit back
and farm because on the other side of
the map there's an alchem is picking
things up I it's still a bold attempt to
go for this P he is very tanky 1400 HP
already they are quite lacking in the
damage early game's bottom Tower is
under attack quick rotation this Tower
going to get pressured massively here
they will be able to hold on to their
mid Tower at the least and get some
levels on the Phoenix but damage being
done here from gaming gladers early on
they're opening it up for Dao to get
good timing even though he's got four
deaths he's about to have his sacred
Relic already done it really seems like
it didn't matter catching up
massively lgd where they go
next and difficult for Luna as well too
if you do start struggling in this game
the Heroes that you have to run you down
there's a primal Beast there's this
necro who's going to be immensely tanky
and a Radiance that's going to come out
soon lgd need to start getting something
going in their favor got the get the top
t one but TPS are coming in from gaming
Gladiators see if they're able to catch
anything Quinn not quite able to get in
reach of new with the ink SW as L they
get the objective and they won't lose
anything for it I look where nothing to
say is being forced to try to find Farm
he's just on the outskirts try trying to
get anything it looks like it was
scouted out though I mean they were
pinging it yeah seler he seems to know
something's
up and that's sort of one way to to get
back in the game as a mid Spirit breaker
it's just not easy looking for kills
looking for action it's not lgd strong
point right now against the tools that
gaming Gladiators have managed to amass
no and overall too he's he's playing
into the Primal Beast which is a hero
that just doesn't even care about status
resist if he gets the grab onto the
again trouble trouble the Luci be just
in time to hold Ace back and he's able
to get out of the range of the ink swell
on by now under of the two supports
gaming Gladiators they continue to move
forward they've got the burst they dro
the side not quite enough damage to
burst pops the egg they can't quite take
it out queler they try to hit it but
they can't stop the Supernova it's a
Turn Around from lgd they're taking out
tofu they're taking out celery they'll
bring Quinn lowo can lgd get more out of
this both Ace and Quinn incredibly low
at the side of the fight Direct on the
retreat nothing to say charges in over
for WS Quinn who stop from you as well
they've got the they take down a for lgd
Strike Back hard beautiful connection
what an egg right in the middle of
everybody gaming tried to go for a very
early aggressive play here the reaper
doesn't do much damage at all oh they
needed that they needed that big time an
amazing fight there for lgd big Wombo
Combo team fight abilities connecting
perfectly
there we'll see the the move again you
know gaming Gladiators they walk right
into this I mean it looked like a solid
start going for Shir but between the
Stampede the they hold back at the loen
beam avoiding that initial attempt from
Ace they feel good at they get the soul
bind it's an early s but it's one that
you feel tempted to go for cuz they link
together but it's just a bit too soon
the burst isn't there and at this point
I think you got the fire Spirits out as
well the hon are new they just didn't
allow gaming Gladiators any chance to
take down this egg I honestly like
pretty beautiful spell casting coming
out across the board Planet even with
that little disruption buying time so
that they both don't get grabbed from
the Primal Beast they're going to try
and go again here gaming Gladiators this
time they might find Shiro they're in on
top of him zin's back up the grabs there
shirro won't survive this time around
gaming ladat is not to be deterred after
that the way that that last fight went
they went straight back here this time
they get the job done no hesitation they
know that they are pretty cool down Rel
line to be able to turn those fights
early game since they do have that
little bit of a lead they do have Global
as well too that last fight celery
didn't have it so hanging on to it for
the next upcoming fights to clean up
these ancients Radiance it is
finished
ranning seeing if Y is going to commit
for this here he has The Shard queued up
very early on this Phoenix I was
expecting to maybe see that Midas queued
up but we'll have to see which route he
wants to be able to go on this
Phoenix think to calm down a little bit
here from gaming Gladiators definitely
going to be a bit more careful about how
they make that next move yeah I think if
they're going to make that next move
they're likely to have the global in
particular hesitate a little bit more
with how far they go for the big
dive but lgd feeling more confident here
looking for Quinn as well too comes
out they will manage to walk this off so
not the worst of situations there for LG
they'll feel quite good about that one
baiting the global gives them a good few
minute or so to make that next play
without the threat of celer being able
to put a stop to their moov so a
successful bait of the ultimate from lgd
yeah good trade demonic Pur only has
like a 60sec cool down so that's going
to be coming up pretty soon again if
they want to make that aggressive move
on the Quinn it's always going to be a
pretty good kill threat just being able
to get make sure he can't ever get Ghost
round off get the focus fire so he can't
move but every minute that anything
slows down the G the gold Le just
massively goes for Gladiators in seconds
L they've got to try and abuse this
window the the global silence being
unavailable for gaming Gladiators can
they find Quinn can they pop
him Al at ready it's underneath this
Ward setup from gaming Gladiators not an
easy part for for lgd to strike into
whilst they lack the vision on The High
Ground Ace giving a lot of information
as well for gladiators their front line
is just so tanky here all three
effectively are pretty pretty tank in
the side of gaming Quinn almost has his
heart finished up
I was waiting to see if tofu is actually
queuing up his bit of a different route
of items he's actually going for the
ules I mean playing versus the spirit
breaker it's pretty common to see it but
I mean I think we've pretty much always
seen those Grims go for those Shard
right away just how effective it can
be but I guess maybe because of the
Shadow Demon he is hesitating for it a
little bit just cuz that demonic Purge
but we'll have to
seees going to have Quinn on the front
line she's going to get caught in the
com for nothing to say but he's still
got H to play they jump forward with the
S B there response Quin he's per with
the side down on the two of them takes
nothing to say out us to fall from the
curse damage of celery the egg
successful but there's no chance for lgd
to fight aggressively off the back of it
why is has to TP out of the fight I mean
your two tanky front liners just get
detonated right at the start of the
fight egg connects but doesn't really do
much of anything tower now looks like
gaming still want to go for even more
kills as well too Dao full
bkb now he feels pretty unkillable with
this bkb on The Alchemist now I mean
mostly magic damage on their draft early
game here for lgd this is just going to
make Dao pretty
invincible and yeah Quinn looks like he
does go for that Shard before finishing
up the heart so he's got a bit more
Mobility versus The Shadow Demon as well
and they are controlling a lot of this
map I mean they're denying a lot of farm
away from lgd from shirro in
particular I think the concern as well
for lgd is the fact that the the one
fight that they did have going in their
favor it was one that gaming Gladiators
handed to them they're still yet able to
find anything positive with regards to
starting the action themselves and
looking to make the initiation it just
hasn't happened from
lgd not easy into this draft versus
these bruisers versus these tanky tanky
cores and yeah the early bkb from Dao
it's going to cause some big issues how
who do they really want to focus fire
now at this point do you focus fire The
bkb Alchemist you probably have to go
for these supports cuz these front
liners are just going to pretty much
absorb everything that you throw at them
so Tower is under attack at the moment
no egg for 30 seconds
gaming that farm don't win he able to
dive away here while you smile but Ace
is closing in upon him he why you smile
no egg no dive at the ready there's no
chance for survival another
kill nothing to say he is very deep he's
going to be okay gets the charge off in
time before draa is able to find
himom to so still doing his best to pick
up what he can across the map and
continue to try and catch up to towards
getting that octarine done and still
going to take time though for him going
to take time and it's always still going
to be issues cuz he doesn't have ways to
really protect himself besides that this
big burst that comes out from Reaper the
grab that comes out from the Primal
Beast always going to be an issue for
this
breaker Dao on The Alchemist blink dag
around the corner next time round he
will be able to get that catch and they
will be able to get the double
connections constantly with the soul
bind of that as well
too some very very difficult fights
ahead here for
lgd Tower he's getting too tanky too
fast on the side of gaming Ace heart
soon on the menu for him too Quinn he's
got it finished even though they've got
this demonic Purge he's just too tanky
61 and three so far in this necro this
pick seems to be a bit too much for them
to deal with at the
moment tier two now starting to get
pressured can they mount the defense
here this is not an easy spot to
fight they have got the ultimates but at
the same time sod gaming Gladiators
unless someone in lgd is able to find
their way to the back lines find the
silence Cel is going to be able to put a
stop to any sort of Team fight that the
lgd try and respond with yeah not easy
for you to just like charge through or
anything like that either there's a
primal Beast there's a soul bind that's
always going to be stopping you and
gaming they're just playing as a unit so
far not giving the opportunities to lgd
Shir is getting some good time to get
that farm going he's got his Manta got
the mask of Madness but he needs more to
be able to actually show up to these
fights it feels like this is great for
farming but definitely needs a bkb this
game plan it okay I mean Dao a bit far
forward but has
bkb Dr the AL upon Him Ace flanking
tring to see if he get the grab on a y
smile but a quick dive is there just a
bit of a poke from the supports but
nothing more to push gaming Gladiators
back as they'll continue to push on and
look to take this tier two Dao knows his
strength having that s here behind him
too a tier two default very early pre2
minutes also able to hold on to the tier
two top they did have quite a few Heroes
up on this Top Lane lgd but unable to
push the tier two
themselves okay he always wants to play
Super aggressive he wants to go for the
SD they might be able to sandwich Planet
here I think they will Ace coming in
from the side Planet he can't run from
this one jump forward to the low ground
from Dao another kill and more gold here
for The
Alchemist just getting way too much on
the map Quinn shows himself top they
have a ward on top of them but there's
just no way for them to punish it they
do have okay the center's kind of in the
area but they yeah they can't go for
it getting very close the sort of timing
21 minutes or so in where they're going
to have to deal with these two cores
that have hearts upon them you know AC
is pretty much got his done Quinn's
already got his and a bkb Alchemist
that's a lot of HP that you got to try
and get through with the damage that
you've got an lgd's lineup and you just
s of look at the heroes and unless
everything connects perfectly it's hard
to sort of see these situations in which
these CA of gaming Gladiators get taken
down yeah can you protect your egg
you're going to need absolutely
everything to connect perfectly it feels
like for lgd in these next few moments
and for gaming the pace is going to
continue accelerating BR soon to be on
the menu for them too but continuing to
look to just control the map before
that full hyperstone now on
Daio
Tower Aline done now at least for
nothing to say so have the higher
frequency of weaving in and out of the
fights with these
charges can keep that farm going but
still feels like they need more and more
time which just still doesn't feel if
it's really really benefiting them the
gaming has just been consistently like 6
AK gold lead even though they're playing
versus this Midas I just sweeping the
map taking these towers down and lgd
they will not be showing up to defend
them oh they have this deep W already
placed down
too why has to be careful he gets any
closer to this High Ground I mean even
as he is going to get CAU daa just jumps
in under the tier two now they know that
word is there but they get a free kill
out of it and potentially even going to
get to pressure two lanes off of this
here with da on one and coin on the
other how does lgd slow this down I mean
they're just continue to try to get this
charge of course to clear these waves
but need more time for shirou to feel
ready to
fight yeah now bkb at the least a
necessity but still a couple of thousand
gold away from that and the necessity of
course it'll help protect him but his
damage is definitely starting to feel I
mean it's still F to feel pretty
lackluster even with that bkb they need
everything to connect perfectly they
need this egg the sun ra feels like is
going to be probably their highest
damage
potential for
gladiators Shan is at the ready if they
want to look for that one first they
almost have Agony also now finished up
on
Quinn and with those early boots of
travel that he was able to get to it's
always this way to answer something like
the spirit breaker right he goes to one
lane clears it out and then he can go
join his team constantly while they're
on the hunt for this SV but nothing to
say is doing a good job at least of
keeping these waves quite cleared out
and he's only died the three times so
he's getting some pretty decent
recovery buys his Shard so going to be
going for that plane in Pocket to absorb
some type of spells at least to protect
shirro not too often I think I've seen
people purchase
it has eyes on Quinn but of course
nothing really that he can do about this
another cool thing is I guess with the
planer pocket it's a magic resist too
75% magic resist if you eat that with a
Reaper sighte you're probably just going
to live through it so it's going to be a
cool itemization here from nothing to
say to tank spells for
shirro potentially trying to cuss with
the creep waves coming in on this Top
Lane but gaming glad they've already got
one right up to two yeah da I me he has
AC done he's just brood forcing these
towers the map shrinking more and
more shro with the Illusions trying to
at least hold back the waves in the mid
lane bkb is
finished definitely feels like moments
away from gaming Gladiators maybe trying
their look at a high ground push as I
say though Roshan is there so probably
going to they'll go for the pick up on
that one yeah it's going to shift up top
and about 40 seconds so I imagine
they're going to set up around there
that very much feels like that they're
in a position where they don't really
need to take too many risks right now
gaming Gladiators a prettyy comfortable
hold on the
game get the cat tofu in with the well
they don't even have to use the reaper Z
early they'll drop it now still won't
get the kill with it but they get the
kill after oh that was sick by tofu what
a quick blink and insta popping that ink
swell mid to 20 seconds till that Ro
starts shifting they're already
positioned around the Top
Lane Gaming's just kind of
cruising playing the map it feels like
wherever they want Even though lgd is
getting the farm they are completely
avoiding every anywhere that gaming
gladers does
Go lgd I mean in terms of items we'll
see sort of what pickups they are able
to get in place before this kind of Ram
pickup into High Ground push that's very
likely to be coming in from gaming
Gladiators does occur with the bkb it's
there he's got the money for The Shard
if he wants to pick that up anything to
sort of provide him some defensive
capabilities trying to get that small
crit online as well Shar just to have
some sort of damage against this
inevitable p push that gaming Gladiators
is going to come charging them with and
that feels it's going to be the big
issue is will they have enough damage to
go through ACE the heart Primal Beast
The Alchemist who's incredibly tanking
and this
necros and now on Aegis as well too
which they cannot contest up
here the levels as well too on the
supports I mean that's something I'm
always going to be looking at for the
Phoenix it does feel like he's going to
be one of the most important ones for
the side of lgd still not level
12 so with this pace of this game he's
not able to find the connection to get
those extra levels from
as this Rush it's
gone should be able to finish the tier
one
mid get an extra bit of a cash bonus
here for the
team any little bit they can get they
need lgd have to be very careful with
their position outside of the base right
now are in a spot that gaming Gladiators
are starting to close in upon illusion
The High Ground surely going to be the
best place for lgd to try and make their
stand here against gaming Gladiators gam
even wants to go for that High Ground
too we'll have to wait how long they
want to push the issue forward
here shirro does find an illusion Rune
probably one of the better ones that he
get in this type of Style game where
things have slowed down massively
cutting some waves does get that top
wave cut out
there so this is the final wave that
gaming has if they don't do want to go
threaten that high ground level 18 has
been hit on Daio see if he does threaten
a little bit here he wants
to he knows it's so hard for lgd to
punish any sort of jump that he wants to
go for on this push yeah he can just
start getting the pke Quinn going to
start throwing those heals out as well
too this Tower is dropping there's no
GPH 13 seconds got to do something gdf
wise they're going to be losing a raack
that was perfect timing really for
gaming to take advantage of that glyph
still being
down to clear out the Illusions and the
ax is gone they the range they're onto
the melee
now GD what's the
plan fire Spirits for now seem to be
enough to stop the the push here from
gaming Gladiators Lan cut so Luna does
get both of those so no more creep wave
up in the Top Lane so will buy them some
time a nice move from shirro nothing to
say considering a charge but doesn't
want to start a fight just yet into this
Aegis nice play from Shiro yeah a little
illusion micro definitely making a big
deal there level 18 now and he does have
that small crit finish so now maybe this
is that indicator for lgd this could be
the call where they feel like they're
going to start having some d Dage to
look for the fight bkb also finished on
new so he can actually get into those
fights and not have to worry about just
getting instantly globaled and get
nothing
off Tower there a double damage as well
on the top side of the river would be
quite the pickup if lgd are able to
catch wind of that one gaming they're
going to continue The
Siege
bkb on Quinn he's also ready to go fully
in on the push
Dao onto the barracks how they may just
have to let this set go but looks of it
this they don't try anything on the
defensive on this one so a full set of
Rex will be taken down by Gladiators
yeah still too still two and a half
minutes left with this AIS to
potentially push for more they are going
to have to head back and deal with the
state of the the rest of the creep waves
as they have been you say consistently
pushed in shirou really pulling off the
work here to keep this game
alive charge
through my
goodness very deep positioning here
playing around his vision though does
have that Ward on The High Ground and
nothing to say should be
fine Gladiators they send drao down
bottom to zal with the creep wave on
that lane the rest of the team ready to
start pushing back out the mid I they're
doing kind of the cool Maneuvers though
where it's yeah the objectives are being
taken from gaming but look at the Gold
you know it's starting to get a little
bit better there for lgd with the way
that you're just playing the full farm
game around the map rather than
contesting the push maybe feeling strong
enough to set up for something
themselves here lgd smoke up we have sh
feeling that they're now at a point
where they can try for for for looking
for a team
fight Dao on the front lines though the
DD still in the Top
Lane I mean ideally who who you finding
here do you do you want something like
the quick squishy Heroes you want to get
on the silencer first take him out you
know what would be the ideal catch for
lgd you probably at least want to know
where the silencer is and someone has to
stop the global to come out but we'll
see who they want to jump first they've
got eyes on the two of them those
interrupt the initial attempt from you
the global silence comes out the
Supernova is there but gaming gladi
they can fight this out keep to the
distance Ace will get caught by initial
St but he
SOB the grab as well drer picks up the
double shro he's got the bkb in the
eclipse Ace he's someh still alive
finally he'll fall as nothing to say
takes him out with the ultimate C able
to bkb TP out so lgd at least able to
cut their losses there and they do find
a kill in return in that fight nothing
to say only just able to catch a
underneath the tower so something to be
found but still not quite what GD were
hoping for and look how much they have
to commit just to kill Ace and he
actually had the bkb coming out on The
Courier so it's good that they got the
jump right there otherwise he absolutely
just lives and now down the mid they go
gacho St has 30 seconds with this AIS
Quinn backing him up they used
absolutely everything there on the side
of lgd no bkb at ready for Shiro him
walking up he could just get exploded
instantly if he
does yeah not a not a great fight of
course for lgd but it definitely could
have gone a lot worse if they lost their
lunar in that
situation it would have been rough
nothing to say trying to clear out the
way put a stop push there in with the
sub a lot of damage Rao's down
once has got his bkb ready here for the
second round he's got the blink as well
he's going to be out nothing to say
though he charges forward inst gets
clipped by the Phantoms Embrace from
tofu they tell him with a slow jump
forward again they're trying to control
the spirit breaker they'll throw out the
dust Another slow not going to connect
so Ace trying to close in but the
charges back up nothing to say able to
put a stop to the push and get
away we'll live to see another day to
we'll be
okay and they're looking to keep going
how long on this egg 20
seconds full butterfly now for sh I mean
Shir he he's he's silently slowly he's
he's doing it you know the Farm is
there they keep him alive bkb is back up
can they protect
him P just continue to commence LIF
still cool down for about 4 minutes who
goes in first if for lgd got to be new
and look at Dao the whole time he's been
doing this turning that Radiance off
consistently when he's going for the in
the bkb's off just in time there for
sure is still going to get C by the sine
he tried to turn it with the lips Ace is
falling low focus on able to take down a
back up the running away the bkb but the
physical damage is coming in drao
finally able to keep to his distance
quck gets back in on the
mid he's able to finish off Shiro Quinn
taking down the Luna shirro out with no
buyback available he's spent up for the
butterfly see
the disrupt but they're not going to be
able to find anything more that I mean
it look a solid defense from lgd but the
fact that Quinn he knew that he could
get straight back in there finish off
the Luna it's a big kill to be found
because if Shir survives through that
lgd they definitely be looking to make a
play Within this next minute with shirro
going down there because of that play
from Quinn LG they'll have to hold back
once more look how much damage shirro
was able to do I Ace pop bkb and just
literally died in seconds I think he had
even had like the vindicator's a bonus
armor he literally died so fast trying
to get the double grab but Quinn that
was a really cool call to make like you
see Dao drops to what I think it was
like 100 HP or something like that Quinn
just jumps into four or five Heroes and
ends up just getting away because of it
yeah the these players really knowing
their limits we sort of saw it yesterday
rightor and his morph wait for me into
these crazy situations this game is
Quinn just going right into the midst of
pretty much what four Heroes take to
take down that crucial kill and keep
this game for now held in gaming
Gladiators favor definitely seeing
though that shirro if they do if they
don't kill if they don't give him the
respect he is going to be doing a lot of
damage now at this point with this
butterfly keeping this game alive here
lgd it's consistently just been sitting
at that 6K gold
lead and high ground it's always going
to be the best place for them to get
this defense it's always going to allow
W smile to have kind of like perfect
positioning with his egg and sunr
they're looking to actually make an
aggressive move themselves they're
feeling confident perhaps after that
last fight it was very close to them
just wiping you know pretty much
everybody there on the side of gaming so
don't blame them if they feel quite a
bit more confident now might see a smoke
from gaming Gladiators themselves as
well yeah celeries ready to pop it on
smoke maybe reading the movements I mean
RIT soon going to be coming
up new pick up as well for nothing to
say has his Lincoln so not easy as as it
before to sort of set up from any of
these single Target disruptions or plays
from gaming Gladiators Ro it's a long
spawn Ace smoke to spell both teams
aware of one another
Tacho looks like he's potentially
setting up for something here they see
up around this top Rune he's actually
going to go for nothing to say bulldo
and Lincoln will eat it be
okay
Tower L GD time being bot chiro getting
bigger and bigger getting these buff UPS
too I saw the solo Crest picked up
before that last fight as well too from
Wu smile they're starting to throw their
eggs into this Luna basket
Ro one and a half GD getting more and
more time I think they'll want to try
and contest this Roan though yes they
certainly feel a whole lot stronger
right now GD yeah especially I mean with
the Lincoln in particular for nothing to
say now he's going to be able to just
straight charge through these fights and
perhaps just eat one of these big spells
or two especially with planer pocket too
right could just tank it off one of his
teammates gaming going to play patient
around here but that does potentially
mean that this map is going to get
farmed out from nothing to say from
Shiro satanic soon on the horizon for
shirro gladiators they want to try and
look for the hit before the RO
spawns can they get an angle they highly
suspect that lgd will start to to set up
outside of the base they send themselves
but The High Ground here who are they
with the jump upon drao goes towards the
creeps not going to find anyone there
though so they're in towards the
triangle
lgd that was close to disaster
Lanes just being shoved in though look
at bottom and mid nothing to say has
completely pushed those into the tier
twos now at this
point new and
gu able to get
away 15 seconds Ro they know it's got to
be up soon gaming just continue to play
in that corner area lgd's got to get
over
here SM up from the Z this time full
satanic done on Shar check this illusion
push in mid Quin he's actually got to go
answer it a little here double catapult
wave with these double
Illusions and lgd smoked up they saw
Quinn move this could be their
opportunity to strike 28 seconds no TP
for Quinn to join his team Tower getting
all these little lmes the fact that
they've now got oh at position two Lotus
ORS ready for the next fight shirro my
goodness look at new he knows he
knows perfect to the side they eliminate
toy they take down Gario they'll be able
to bring down celer as well as gaming
Gladiator tra in the corner they didn't
quite have the detection for CIO Ys
himself up but there's no Escape for
this silencer so sick I mean just
trapped in the corner the Gladiators
they were not ready for lgd to come and
pins them in and now open up the
opportunity for lgd to head into the pit
and get roam for themselves it's the big
brain split push plays that were coming
out spare breaker cutting bottom Luna
cutting mid eventually someone reacts as
soon as they see Quinn no hesitation
they know exactly where they were the
way that they've held on in this game
kept their call now they striking back
and they're striking back hard
Gladiators are going to be shaken in
their boots a little bit with the way
that these last few fights have gone
these moves absolutely huge for lgd as
lgd now starting to take the lead in
this game I mean Shiro is pretty much
completely neck and neck with that
Alchemist now and an
ages really feels like some of the best
Luna performance we've seen really
honestly with how Shiro's done in terms
of finding the farm keeping the game
alive with his sort of the map movements
of himself and the Illusions he's been
doing so much I mean him had nothing to
say even though you don't
it's like this invisible kind of impact
from this Spirit breaker but the amount
of space that he's been able to make
just clearing creep waves with this
charge he gotten them completely back
into it and now they're potentially the
ones going for this High absolutely I
mean now for gaming Gladiators now that
they're playing from behind how does
this change things up for them what sort
of conversations you think is going on
right now in the Gladiators boost good
question they're probably still feeling
pretty confident with their fight but
they're definitely feeling a little bit
more scared of this Luna they probably
need to start figuring out the answer
for nothing to say cuz he's just getting
way too big on this SP breaker now too
in the bottle got everything ready she
very close by, gold away from being a to
pick up the full L as well this Luna an
absolute Terror in these team
fights I mean w smile is also queuing up
for the big play he's going for that
refresher feeling they do not have an
answer for the egg if they don't get the
global off he's going to get these eggs
off every single
time
ooh see with Shiro we'll see what Shir
does does go down this route
changing item builds a little bit but he
is just going to go
dataless btom Tower ATT gladi do they
want to try and fight into the ages
three and a half minutes here for
shirro they don't have the same way to
be able to push these waves and visibly
right like now it's difficult for them
to actually keep their Lanes pushed out
they don't have these illusion pushes
they don't have the spirit breaker kind
of charge thing to be able to deal with
it so they kind of have to stick as this
unit now on gaming Gladiators for the
next probably for these next like 2
three minutes
lgd patiently waiting be able to find
the demon Edge a big kill they do
they'll be able to stop a bit of that
damage being buil up by Dao Shir he's
ready to start pushing it I mean this
building dies quick versus the DD forces
out the fortification now it's
gladiator's turn to try and do something
on the defensive we'll see if they're
able to put a stop to this one I mean as
soon as that Tower drops these racks are
going to drop in seconds trying and get
the jump on his sh of the man part A has
to back away nothing to say him with the
charge but gets push backo trying go the
Ki but it's on to the illusion shirro
put the bkb starting to get a bit low
himself doesn't feel confident even
though he has the ages to finish off the
racks he'll back off for now dless now
picked up that was pretty cool from Dao
actually doesn't have to use his bkb
doesn't he's scared about the reflection
of the concoction actually forces shirro
to use his they'll back away I they've
got so many ways as well to to sort of
buff up and protect Shir on the pushes
right with the Lotus picked up by new
the Lotus picked up by Planet so many
things to just throw upon this Luna and
just allow Shir to get in and do the
damage lgd they may have been pushed
back but I'm pretty sure they we looking
to go again still two minutes to play
aggressive with the agis yeah some nice
itemization I mean playing into the
silencer playing into necro even even
Grim struck Ian this this Lotus could be
incredibly
effective gaming now bit trapped inside
their own
base Dao they're going to get the jump
on him open things up they'll drop the
global but the super over time with the
r it burst through Dao he's for 75 new
OG seal toing forward they're pushing in
on the mid lane they'll be ready to
approach The High Ground again and maybe
even Force out this P back from Dao he's
out for
70 Quinn now Quinn also HS a Lo and beam
charging from nothing to say knocks it
back as well the the bkb is out qu backs
away the turn of the sine jump forward
Dr Tri to get the ab BL St but it's on
the L stuns himself Ace in the mid to
the mdle the s's coming it takes nothing
to say down there's a he's getting
completely trampled upon by
Ace can they do it a second time round
bkb is still on C out for 2 seconds he's
going to have it up now he's ready to
press he ready to turn looks toward with
a Lo be but he crashing across the two
of them sh he's ding the the BB com to
get sh able to TP out as he as game you
will not as Gladiators they'll find you
but they won't get anything else no I
don't know how but be able to live there
despite his bkb coming to an end I mean
both s the things around that the fact
that his bkb came back up just in time
from be able to survive that initial
burst from Gladiators and then even
though it was a short one he still he's
able a TP away both teams expending a
buyback directo with a buyback for
gladiators nothing to say with a buyback
from from lgd Quin is still a definite
problem for them though I'm seeing him
in these fights just absolutely wrecking
everybody he gets ignored for a second
and like I watch Z pops a tanic and turn
to try to hit I'm just watching his
health actually going down anyway so
does still have to be
careful still showing that it's
anybody's game these though going to be
very crucial Dao having to his use last
having H use his for the defense there
and then also now Spirit Break nothing
to say he used his to try to join that
pre afterwards he got worried he got the
bkb purchased as well now ready for the
next fight so a new bkb on him close to
25 as well on nothing to say mkb now
finally done with the Cur coming back up
D is able to pick up his demon Edge big
it hex for Quinn they have two different
ways now to be able to go for these big
plays to go for this big double plays as
well too with the grimstroke more and
more ways to break this Lincoln more and
more ways to go for nothing to say
tofa with his Agony of course finished
up all now another element that lgd does
have to answer this this Luna illusion
is going to be terrifying oh it is we've
seen many many times how much this dark
portrait can do against the right carry
and against this shirro lunar is
certainly the one to to get a dark
portrait upon if they have these
butterfly but to have on these dark
portraits sh trying to close in the sign
to get the he as well but he will loow
just back over towards Quin with is a
three man who stop the charge a
beautiful jump from you gaming
Gladiators they have to run bkb for Dro
is on the retreat another Char for for
nothing over towards Ace Quinn getting
completely kite this lgd back off away
from him during his
bkb again Cates there whoop into the
charge do they have the damage to
threaten Quinn the buback going to be
coming out from to turn back over
they've got
the the side K but he's still going to
be kep the ground they finish him off sh
out of the game the T what nothing to
say nothing to say he has no bu back he
canot afford to get CAU and he won't
charges over towards the mid they back
up can he get away T over look like they
have the detection here on the front
line so nothing to say he'll live a big
escape from him if he goes down he's
down for 2 minutes I mean massive stun
from new but still the issue is Quinn
he's zoning four Heroes away while
protecting his allies and they find the
big one they take shirro out buyback is
available for him we'll see how much
they're able to take here gaming
Gladiators before the BuyBacks come out
from lgd as drao in on the mid lane tier
three are gone onto the back STS to buy
back gaming Gladiators they respect it
immediately they got out big there on
the side of gaming forcing these
BuyBacks Ro 50 seconds till coming back
up how do they come wi actually like
he's really just zoning four or five
Heroes away constantly even though his
Alchemist is getting burst in a lot of
these situations quinnn he is a standing
on 91 and six so far in this necro sort
of offend wi in terms of the items we're
seeing lgd just feeling that they have
to lean towards the defensive you is
queing up himself a Lincoln SPH for the
next item this really doesn't want to
get caught or suffer the threat of being
just jumped upon by this instant hex
catch from Quinn hey lotuses and Lincoln
definely are the dream versus these
single Target abilities but I don't know
I'm seeing him switching a lot okay now
he's got the r up I saw him do this
before we get that one maybe he feels
like he does need it just be able to
bring down this necro cuz their overall
damage it's not fast enough to kill him
it seems like he's getting this regen
just to build up constantly and yeah
just the overall damage he does in these
team
fights NE and still 6K lead back up for
gaming a lot of BuyBacks of course use
the most important thing here lgd used
quite a bit there they did the big one
Shiro and nothing to
say but it's time for their of course
over on the side of game Gladiators Duro
still on the three minute cool down
himself absolutely 2 minutes or so until
we see rosam back in the game ninja gear
picked up for Dao 25 also has been
attained could make the difference as
well those last few jumps of Dao they
have been kind of caught out by the lot
they're able to get out this time maybe
making the jump from the ninja gear
smoke up could allow him to get in with
that opening Abyssal blade before lgd
can react this could also be a big
difference maker in the fight s now has
the refresher we' seeing some fantastic
eggs and sunrays come out from him he
can now have that double of course and
he's level 18 y there that big
one his Mana pool is quite lackluster
though I think he's lost a bit of he's
at 699 Mana so pretty much has to just
refresh her an egg has to be a little
bit careful about that secondary gaming
Gladiator is ready for this oneart they
smoked up
new charge coming in trying to get some
information nothing to say get some
Vision here for maybe New to follow up
with a potential h on the Illusions
they're pressuring in on the mid line as
well gaming Gladiators they might have
to do something about this it's going to
be a fair bit of damage done potentially
with these creep WS pushing in I don't
think they want to go back though last
time the Quinn went
back his Barracks are taking quite the
hit in the mid lanane likely to fall I
mean these these losing yeah they have
to put the fortification at least there
and Quinn is walking back okay so he's
trying to save his TP to be able to join
his team but yeah the racks at least the
range racks might just fall down they
finish it off Ro 30 seconds this sort of
the slightly longer respawn so
definitely working in favor of gaming
Gladiator is allowing them time to get
back and hold the base and maybe get
back over towards the pit if they do
want to try and contest lgd in this
position do they have a I don't think
they have a smoke left on the side of
gaming though they have a couple ninja
gears I don't see a smoke on them to
make it their way back up there they're
going to go as a
unit I mean do you think you have to
still try and force this fight or do you
now what's the call here from Gladiators
this could be a difficult fight to take
they probably still want to fight cuz
they feel maybe like they have like some
of this number Advantage with Quinn
having this
buyback got to make the call quick
though cuz this Roa dies in oh he going
to be going down quickly there's the
smoke delivered out gaming Gladiators
they'll start to head towards the pit
but they've got to do it fast look at
the positioning from nothing to say be
able toing break the smoke he's in on
The High Ground it's going to be hard
for gladiators to get past him Shir
getting the space to finish off a to get
the grab they turn straight away the
side comes down nothing say he's able to
put the bkb jump for fromation nothing
to say he's able to live for that he's
on the egg with the chemical to take Tak
the over turn over put
the with the T gets the AG on tries to
stand his ground against him but he's
caught by the disruption they're on to
the Luna the Luna's out the watch he's
not got a lot of buyback this second
life here for cherro could a rough one
he's able to get out of this one G he's
big up the rap here he's not able to get
out he tries to put the refresher but
he's he's he's out and he just SP up his
buyback of course still on cool down he
is out of the game for two minutes a
huge window now for gaming Gladiator to
try and end this one they had the bodies
Dao solo killed the egg he just full
commits onto it no Shiro here that's got
to be it I mean they can just push the
the two most important heroes are G
nothing to say we'll be back in 20
seconds 20 seconds and buyback will be
there for the spirit breaker but no Luna
for the defense they at least have one
of the extra eggs still up with that
buyback from the Phoenix since he did
just die on the first go gaming just
throw bodies in and
Quinn I mean can they hold it's not easy
without shirro he's all the
damage they're going for the magas
they're playing it safe here just in
case nothing to say the buyback
available
there will be a 4v5 at the least here
for the
defense the r gone building dropping
Spirit breaker buyback but still 60
seconds no shirou
lgd nothing to say trying to start off
the defense jump foring you in with the
straight away onwards Dao Dao stepping
away's able to put the bkb off for
nothing to say bashing in on towards H
bring it h down low the super NOA pop
successfully but the building second
round taken the base exposed they've got
to do something crazy here lgd if they
want to hold Dao being careful 10
seconds for chemical range he's letting
Quinn just hit the throne they're doing
it safely they're doing it carefully
here gaming Gladiators another charge
for for nothing to say trying his best
to tank the Spells load to throw out
upon Him reflectly AOL blade from Dao
celer trying to hit onto the ancient
himself 20 seconds they've got the
fortification lgd doing their best
Holding Out for a Shero here but he may
not respawn today as he's dead for 15
more seconds
the ancient 10 seconds until the Lun is
up nothing to say tried it but it stop
to it all he's with the H stop he's got
the two of them he gets the jump the bur
over buto he's dead K him it doesn't
matter the ace finishes off the Agent P
is called gaming Gladiators will take
this game one I what a team fight up top
beautiful stuff from gaming Gladiator
just having the confidence to just walk
in there and take out nothing to say I
mean throwing everything onto him he
feels so tanky he's got bulldo he's got
all this capabilities to try to protect
himself but they still burst him through
it and somehow Dao solo kills the egg
when it means everything wow I'm been in
an insane final push and a close push as
well you know if there was sort of
anything like a 10c less on that cool
down of the the buyback of Shir if he
was able to turn up for that defense
maybe they could have held but as it was
Gladiators realizing that they had this
window to go all in to end the game
before Sher was able to do anything with
the rap here pickup I mean look at these
damage numbers in particular Quinn doing
about 60 th damage this game the next
highest on his team daa with like 27
Shiro also of course carrying heavily
inside that later stage is 52k damage
but overall gaming this necro pick
seemed to be pretty perfect for Quinn to
take over I think it certainly did
either way an insane opening here to
this final day of the international both
teams absolutely playing their hearts
out but as it is gaming Gladiators they
will close up and take this game
one a phenomenal showing for this first
game I really thought lgd had that
middle part of the game that they were
going to be able to close it down that
lunar illusion taking a lot of doing a
lot of damage to the racks but
ultimately that third Ro fight was the
game changer Gunner yeah and it looked
like they had it for a second the Luna
Shard just was doing so much damage but
I think nothing to say dying at the
start of the fight really hurt them he
wasn't able to protect the egg which is
really important for kind of their
success also uh there was an
uncharacteristic mistake I think from
Gaming With The High Ground push I was
really surprised surprised cuz they're
probably the best team at this early
game High Ground siage they know when to
do it they know how to do it without
dying but in this game after they had
this really nice early game lead they
kind of threw it away a little yeah they
didn't have the best Lanes this game but
they they managed to come strong but uh
like I want to talk about like how they
manag to take that mid game lead with
the rotations of the supports because
they play so well with the ccnc that
they managed to like make an even game
to look like insanely one-sided right
and they were pushing for a long time
they were pressuring them of course they
few s sleep UPS on The High Ground but I
mean the fights the fights around this
Rush pits like they were they were
deciding and I think on the last fight
lgd had had an opportunity to jump them
first when they saw them on the on the
board but they decided to go for The
Rush pit instead and like it was like
very um the last position there in my
opinion having a look at some of the
reactions there from not only the
players but also their supporting
members too uh this game wasn't clean At
All by any means for G like we've
already pointed out The High Ground
issues that they had but what exactly
were lgd able to do sheep to be able to
capitalize on those poor High Ground
pushes and make it so difficult for G I
think it was more than just The High
Ground pushes but just like a little bit
of sloppiness and lack of discipline
from G in general like for example when
they smoked into the triangle to try and
uh disrupt Luna get a kill there the
fact that they overcommitted and dived
and threw away the lives of four Heroes
when they had like it was close to like
5 or 6K leads so early on like that was
kind of where they could Stomp and end
the game and instead they kind of of
threw it away and I think that was like
a massive moment for them um otherwise
like I think they did a really good job
getting to that place in the in the
first place the fact that this fast
boots of travel on necro allow them to
be everywhere on the map I think Ace
usually he plays incredibly greedy but
this game he was way more sacrificial he
was way lower on the net worth he was
super hyperactive with his supports
playing around making moves I also want
to talk about item builds because when
you're playing against lineup like this
on the gamings like they have three
Heroes that build like you know two
Heroes have hard s Alchemist is insane
in HP region and on the side of lgd they
didn't have like they didn't have shivas
did you guys see that he went to go for
the fist pump on Quinn and Quinn just
stood up and walked away oh that
happened to me many times it's all right
still there's a game too he's got to get
back in the zone but yeah the item
builds like you need to have shivas you
need to have vessel against a lineup
like this and if you don't have then
we've seen so many fights when they
start and like the fight look good in
the beginning but then they go out the
region and then they go back and this is
like how they lost many fights I was a
little bit worried about the AL we've
just seen him be quite tumultuous
throughout this event he's had some
really good showing some really rough
ones and that mid game was where I
worried about if the Doro Al was going
to be able to carry it obviously we see
it it was able to in this way but what
else about the AL meant that that late
game was kind of difficult that he
wasn't really hitting the the timings
who couldn't be together as much with
gaming
Gladiators uh the biggest thing with Al
is you generally want this really fast
early game timing which is always what
gaming goes for so I think the AL looked
really good up until The High Ground
push and then after that it kind of just
ended up being a little scary cuz he'll
get outscaled by the lunar really
quickly and I think they threw their
gold lead up to around only four or 5K
gold and when you have an Al it's always
just fake so it started to look a little
scary but I think just the power of
necros in this draft was it kind of
showed also Primal Beast with like they
have double Hearts I think heart there
was none on lgd if I'm not mistaken
maybe the center had one but I just
think that having more Health than the
other guys just matter so much right now
it's all about being tanky we're going
to see some uh more breakdowns of this
game number one purge has all the
information thank you Nat yeah being
tanky is very important but how you get
there is by collecting gold and
experience and the way the gaming
Gladiators do it is so so fast compared
to other teams and a lot of this comes
with pressure on the map Quinn here 8
minutes into the game they just got a
kill on the spear prer he's constantly
Crossing into the enemy part of the map
and the you already have an observer W
in this of the Jungle so what he does is
puts himself in an offensive position
but also is stealing Stacks that enemies
made that means he's basically getting
himself more gold while wasting their
time with this move and this
continuously happened the first 15
minutes of the game here's the obvious
Shadow Demon stacking two camps in this
area he kills the watch run which gives
him vision and they come over and kill
him they were just ignoring tier one
Tower the vast majority of this game
which is not normal instead saying we're
ganking and clearing Stacks easily using
necros who's tanky and has tons of AOE
damage very able to do this uh at this
stage of game now the invade fail that
happened at the toin Mark was a little
bad for them this AOE here this ink
swell around the Primal Beast if Luna
gets within this range she gets stunned
and probably comboed she interrupts the
first stun Stampy keeps are slightly
outside of that range and that's why
they were able to disengage and win that
huge fight against gladiators but what
did they do immediately after they
respawned they went back to the same
spot they do not want to let them clear
these Stacks easily they want to get
kills they want to accelerate to Gold
advantage and this all helps them
accelerate their timing so they win this
fight and Dao rotates over with his
Radiance to clear this ancient stack
taking away from uh Luna and all of this
acceleration that they work for hits him
with this crazy timing at 16 minutes bkb
finished on Alchemist the whole team is
already set up to prep this fight and it
ends up going well for gaming Gladiators
this is why they're able to Rack so
early cuz they're invading constantly in
slightly abnormal ways and winning great
fights it was a very very close game
though it was a really close one that
early game we've already said it many
times you said it Reser lgd sometimes
struggle with the laning face gaming
Gladiators they love the tempo they love
to be aggressive for themselves everyone
in this Arena they loved the game one
and it's nice to know that we still have
at least one more game in this best of
three to be able to see some more action
just like that but it's not only people
in this Arena that are enjoying ti2
there are locations all across the world
right now that are enjoying the action
that is taking place here so game
Gladiator fans lgd fans they spend all
the way across the world not just here
guys yeah and the game is amazing like
you know you you you you expect this
game to be like over soon because of the
high lead of the gaming g they they had
but at the same time like it's just like
very back and forth in those team fights
like they very little gimmicks that
decide that who's going to win the game
you know it's it's not clear until the
very end yeah we talked a lot about how
gaming maybe made a mistake on The High
Ground push but I think lgd the way they
played the mid game from behind was
really commendable they actually came
back into the game at some points they
had a Rapier timing on this Aegis and it
was just unfortunate that the contest on
the RO fight didn't work out cuz he
ended the game with a Rapier in his
inventory he was just dead for 2 minutes
so he couldn't use it and so in the next
game I'm probably looking for their
Lanes to go slightly better in the draft
I think maybe the necro ban is probably
something they should look towards cuz
it seems like the hero pool they won for
nothing to say is not really going to
work out versus Quinn at least if he
gets the necro um but overall I think
the way that they're playing is honestly
pretty stable versus gaming Gladiators
if they can kind of fix some of the big
major mistakes in the draft I think
they'll be kind of set for the next game
all right well let's see where the crowd
is sitting if they gaming Gladiator fans
if they're lgd fans if they're hoping
for a two if they're hoping for three
games so let's see slack uh where where
are you where are you hello I am here
with the lgd fans lgd fans this is the
darkest that it has looked they are down
a game and they need us now more than
ever gentlemen ladies it is time please
get your dogs
out Team Hot let's go with lgd
LG
LG L excuse you excuse you what we
vegans will not be ignored get out your
celery
okay a little less vient with the celery
we've also been talking in honor of our
vegetarian game and Gladiators the
celery dance are you ready celery
dance celery dance what the hell is that
no no we will not let these calorie
deficient vegetarians meet us we are
preserved we are the hot dogs LG hot dog
one more time lgd
l
[Applause]
g okay I'm Ching on the hot dog okay
thank you very much take it back to
me oh God no get get him away from slack
get away from slack i s we might have to
give him the high look there he said
he's Ching on the hot dog uh but that is
a a great bit we love to heit the chance
celery Team Hot Dog where are you guys
going for for game number two do you
believe in the comeback from lgd that
they're going to face team spirit again
in the grand finals who whoa whoa we're
not biased panelists we are very okay I
very biased like even like if they
manage to win this game like with this
you know back and forth you know
happening in the game for gam I don't
think like the next game is going to
look any different like if if they get
their lineup with the you know pushes
and like how they can take down the
towers early on even earlier than this
game I think it's going to be like super
easy super one-sided okay you guys might
not be uh biased but maybe I can win you
over because we do have a listen in we
have inside the pods for game in the
Gladiators during that game
one but it doesn't matter I think we
just want to fight this Ro I don't
need this objectives just want a
straight fight head to
hit did did convince you they just want
to fight yeah very calm yeah want they
they calm and all they want to do is
just uh take fights they don't care
about objectives they don't care about
buildings or Ro or anything like that
just make sure you're killing the enemy
Heroes just kill them twice yeah I mean
I'm biased for a game three so okay so
you I have to ref for lgd this game just
for a game three cuz I think you know
more games today the marrier yeah for
sure it's it's our final day so we want
to see everything go the distance I
completely agree it's also like the
level of DOTA now is just like so
unbelievably High when it gets really
close like when we see these 78 minute
game we're getting all the tier five
items out that's the hype that's the
stuff I want to see today I want to go
the distance you wanted to go the
distance you 17 plus of minute games you
want three games in this best of three
well game two it's still a little bit
away but we can talk about some change
ups that necro is a focus that you guys
talked about but then I wonder what
you're willing to let through are you
willing to let through a bristle A
Dazzle the Chen the ench on the side of
lgd for gaming Gladiators to pick up I
think it's hard to make an argument for
Chen or en just because they both fill
the same role so if you ban one it's
kind of forced to ban both otherwise
there's no point so it ends up being
they have to choose between Dazzle or
bristle if they want to ban the necro
and I think gaming has shown for both
Heroes that it's really really scary to
deal with and I think as as of now
Bristol probably has people are more
used to playing vers it than the Dazzle
especially because Dazzle is a flex hero
it goes mid it goes off lane for gaming
but the Bristol's kind of always off
Lane so you'll know you go in the draft
knowing what's going to happen and you
kind of at least can have a plan walking
into it I imagine this time lgd will
have first pick as well since this game
to which gives them the advantage cuz
last game obviously the necro came out
at the end of second phase where they
got to just like counter their Lane and
have a really good moment for the necro
so they shouldn't have that this time so
I'm not sure if they need to like ban it
I mean if anything they could change the
life steer band to necro band right in
the second phase I think it's important
but I do think that that there's two
topics that they need to like discuss
within the team first is like how to
prevent those rotations from supports
and like protecting your mid lane
because this is where you know gaming
lad is start to pressure and your super
hard and the second thing is about item
builds if you're playing against lineup
that has a lot of region like you need
to have vessel you need to have shivas
you need to have some way to deal with
it look G I'm going to ask a question
you can tell me no you don't have to
answer but you were in this position you
were on the main stage and you were
facing up against gaming Gladiators you
guys lost game one what was that 15
minutes for you spent like to look
towards game two what was your focus and
what did you just kind of have to push
to the side and ignore it was a lot
about we talked a lot about the Chen
which is kind of the guys that to try to
end the game really fast and we need to
find a way to deal with it and we didn't
find the solution in time and so it's
time to see if lgd can find the solution
in time all right well the players are
walking out now they're going to be
taking the stage maybe for the last time
for lgd maybe there's going to be a
little bit more in it we don't really
know but we do want to know more about
lgd you just put carrye mag and throw
Len M or what 10 seconds remaining have
to see here I do know for a fact that
we've seen some interesting heroes from
shirou well they're going to put the
skyth wait are they going to put the
skyth mid I I believe that's I think
that's Kota Willow it's Willow
did Willow
wow carry dark Willow yeah what in God's
Grand earthart is
this this is why LG has so many fans
because every time you think you've got
this team figured out on how they want
to play they just bust out the wildest
[Music]
St can they find him yes the curse crown
with that Shard activating is trip kill
for
[Music]
SHP is the ancient wa for Ramy is going
to get hex right off the bat there's the
ancient seal Apollo the ggs are called
the ancient gets destroyed for
[Music]
lgd
gaming versus game in
Gladiators game
two G Gladiator game two of our lower
bracket finals we just heard it there
from why Innovation is a confidence this
team they've been known for those wild
drafts they were the first ones to do
dark Willow on the main stage we saw it
last weekend this could be the do or die
this is where the Innovation is really
going to come in clutch for them how far
do you push the envelope to make it to
the Grand finals to make a comeback in
this low bracket to me it's definitely
it was their best draft with dark Willow
and BR Mo and Magnus and I would love to
see them going for this again because I
think this is like the way to break the
game against gaming glus and they to
pull something that they don't expect
and it will break their plan of like you
know having the stable mid mid game I
definitely hope they don't take the
carry do Willow I think the rest is good
but if you remember that game I think
the willow took a really long time to
come online if you're playing against
Gman who want to press you so early I
don't think you can be one hero down in
the way they were for so long like she
just needs so many items to come online
and it really was a case of like the
rest of the lgd team really like
carrying the game to the point where
shirro could take po yeah cuz the big
timing on level is level 20 for dark
Willow carry it's when you get the more
duration on the W so a lot of the time
when you talk about the her like we're
playing for the level 20 Team guys and
uh if you're playing for level 20 for
gaming Gladiators you might be in for a
struggle so good news is it looks like
lgd is first pick so that means that
they have the opportunity to ban the
Chen and the end and then they can take
whatever they want in the draft so I'm
I'll be interested to to see how the
draft changed it up this time I'm mostly
talking about like how they can take a
lead and like pressure uh GG themselves
because this BR mother had an
opportunity you know to to pressure
their towers and to create a lot of
chaos and I think this this is what they
should be aiming for not dark specific
but something unique
lgd had first pick they're still
focusing on that Dazzle that Chan
enchantress like you said Gunner if
you're going to take one out take both
of them out so that's their three bands
and it opens up the Mora for them to to
be able to get their hands on the cool
thing about the Mora is we were talking
about the necros and so thankfully if
Mor ends up being a carry she she's
really good cuz she can shoot him no
matter what if he's ghost shouted so
it's kind of already like a soft counter
to the necro later in the draft and it's
also I think it's one of the better
carriers versus chaos kn he can't burst
you during your old so you have kind of
a way to fight around him yeah I've seen
this match up go both ways obviously
because mu is very uh dependent on her
positioning in fights and Chaos Knight
usually goes for this like silver Ed and
stuff he's going to be seeking her out
if they do find her it mean the bus is
insane what is quite squishy without her
all um and Chaos Knight in general just
this this patch is is so strong his
laning is terrifying like I I wonderful
see grimstroke contested again going
into the second
phase b boom had the flex with chaos
Knight yesterday we saw it it was able
to go to carry off lane for themselves
is that the same for gaming Gladiators
or this is very much a Daio they're okay
with uh if this hero is attempted to be
counted that Dau can still have a really
good game for himself and he'll be able
to come back into do it I think it's
most the heroes for daa because it's
already very strong Lane and it's the
hero he excels and it's very aggressive
as well and it allows celery to pick
Heroes that are not really uh needed for
the lane because it's already like very
self sustainable so he can do his things
with itself T and like run around mid
lane help
Queen so something I'm interested in is
nagaon I think this hero is pretty
strong and she's really good versus
chaos Knight either in a lane match up
or just in the game as a carry to carry
she her Illusions pretty much do the
same thing as K Knights where K Knight
will just use his ult to push out all
the lanes the whole game and N get has
that for free with a much lower cool
down so she's always ready to fight she
can use song to disengage from the chaos
KN and they also ban The Brew uh for the
side of gaming so if I was lgd I'd
probably be looking at a Naga at some
point in this
draft and I'm sure GJ is looking for
another La Droid game I think it will
fit their lineup very
well they want to keep picking their
comfort it's gone them this far it'll
keep you know keep them going so I don't
think gaming really feels like they have
the need to change anything if they get
you know one to two of they're just
stable Heroes every game and they just
change the rest around to just fit it I
think it's kind of their
formula I was very shocked that maybe
not very shocked is the right word here
but I was surprised lgd they went
hardcore on the supports the Phoenix and
the Grim being their ban does still
leave that dark Willow open for gaming
Gladiators to pick up but their response
is Magnus ET yeah I think teams consider
it like one of the counter picks to the
CK nowadays because it stops the
Illusions and along with the Magnus as
well you have their aerp and there's
also like one of the best nothing to say
Heroes so they're looking pretty good
already is also one of the first people
to actually start spamming in pubs a few
weeks ago he I he honestly you know not
to him up too much but I would say he
probably started the meta in pubs a few
weeks ago just like spamming it off in
every game and around that same time was
when you know you saw everyone just
starting to even play a mid but he he's
also really good on in the off Lane so I
wouldn't be surprised that they just
have this as a flex pick and if you know
Quinn tries to counter it right now that
it can just go to the off lane and be
comfortable versus chaos Gladiators to
oh there's another Ace hero that he
excels at I thought they would go for
the laid but uh R king is also quite
nice it's very stable very solid they
like to play with the two course in the
side Lanes so I mean they had it uh
earlier in this weekend as well and it
was part of that push trp that they had
those skeletons can be very annoying and
obnoxious I think everything right now
though is leading for nasire and for lgd
this is looking really scary unless this
next pick kind of counters it which I
don't really know what they can pick
outside of a pugna to prep for it and if
if lgd get AA I think the draft looks
pretty good for them they'll have a way
to constantly give vision for the Magnus
ET also gives Vision they have S sleep
into you know net and sleep play so they
just have a lot of kind of utility with
the Naga across the map I like the Naga
suggestion for sure because it can delay
the game for them but and I was I was
suggesting this profit yeah I was I was
see coming and the
N yeah that profit pick was like that
just made Naga even better yeah so they
take the furion I really like this
versus the strong laning fives like
Elder Titan because what happens is the
fing goes to your safe Lane and kind of
exists there and he's always a 3v2 in
the Top Lane so anytime ET wants to go
aggressive onto this the you know the
safe Lane theal TP in now it's a 3v2 and
the ET is not as strong of a hero well
last time I saw this profit I wasn't
really big a fan of because it looked
like very squishy during the mid mid
game but the way GG are playing this is
like this is such a huge Tempo and uh
you know this Naga like we've seen many
times already like this this Naga is not
going to be able to come online even
after like you know they're pushing your
high ground at 20 minutes 10 seconds
remaining yeah thankfully for Naga one
of the cool things is the games are
really boring to play when you're the
other team cuz she just delays it so if
there's one way to stop gaming from
pushing your base it's to cut all three
waves at the same time simultaneously
and be completely safe cuz you have song
So Naga is one of the ways that you can
pretty much delay a game it's kind of
like a probably more consistent version
of keeper the light just from the carry
R so already right now I feel way more
confident for lgd to take this game into
the mid game to the late game to where
they're more comfortable taking the win
dude I'm terrified for for game and like
how how do you ever take High Ground
when you're playing into ET stomp you're
playing into this skewer back you have a
Naga that's going to cut your waves
while they're holding you off like that
it seems so difficult to ever breach
High Ground without just killing the
entirey of lgd it's so easy when you're
doing it this early yeah I thought that
too for their previous draft but it
seemed they seem to be make it work you
know somehow just purely from winning
lanes and uh making this aggressive
moves in the mid game and like taking
complete lead because of how stable
their mid game is I think as long as
this last pick for lgd either the mid or
offlane has some sort of wave clear to
deal with the skeletons that are going
to come and kind of help defend the tier
tws when they're actually sitting there
in front of you I'll be really happy for
lgd's draft oh there's no way they
didn't P Pango and they pick Pango all
right well there's their wove it gives
them also a team fight to fight on the
towers I really like this match for ra
King you onot the skeletons you burn his
Mana before The Shard so I I really like
the lgd draft I think it's uh much
better than what they had last game they
also kind of don't have the ability to
get countered as hard so I feel very
good for for them and I'm curious as
what Quinn will play this is you know he
knows pangier yeah is it another hoscar
game for him just purely of like how how
they can snow ball after this game I'm
I'm not too sure I think there's
probably a queen of pain angle I think
queen of pain is scales really nicely
verus Naga siren also there's not really
stuns that he has to worry about it's
only the route from Naga siren and so I
think queen of pain kind of has the
mobility also it ganks really well with
the fan that can set up everywhere
across the map he just needs to now deal
with the Naga and have a stable ver Pang
there two big goals I just really
believe in a husar I think you can allow
to have two M Heroes against the queen
and not B the husar in the last Pi I
think he's he's chosing about it right
now he's thinking about it he's worried
he's telling him like don't worry man he
W hus guards it's all good trying to
ease those nerves don't think about it
don't think about
it oh you're right that's a good thing
nice suggestion uh I I think it does
check all the boxes for gaming
gladiators but it's kind of
I again I'm really scared of this Naga I
thought the second that they pick chaos
Knight Naga was going to come out at
some point in the draft and so if
anything I would give lgd an edge right
now yeah all right and what about
yourself sheep uh I think Gunner's
popped off kind of that's true you kind
of predicted everything yeah he really
did sorry no it was great I apologize I
agree with that I think lgd have a
stronger draft I think this Pango
brought everything together that was a
hero I was thinking of for ging to help
deal with the Naga but them just
sweeping it I think it just solidifies
their draft I think their High Ground is
way too scary to go into as well so even
if uh we focus naga's Lane time and time
again Ghana you think that that shutting
down isn't enough to build into gaming
Gladiators that everyone else on the
side of lgd will be able to make space
yeah I think she got picked into pretty
much R king and K KN which are the same
hero that she'll Exel in the lane they
don't really have a way to clear the
illusions that easily so her Lane should
be fine she can honestly be left alone
after four or five minutes and her game
will be good the biggest thing is
whether Quinn can get a lot of work done
in this mid matchup is kind of the way
that GG wants to play is bring up mid
Quinn's going to outplay the enemy mid
laner and just go from the
I'm just worried about supports on the
lgd side like how they going to protect
the Fango from the you know from being a
run over with a queen and supports all
right we'll keep our eyes on Mid we'll
see how impactful this nager is and
we'll see how confident lgd are feeling
about their
draft I am joined by sh of lgd and Helen
will be helping me translate Shia you
have played at countless TI you've
coached countless TI You've Won TI when
you are looking at this tournament is
there any one thing that's unique about
this International compared to others in
the
[Music]
past it's been a while since I've been
in Seattle so that familiar feeling is
coming back I'm happy to hear it but how
about all the fans who are watching
across the world this may be your last
game is there anything you'd like to say
to them to get them excited that lgd is
going to continue
[Applause]
fighting we're going to get them they're
going to get them let's get ready for
game two
there we have it some good words of
confidence coming into this game two
here for lgd up against gaming
Gladiators a hard fought game one from
them for but they weren't able to do it
Gladiator pulling through in that first
game here in this game too what do you
think about the change UPS I'm seeing
already the fact that lgd they've got
Shir on this Naga siren if his Manta
play was anything to go by in the last
game with the Luna you've only got to
imagine what he's going to be able to do
on a Naga siren yeah it feels like two
very different style drafts versus each
other a very fast-paced draft gaming
trying to just take advantage to slam
these Lanes in particular mid Quinn
going for his Quin of pain of course
they're trying to just Snowball the game
out of control lgd trying to slow things
down and if they can the draft looks
amazing right if they can get these
later stages this draft from lgd does
look like it will reign supreme but can
they withstand the pressure gaming has
been the team to dictate the pace to
dictate these quick games this could be
another one they're able to set up if
they set up this queen of pain in
particular for that success sure and you
think sort of some rightful concerns
from the panel as well with regards to
what lgd supports are going to be able
to do early on to sort of enable the
other lanes or or how do you think
that's going to play out I mean it's
it's just difficult to be able to like
with the pro you know the Nature's
profit constantly making these rotations
with the teleport that's where something
they could struggle they're going to
have to like preemptively be ready for
the moves say already right the here
he's to get off the three Shield crash
but still the the damage coming in he's
going to be first blood for cery the
power of the Nature's profit already
coming into fruition here with that
level one play whose blood grenade was
that was that celer I saw one being
thrown out uh yeah was okay so I mean
easy easy grab there for him getting set
up Quinn doesn't get the last hit but
either way does get an advantage inside
that Middle Lane that's the way they're
going to look to play I'm going to just
watching accelery overall these TPS but
are they going to be able to slow down
Dao is the question cuz celer is going
to be constantly moving around perhaps
that's where new and planed are able to
take some Advantage versus this chaos
Knight who usually just wins every
single Lane yeah it talk to me more
about this sort of queen of pain pick we
just don't see it a lot but Quinn
realizing that this is the game to pull
it off what do you think it is directly
about this draft from lgd that's made
him want to get the queen of pain out
against it definitely limited stuns
right just looking overall what they
have they have to commit kind of like
ultim M there's a net and then there's a
Silence from the wera and a Deadshot
it's pretty limited these skill shots
are not the easiest things to land on
something like a queen of pain if he's
able to get that big snowball Advantage
nothing to say getting seven of the last
hits on the first two waves though so
even though he does get killed right
away very very good start for this Pango
but it gets it gets quite rough those
levels once they build up for the queen
of pain does get pretty difficult for
that Pango in the
mid bottom Lane dra being kept very low
here by the harassment from new and
Planet I mean how how strong of L is
this in your book in terms of the Magnus
and the Moa very strong yeah they I mean
it's Universal Magnus you always have
great right click this year I think cuz
he's been the one who actually was did
it first I think they were mentioned
Chanel Theo has to turn turn with the
stun that a whole back new playing on
the edge of his life here drao I'm glad
to see more of the Magnus I feel this
Heroes always has potential in the off
Lane just to make so many out plays just
to shock wave into to skewer plays
overall good base damage to get last HS
I like this Lane a lot it's quite a bit
of attack speed slow too so even if they
try to like turn and fight you you
skewer and you have this calling down
both abilities of course slowing attack
speed it's really tough to fight versus
these
two looking at sort of the the top playe
W you smile on the Elder Titan a pretty
good game for et to combo up with some
of his teammates absolutely I mean he's
playing it's all about the stalling
right stalling out the games they have
the Magnus as well to two of the best
womo comb and even with the N time they
get him still for from you Dao getting
punished the same time though Shir also
to fall both Carri is getting punished
in the safe flan oh wow the top one I
the top one I really wouldn't anticipate
happening but the bottom one with the
way that they were bringing it to
Dao definitely more expected can't
believe they killed this Naga with this
Top Lane there a reason this wraith King
has been constantly picked for this off
Lane how much he's able to do in the
early game and Ace he's been one of the
best with
it keeping eyes on this mid as well
definitely a match up where you could
you could see the solo kills occurring
both Heroes having to be cautious
they've got good amounts of jump and
resets way to back up and and jump back
in if they catch one another low yeah
nothing to say just has to be very
careful with how he uses those swash
buckles a TP comes in from the Nature's
prop and it could just net a kill almost
immediately up top The Stomp gets the
Lotus two of them Shir trying to close
in onto tofu but tofu does have to
Shadow around with the and they've got
back up terer is in they turn the red
five blast over toward Shir Shir getting
surrounded caught in the Sprout he Tak
it out again could be have a good chance
of chasing why smile out as well as why
is SM trying to back off for the right
clicks on tofu are enough double kill
for tofu this Top Lane getting Messi
Messi already as soon as the Naga comes
back and this is going to be the Long
Walk of Shame 30 seconds no TP so much
physical damage the blight Stone coming
in The Wraith king skeleton just hitting
on him there nothing the Naga can do
these early deaths they absolutely hurt
Piro yep and Dao even though he did die
this hero overall it sustains on its own
really nicely two points up on the chaos
strike for Dao so should be able to at
least get this Farm under under the
tower here and Shir TP still on cool
down he's having to take the smoke to
try and get back to Lane as quickly as
he can
a big hit against the nagar in this
laning stage a massive one is also fnn
can now go for the bottom room while
tofu checks the top one will nothing to
say be able to get it nope Quinn gets it
and now tofu's here to back up nothing
to say as a squash he's going to get
caught by the Bramble though still able
to jump away and will have to
potentially back off as this dagger kcks
him him for the kill another dagger
Quinn he's going to get it the kills
there Gladiator is finding a lot of
early action done botom planet and knew
they tried for Cel but Cel is a but he
just walk away from them the stomp does
clip him can they finish shock wave will
drag him back new really wants the kill
he'll get him but now under Tower the
stuns there director trying to step up
see if he can finish on new in return
doesn't look like he have any further
grab 6 seconds to do the stuns back up
in fact he might be in trouble himself
another dead shot connection from pet
into the shock wave got a Lotus may be
able to turno pet cu the stun it's back
up the crits are coming in the stop is
there just in time before Dr is able to
pull in planet with a reality Rift
doesn't matter though celer s his grabs
him the vision to grab him back I mean
now whyu smile's got to be cautious
direct has been handed over to tango he
can start healing up I look at new even
has to be careful with his positioning
Doro just standing Toe to Toe versus
three Heroes I mean again in the mid
lane nothing to say getting bullied by
Quinn and tofu as soon as he's back to
the mid lane he's back out again then
without TP available and Ace is now in a
1 V one versus the nagas and he's more
than happy with that with this type of
setup they have to just keep trying to
move these Lanes around on side of LTD
they need to do something and they will
Planet turns up make sure that this time
round shirou is able to get the kill
against Ace I look at the aggression
it's 10 kills 5
minutes gaming Gladiators their draft
definitely thrives off of this they want
to be the ones just dictating Pace
getting these early kills getting that
lane advantage and so far looking pretty
damn
good long walk back to the mid lane is
going to mean that there's going to be
quite the XP difference here between the
mids qu already halfway through the six
and of course nothing to say yet to hit
his and it's right around the power run
two Quinn very likely to be a to set
this one up planet has to play around
mid to try to stop this queen of pain
from snowballing so
hard will he get
lucky planer will get it quick pause
okay get a crash okie dokie see a quick
reset here from Dao but as things have
gone in this first six minutes
Gladiators exactly the way they want an
explosive opening really with these
moves that they've made and as was
expected with the power of C's Nature's
profit he's always been there as a plus
one I mean even tofu too 40 and two so
far right he is actually ahead of Daio
on Networth he's tied with almost all
the cores at this point as Willow
beautiful stuff I mean getting those
early kills up top making the rotations
onto mid so far means exactly what
gaming wants to do with their draft get
early kills snowball keep putting that
aggressive posture on the map theyve
they've kind of pushed Shir a little bit
to the Jungle already he has to move
away as this nagar so early in the game
he's got might is queued up it's going
to be one of those recovery games for
him after Lane like this those early
deaths slowing down sort of the
potential but as we saw last game l
they are very good at stalling the games
out even if the beginning goes rough
yeah they don't have a Shadow Demon
though to create those Illusions yes
they have the natural nasan but they
don't have a spirit breaker who just
literally clears every single wave a lot
more difficult for nothing to say would
seem this game being slowed down this
much and losing I mean losing Lanes like
this also when you're playing versus
something like this this wraith King and
this Nature's profit there's a reason
that Gan likes to play this so much
right you pick up the tempo so fast so
if you start having to get pushed to
Jungle this early on the side of lgd
these towers are going to start dropping
very very early on with the way that
they want to make moves with the the
sort of the start the supports of gaming
Gladiators got and the fact that Quinn
is is in the lead right now it's it's
not going to be too difficult for
gladiators to go for these deep
movements and try and catch shirro in
his jungle absolutely they just have to
watch out how far they overextend cuz
the way the counter initiation every
from lgd that's kind of their biggest
Thrive is is if gaming pushes the limit
too far they have Wombo Combo team fight
they have massive ways of repositioning
and taking them under these tier tws
potentially
so far early game exactly what gaming
Gladiators wants maybe even more than
they could have hoped for with Ace
having such a damn good start in
top just not easy for nothing to say to
off around this med he's just trying to
at least find the XP for his level six
and a definitely having a very nice
understanding with this wraith King
playing versus the nagas versus the ET
he's all about that plus armor he's got
the Ring of protection I believe he
started with wraith band right
afterwards and phas boot so hard for
them to really bring him out of this
Lane with this with this Naga or the
CT L to restabilize Dao now able to get
this free
Farm why you smart maybe see if we can
go for some sort of Stomp play to grab
the wisdom but it's a risky play for
profit he's not going to be able to stop
them from securing it themselves the
Gladiators in fact he actually gets
caught a indeed is ready with the stun
puts a stop to the TP so not only not
getting the chance to to grab the wisdom
room he ends up losing his life to Ace
such a quick movement there from Ace
don't think that the ET expected him to
move that quick and he's queued up the
radiance now already so going to have
that itemization even versus the nagar
As game does potentially progress he is
incredibly farmed so far on this wraith
King I mean for lgd can they look for
aggressive moves themselves or is it
just a case of them preparing to turn
things around if gaming Gladiators start
heading onto their half of the map they
need more levels for sure I mean the big
one that usually wants to make the moves
is going to be that mid laner but when
he's playing versus queen of and he's
super shut down and new also it's level
four Magnus Now versus the level six CK
Dao is perfectly fine to be left alone
down here so difficult for them to
really make moves in this early game now
as they set on panel these supports
they're kind of needed with with the
cores they have to make the moves with
the cores in
particular this say will get another
Power Rune Quinn they're trying to set
up but it's so hard they need kind of
the silent from the the calling to to
Really clip him outside of that Quinn
he's jumping away every time yeah they
need like the perfect kind of chain St
with the Rolling Thunder and everything
that's why they wanted this poop very
elusive still looking to play around mid
too they got three Heroes poised on the
side of gaming gladers looking to still
go for nothing to
say almost eight on
Quinn actually is going to instantly
smoke him takes the point in the sonic
wave he wants to look keeping the pre
look to keep the pressure going here I
mean wouldn't be a bad catch finding you
he's already had a bit of a tough time
in the lane if they could him down will
be able to break that smoke at they'll
see what's coming but look at Dao's
positioning he still wants to dive new I
mean who wants to come down here to help
him TPS are going to be coming over got
the caught by the BR though nothing to
say the stuns out for Dra nothing to say
he's got the Rolling Thunder the ready
but the Sol way point to the two of them
back new has now nothing to say he's got
to run perfect angle from Quinn to get
that push back stops him in his
tracks gaming just continue to keep
Advantage going and Planet be careful
he's going to miss the dead shot the
stuns there I mean planet he's gone as
well that in an instant they just can't
fight them at this point despite how
hard they try LG and I mean without
rolling thunder now they cannot protect
this Tower top also looks get starting
to get pressure rotation from tofu
coming in with
Ace pressure on all fronts 10 to three a
4K lead already pre 10 minutes gaming
doing what they do
best daa almost having he's going to
have his armlet pretty much done already
Shiro is starting to get some recovery
Farm but he's not really the one who
makes plays to recover things he's the
one who has to just kind of sit back and
farm for a very very long time the fact
that this off lane and mid lane are
struggling so much it's going to be very
difficult for lgd to mount these
defenses on these early
Towers it's going to take time for for
sort of 300 gold in towards the blink
dagger yeah he's very
poor it's tier one in the mid lane
starting to take get a bit of a beat
down here by
Dao he's actually ready to start
jungling over on lgd side of the map he
knows that there's very little that lgd
can do to push back the CK I mean he
knows they're just very underleveled
Magnus still not quite level six the two
supports as well too their damages just
extremely lackluster on the side of lgd
the only damage they really have is
going to be coming out from the Pango
right now and this Pango is very shut
down in this game top Tower to fall
a he's getting the chance to step up and
trade hits here with Shir right up
towards close to the tier two look how
confident he is they can't him they
don't have damage for him by this point
they does even have the armlet just yet
I mean isir is just getting chased out
completely from his
jungle and immediately he has a wave
bottom meets his Tower Dao just heads
back over as they take out top Tower Ace
is going to have this I mean this is
going to be one of the faster off Lane
radiances that comes out and it's a
great Radiance game playing versus this
KN turn qu continue to play incredibly
aggressive here push the limits I me you
got tofu coming in from the side as well
and look at Dau I me he just pops a
fantasm and sends the illusion on new
and just zones him out of the lane new
actually can't walk up and contest an
illusion
and could just die if he steps up a
little bit too far that's to be pretty
careful same to be said for nothing to
say he's having to go right back under
the tier two cannot show his face
anywhere close to one going to try T it
down bottom SK is only going to be on
towards the fantasm maybe they can find
CER they get the stomp set up D's
considering maybe helping out on this
fight but the they're in with the stun
sonic wave pushing back the three of
them it's actually given the space for
celer to walk away he's perfectly fine D
considering nothing say tripped up by
the Spells of tofu is the dump Forge
there from Quinn nothing is day taken
down they just can't kill any of them
not evener again and a Quinn this time a
sonic wave just to knock back the Pango
works out perfectly completely messing
with nothing to say this Pango is having
no effective this night right now can't
even touch accelery a 6K lead already
for gaming Gladiators this is as hot as
a start as you can get
really The Relic is done the radiance is
going to be coming up with 13 14 minutes
for Ace
oh oh oh it's a Dao I was say it's bound
to happen it hasn't happened much at I
feel when he dies like this the win is
pretty much guaranteed uh you know can't
believe it always happens we should have
had a camera on him that was unexpected
we'll get a replay okay well as I say uh
when that's happened before he pretty
much always wins the game so um you know
all path the course hereo can't believe
it always happens oh my
goodness things calming down for a few
moments here but gaming have I mean
they've hit so hard in these first 12
minutes what more could you ask for all
three tier ones taken out you've
completely shut down the Pango the
Magnus his timings are all shot as well
too you're having three cores farming
perfectly and the two supports as well
too look at how Farm the two of them are
neck and neck 3600 gold on the two of
them and yeah Radiance it's it's going
to be done already so he's going to have
that way to just control the map even
more and have the counter versus the
nasar and even as game
progresses these passive moments just
not favoring lgd at all see it again
here I mean at this point we all knew
there was a high likelihood something
was going to go wrong and it did oh my
God any there we go toea with a smile
for that one Quinn did not whole Serious
Business from Quinn he weren't happy how
dare you and my perfect queen of pain
game what are you
doing look how aggressive they're still
posturing though continuing just go for
nothing say no space for this
man uhoh man I mean jawe gave him some
rubs on the shoulders but so far it's
not helping
050 they're trying to find anything that
they can to get look at this W smile now
positioning for wisdom room potentially
trying to get the two of them stolen at
least but to already running
over and celer is even teing in
aggressively they're just going to take
both it seems on the side maybe with a
stomp why you SM can get this one no to
a to kite it out gets back in picks it
up will be able to grab their own okay D
actually isolated new is here as well
see if they can get it they got the skew
up they'll try and turn but this time
ooh nice on it might be allowing them to
get the two of them actually cuz now
they can set up over towards CER they
kill off Daio they close the gap in on
toward C gets clipped by the Deadshot a
couple of kills here for LD nicely done
from shirro I mean he's the one with a
minus and he's the one actually making
the plays happen here to bring some
stuff back nicely done and they got the
wisdom something finally gone for the
side of
lgd that area of the map not not really
been a happy place for Duro in these
last few moments back ends up denying
himself and also ends up getting kill
killed off probably not a place we'll
see him head back to anytime soon but as
probably says don't worry guys I'm the
real carry I mean it's all a distraction
it certainly seems that way cuz indeed
he continues to match the farm of shirro
and I just I mean I this is going to be
one of the slower timings I think we see
comes out for nothing to say this
diffusal blade it's been slowed down so
much he still doesn't have it he's still
about 800 gold
away Midas they're just going to be
going for all the way to this late game
here double Midas is coming out for lgd
shirro he's caught
going to get clipp by the sonic wave
once more nothing to say getting pushed
back have to use the remainder of the
Rolling Thunder to just Retreat cannot
afford to go into The High Ground
against gaming Gladiator his bottom
length drao he's alone I mean he still
feels just sort of super confident to
play like this and just be this
distraction really just try and draw the
attention of lgd down here and away from
Ace it's very typical D all right just
just getting in their faces super
aggressive sometimes over aggressive but
either way it's his place down it works
time and time again does it really
does look at these Illusions they die so
fast extra bit of gold going for celery
going straight down that pipe route
himself to after the solar Crest just
looking to ball up 7K lead Quinn oh does
get caught by the net got the opening
net do they have the follow up for the
silence the dead shot as well is
perfectly done but enough no way still
able to Blink away the wraparound coming
in from a with the red fire blast and
the skeletons over towards why you smile
why you smile he's able to move speed up
here H enough mov be to get away from
him a trying to turn his attention
towards more but lgd CED out this
counter play from face plan it back in
range of the The Wraith King though is
Ace with the back of accelery should be
able to block off his escape the stun
comes in the crits come out they take
Planet down I think you can imagine the
Gaming's going to look to really
accelerate things as soon as they see
new the Magnus having a Midas they're
probably like guys let's go go go they
have no blink dagger on mag every single
time Dr is just going straight for new
anytime you shows his face on the Lane
right lgd they're playing for the Super
Lane game right this might is queued up
top gaming probably wants to keep
pushing down for this Tower glyph is
down can't believe Quinn gets away I
mean he is very tanky at this point I
mean and they really did everything they
could to lock him down it just wasn't
enough it was pretty much perfect but
yeah the occult bracelet the magic
resistance just get 2,000 HP on this
queen of pain cuz that Advantage he's
gotten from the early game all right
blink done on you are you smoking up on
lgd to make a play around this or you's
still sitting back and looking for the
counter plays I think they can look to
make plays with the Pango and the Magnus
for sure
still I mean they're going to be playing
for later stages but if they can find
Opportunities to catch Heroes that are
pushed up too far toward these tier tws
they can definitely get some kills maybe
even surprise ones on to something like
Ace penel was talking about the the mana
burn sometimes from the Pango can be a
little bit of an issue for these W kings
ace is just going to go straight for
that Shard next catch bottom go the
split up do they have enough it's a huge
amount of damage not quite enough
yet does get as well making sure that
these illusions able to finish Duro off
I Shiro is he is getting quite involved
with this nagas just trying to bring
things back together for his team I mean
he really did so much last game keeping
it going into Luna with the Illusions
this very much even more perfect hero
for him to play when it comes to just
keeping the game going buying time for
the entire team of lgd to
scale there's that Shard for Ace doesn't
have to worry about that mana burn
coming into play here lgd still looking
for a player at DD now on nothing to say
they want to get something done with
this
blink a solo RP would absolutely cut it
they they'll go for Quinn if they want
to about it can they get the cat they
straight in they get the drag back this
time have they got enough lock down to
sleep the alive pushes back you and Quin
is's able to jump away turn with the
sonic wave and walk this one off as Ace
he's considering getting involved he he
starts to set straight towards them
feeling strong with the fact that he's
got that shot hasy The Reincarnation
ready to use aggressively I they just
use so much
use their Pango roll they Ed their
Magnus too so gaming they're going to
run at them right here celer tping up
top already looking for nothing to say
he got backup coming in but they want
this Tower it's 300
HP Quinn just keeps getting away over
and over again
here a nice attempt there though from
lgd they had they had to go for
it I mean look how aggressive he's
playing even near the tier two the
Magnus is this is this this is dangerous
positions here though those skewer plays
near tier 2 is is something they still
have to do respect on the side of gaming
Dao we're closing in on the the bkb
timeing he's got it pretty soon if he
wants to take about the
echo still looking to keep accelerating
things with these ult on cool down 550
seconds no RP 28 on the Rolling Thunder
top Tower will
fall Ace has skeletons pre at the ready
too they want to keep threatening it all
here maybe swing toward the mid lane
they've actually dragged the wave from
mid Daio to look to keep this pressure
going Quinn taking out Shiro bottom
smoke time from gaming glates at this
time
round they know the heroes are
positioned down bottom in particular
that nagas they know that chiro was down
here making the long wrap around you see
nothing to say for a second your a h the
jump straight away with the stun it's
far too much damage for nothing to say
to
survive tofu and Ace menaces this game
tofu 5505 the instant bedum trusting his
buddy
might be able to run into more too Shiro
he's been spotted Ace oh he knows which
one the real one get with the jump the
Illusions are out Sher going look to try
and turn to him with the fear pushing
back sherro for now means that Ace
doesn't have to worry about losing The
Reincarnation quite yet he's still got
that to protect himself and go for a
second round it will get forced out here
with splitter too deep forward new
looking for some skew Place 5 Seconds
till it's back
up we manag to clear out the make sure
there's no vision for lgd to play around
to try for that sort of jump so gaming
Gladiators will back off safely a cool
smoke thr from gaming they kind of force
lgd all the way back to their base
getting out of their jungle with that
one even while picking up a
kill and Shiro's Farm continues to roll
in very nicely still nice trying to get
this heart done on top of the man he's
closing in on it the only scare is that
the pengle just continues to have this
very very hard game same thing for the
Magnus and the Naga siren even at this
point like even if gets the ultimate
scaling all the way to the end of these
games is he able to carry versus all
this they have great late game but it's
an 8K lead already for the side of
gaming Gladiators they're getting crazy
scaling even on the supports as we were
mentioning I've been waiting to see what
tofu looks to queue up cuz he's having
such a good game the U scepter but he's
sitting on 12200 if he does want to look
to go down some scaling route
too and there's the pipe now for
celery more and more
tankiness when he's got the agony
finished up now too so much more
potential much better ways to be able to
clear out this nasar
too as Ro potentially soon on the docket
here for gaming bkb finished up for
Dao and those last few attempts from lgd
they just haven't been able to take down
this queen of pain 100 to zero and
Shiro's gone for the full tanky route
rather than the aggressive route that we
sometimes do see from the nagas I think
sometimes we do see that like Orchid
kind of playmaking style come out but
shirro he's just trying to build up for
himself he spotted got eyes on you f the
TP is coming in as well see if he can
get the blink off in time no right cck
are there celer will catch him they drag
him back into the stun new punished here
for trying to farm this bottom half of
the map gaming Gladiators they'll be
having none of that kind of the name of
the game though for lgd paull pull
gaming away from their base try to buy
more and more time even though new does
die does force three Heroes to make the
move down
there up the RO now Ro now yep to grab
this ACE also very close to his own bkb
yeah and with that kill that they got
onto new I mean for lgd it's probably
too difficult for them to contest down
here anyway
but now it's guaranteed here for gaming
to be able to finish that one
off and tofu still considering his item
build 1700 gold he hasn't queued it up
I'm waiting to see which one he does
want to go down the route
of we shall
see que going for a little bit more
protection something you don't see too
often anymore on the queen of pain but
is buying a ules after having his Agony
and his Kaaya so just that little bit of
extra protection versus the calling in
particular could be
huge as with this agis imagine the game
is going to look to control the map a
lot more here try to constrict this
nagas from getting out shirro playing in
these dangerous positions trying to get
Farm in the enemy ancients and cutting
some waves nice micro coming out from
him just like we saw from that
Luna I mean honestly as long as he's
able to survive survive and stay alive
you can probably guarantee that two of
these waves at least will be held right
back onto gaming gladiator's half of the
map it's not going to be too easy for
them to get a push going towards
multiple Lanes at the same time
Gladiators with the play from
Shir as lgd smoked up want to try
something here with the RP once more qu
they're going to try it again this time
around do they have enough he got the
the out of there that's an RP down and a
splitter and that time they don't even
come close to killing him this your pick
up feels pretty damn beautiful there if
they don't have that chain Stone which
they really don't have with their draft
he's going to be able to get it off
every time and he's going for kayange so
stus this is going to make it
potentially even easier for him to get
off afterwards in these later instances
pretty much the only way they can kill
this Quin a pain is if Quinn sort of
blinks into them but Quinn's not been
making those mistakes this game or if
they have absolutely everything that
comes in like perfectly with Shiro
though they need everybody hitting him
at the same time ult on cool down gaming
might look to make another move here
they see sh top I mean this is an
empowered nasar they're kind of giving
away which the real one is I mean and
they know that there's no RP and H knows
this is the real one I mean they're
already teing in onto the back lines as
well Shir is going to go for the song TP
out same to be said for while you smile
get out oh that was close though the
fear from tofu nearly catch in but lgd
will escape oh man if tofu's blink was
actually on him there that potentially
could have been a catch on to either one
of these Heroes blink was coming on The
Courier for the willow so tofu he made
his decision what he wants to go for
this is a cool pickup too I feel this is
more about stopping it that initiation
or the counter initiation that lgd is
going for rather than scaling for
himself he's looking to see where this
RP comes blink get the fear off and
reset the fights for his team so a cool
choice if he's able to get those
catches how's nothing to sa his game
going I mean recovering slightly but
still 06 and zero hasn't been involved
in any sort of positive action this game
when it comes to kills it's been rough
he's tried but it's just been completely
stopped from Quinn every single time he
comes in a sonic wave just pushes him
back and stops him in his
tracks 81% as we see there right now for
gaming plus is liking their chances so
much weight right now on shir's
shoulders really feels like all of it's
going to be these big plays that he's
able to make with these Illusions assoon
having a butterfly so he is getting
quite
tanky but the rest of his
allies contining to be pretty poor
gaming they're scaling on all three
cores oh they really are they really are
a still holding the top spot out of the
team incredible Farm on this off flame
wraith
King just a blink the bkb going down the
or afterwards just to enable his
teammates even more
so and just keeping now they're starting
to keep more and more control of the map
after they got this AIS they're dealing
with all three lanes celery showing on
one lane Ace showing on another and
Quinn with the backup of two Heroes
showing on another one so they're
keeping the lane shoved in and
constricting shirro from getting his
Illusions actually out to cut these
waves he's actually been unable to for
the last few
minutes the fact that they R&D getting
the chance to hit these two tier tws at
the same time definitely a concern for
how lgd would want to be keeping this
game going and they can potentially even
set up a Tormentor if they'd like to
maybe a little bit of a risk playing
versus the Magnus and everything but Ace
may be thinking about
it did celer show what he's going to be
building just yet okay does have the
agony queued up we know he's going to be
a great
option look at this the Deep jump oh
he's going past the two three is ready
to sort of dive in a look for Action the
sleep is there RP as well two of them
it's going to bring them low up from
Quinn Quinn will be a jump out of this
one get to the side actually hits pretty
much a fight wave there a on the second
line goes towards the ET takes down y
you smile Shir has to use the S to back
up I mean what a jump there I mean
salary tping it aggressively and then
Ace jumping for just go straight for it
yeah Quinn gets a connection on almost
everybody withow pretty much a five
map just trying to use this AG just as
much as possible Dao 40 seconds left on
it he should be able to Prof it the once
maybe maybe not he's actually able to to
get out of this dire he's not even lose
the ages quite yet little toggle gets
himself out they force the glyph they
force quite a bit there I mean pretty
much every single ulti being used from
the side of lgd just to sustain and
withstand themselves celer does buy back
at the least there one silver lining for
lgd but gaming at any moment you can see
they're very confident just jumping
in
Dao the skew back on him 10 seconds to
lat
seconds and we just look to take him
down the first time whilst the ages is
still there and they get the torment to
qu go for round two Quinn he's in with
the Jump drao Plus the pkb turns over
toward the surrounded here in the corner
they came blocked off by the Rio son
wave as well he's pushed up to the side
of the mount Quinn jumps in he's killing
off the back lines he's taken out
blooded you a all as R the round of the
nasar and Shir he's out 50 seconds none
of them with by back gold available as
GG will be able to push down this bottom
Lane maybe even get the tier three in
the barracks with this one they're
starting to fall a bit long Quinn
but Dao's he's full HP he's back to for
Quinn I mean what can they do to push
this one back at at least they's still a
tier two in the mid lane they don't have
their Magnus they have no way to skewer
no way to hold this off this RX looking
pretty dead can they stop
this I Quinn this Arcane Rune right
there coming into play and now Ace
nothing to say going to try and put a
bit of a slow down to this push but at
the same time he's going to make sure
that he keeps a fair bit of a distance
when the Rolling Thunder does comes to
an end I mean they're still going even
for the melee Rex here gaming Gladiators
pushing the limits will be backing up
Magnus is respawning RP's back up
they'll give respect but another massive
hit 13k lead they bring down shiron and
Quinn with the back of that Arcane Rune
kind of making the magic happen The
Confident blink forward into everybody I
mean he knows they can't kill him yep
now his itemization feels absolutely
perfect this game and he knows it he's
playing so
confident full heart now on the CK as
well too a massive hit from
gaming and everything coming back up for
the pretty soon sonic wave 15
seconds it's just been so hard for LGT
to really find a a kill at all yep I
mean as soon as the song gets used they
kind of just have to like reset and run
and then once Shir gets isolated without
song He's just dead they have no way to
follow up to protect
him Quinn soon to have a shivas as well
to more and more layers for them to try
to get through to bring down this quad
trying to step out of their base a
little bit lgd
but scary to come
out they keep having to just follow each
other together they have to play as a
unit here versus the side of gaming they
can just get picked up in an instant as
we see there gaming no hesitation to
jump if a hero's
isolated they find something with this
smoke Quinn he's got a shield run they
try for the skewer back hesitations of
course they they don't want to drop the
RP because the last few times it's just
not worked out I mean even if they get
him there honestly he just probably pops
Shield R and will fly see the same thing
that happened time and timeing
before three lanes being shoved in you
see the lines being drawn from lgd
they're like we need to get these Lanes
out
tooing for the very aggressive play
here for the jump jump Shiro he's got
backup get glimmered
instant play I mean why you smile in the
perfect position there to protect him
more and more items to deal with that
Naga you said you know the radiance is
out the AC's out for Ace great items
versus Naga now shivas of course coming
out for Quinn harder and harder for
shirro to Solo Carry
this all three lanes shoved in no space
for Shiro to get out on the map should
be able to take out this final tier two
tower now gaming Gladiators and R it's
going to be a long spawn Ace jumps in he
goes straight forward straight over
towards planet that will be the glimmer
again to try and get him out of there
butel with the TP PS up to The High
Ground Planet he's been caught by the
Sprout they get the skew back on the
celery C caught by the Sun as they take
the Nature's profit down but the sonic
wave from Quinn Clips planet look how
confident he is with the shield Rune
knows they have no way to get him celery
does die and that was the dieback so 60
seconds without him gaming looks like
they will be happy with that tier two
and that kill they back up and get that
farm going here DD spawns up top and
Quinn gets one of those big talents with
the agony's build he's got the 20 Talent
long spawn on that Rush maybe a
fortunate one for lgd it feels like a
little bit but either way they have more
than enough time on the side of gaming
to just keep these Lanes shoved in to
constrict
Jiro scaling continues we are going to
be able to listen in on bleed gaming
gladia to see what they had to say about
those previous
moments if we play in formation they
have no chance of fighting we just do
not overreach the only way they can kill
us if we get like Ultra scared into
combo yep I mean he's absolutely right
on that one we're seeing it the way that
the gaming Gladiators are moving as a
unit it's just not allowing lgd any
opportunity to to get the jump on not to
get the jump on multi- Heroes too right
we've seen one man RPS one man skewers
one man Splitters just God gaming they
really have not been giving the
opportunities to them to get that big
womo combo onto multiple Heroes full hex
now on to Shiro a little bit more catch
to potentially trip up Quinn
he he's really got his work cut out Shir
really does he's had the chance to get
the farm but can can he do what's
necessary to keep lgd's hopes alive here
in this game too it really is all up to
him Ro 30 seconds gaming positioning
themselves for
it all four five Heroes actually set up
down bottom Daio getting closer and
closer to his mkb to be able to focus
down this nagar as well
Ace almost has an agon so even if they
do get caught in some type of Wombo
Combo and stuff like that there's the
plays around
it more and more scaling continues
Ro
lgd is a tough call to make but maybe
they might feel like they have to
potentially try to contest this Roshan
but yeah this it's a very very hard call
to make I mean and gaming Gladiators
they're going to be coming straight for
them first smoke
gladi this could be totally unexpected
here they're going to be ready to head
into the triangle Dao leading the charge
scouted by a tree blink link is there in
time nicely
done and they will all get
out s will back up deal with the lanes
as his team goes for the RO super close
to his own
Agony me this item is always is super
nice just so you don't have to really
like commit your hero so far he just
throws a Wrath of nature cuz it disarms
as well too all the bounces that it gets
on with the route so can be really nice
to just protect the heroes if they do
get caught inside of a big womo combo as
Ro will
fall Tacho can play a little bit more I
mean not say a little bit more
aggressive but more
aggressively and Quin a secondary life
has yet to die this game I mean they're
heading towards him top there's still a
tier one available here for backup to
come in if if they do want to dive this
but it's a CK with an
AIS try and te something out they'll get
the bkb response but nothing
more Tacho seems like he knew that was
coming from a mile
awayer wisdom runes double grab double
grabed again for gam lgd looking to try
to keep getting something up out of top
here but the lanes are starting to get
pushed in it is a lot of them out here
pretty deep on on the map but can can
they really start a fight
Planet able to get the Pierce the Veil
off little bit of protection but still
the damage really coming in gr the
magical bringing him down low he's
caught in the trees Quin finishes him
off lgd they've got to get out of there
nice Ward from tofu quickly places that
one down on the
side tofu also still just having this
flawless game 5 Z on eight it's enabled
Quinn to be able to snowball how many ad
spawns bottom Ace able to grab this one
now
too that Agony is done
and they can play like this just sort of
split across the map knowing that lgd
just can't really jump any of them and
if they do there's going to be more than
enough time for for them to survive long
enough for backup to arrive yeah they've
got all this itemization to to deal with
this nasar and as also of course didn't
point it out but he did get blessed with
the cloak of flames on top of everything
too so cloak of flames radiant so he's
going to be amazing versus these
illusion Heroes on top of qun having the
shivas and everything too and having
clal CL look how many of them they have
yeah these Lanes they're just constantly
being dealt with on top of the wrath of
nature of course brooding once you get
that Agony is the cool down also
dropping down to that 60 seconds he can
just throw it off cool down keep these
Lanes constantly shoved in keep lgd
inside of their base Quinn now with the
Lincoln as well to another layer to try
to go through they're just never going
to catch him nope doesn't feel like it
not with the way that he's played I mean
honestly it's been pretty much zero
mistakes from him so far Quinn a
Flawless game a Flawless two games to be
honest with
you lgd they're going to try it for it
again smoke
up they've got to take some sort of
highrisk plays here to try and pull this
game back in their favor who do you want
to go for though there's an Agony for a
king as well too these tanky front line
with AIS cheese too and Ace is just
walking he might just even blink in he's
taunting them he wants him to go for him
he's going to jump let's start off and
see they turn with the hex if they can
bring him down the once they get the
drive back up towards the tier three to
the base take him down once see as they
can do it a second time Quinn starts to
jump for get the shadow strike out on
New it's enough to hold them back and
indeed there's not any sort of attempt
from lgd to try and go on Ace a second
time 60 seconds we'll be back
up pretty much all wave starting to push
in against
lgd minutes
just under big neutrals found pent Edge
now for him as well after this mkb he is
hitting incredibly hard Quinn also finds
himself a storm crafter and Ace a Havoc
Hammer more really good items versus
pretty much all these
Illusions it's rare to see the nagas
unable to really send the Illusions out
to try to get any Farm but they're just
dealing with them so quickly every time
they see
them leaving the base just just does not
feel like an option right now now for
lgd whatsoever getting massively
outarmed the Gaming's farming 90% of the
map we heard it in the coms earlier just
sort of keeping everything very calm on
gaming Gladiators Dro clipped by the
Harpoon they're able to pull him in but
Quinn's here with a back up they get the
push back on to the three of them the RP
is there but it looks like it doesn't
really matter they've already lost
planet Shir having to use the song to
reset it's another Retreat from lgd they
can't even hold around the barracks as
the melee Barracks will fall is that
another for man sonic wave I feel like
from quid I feel like every single time
he's getting so many of these Heroes I
can't imagine what his damage in this in
this game but it probably is by far the
highest and Ace going again he's going
up towards the tier four they get
another round of the Shadow strike
daggers out into the two of them sh
trying to step forward the Illusions out
but drao pretty much ignoring them
hitting onto the tier C with the Sun a
stepping forward they get the pull back
with the rift Shiro's in trouble the hex
is there thrown down ons dire not enough
to to save shirro taken out short of the
money on buback you also to fall they
don't have to buy back here lgd is
gaming Gladiators taking them down one
by one St over the walls nothing to say
he's also out without no the exposed
they're looking to close it's over GG is
gone gaming Gladiators take this one two
will be moving on to the Grand finals
what a display of dominance this last
pick queen of p i mean this seemed
perfect Quinn just took over everything
nothing to say ends the game 07 and zero
that has got to be one of the most
brutal mid comparisons we've seen I
think Quinn just letting out his disgust
for Pango Pickers big time in this game
with how dominant and how just rough
that mid match up ends up looking on the
scoreboard F I mean look at the damage
numbers it tells the tale of it all
Quinn look at this I mean ridiculous
36,000 how many fourman SS can we see
how many times is he just going to stop
nothing to say in his tracks in the
rolling Thunders nothing to say did
11,000 damage lgd tries to play for the
lake game but it doesn't even matter
gaming just controls everything and even
if it gets to these later stages they
had full grasp I mean they look
brilliant I mean as we said we we knew
it from the Dao def at the neutrals that
this game was over they always win the
games like that it's a crucial point I
mean you know from that point on she
just not beating them you know dero he's
in full Duro form and he does not get
stopped no he does not a Flawless game
from gaming Gladiators absolutely I mean
LG they had a great run but here today
they get shut down out of the
competition by Gaming Gladiators who are
going to be moving onto that ground
finals with an incredible Force after
the sort of ferocity that they win these
two games with gaming Gladiators they'll
take the series 20-0 against lgd and are
going to the Grand
finals a dominant showing from this team
they have made it all the way from the
first lower bracket round and now
they're going to be playing in the grand
finals in a short time they have a
little bit of time to reset and we have
some time to break down this series to
talk about game number two because Naga
could could have done work Gunner we saw
the pick coming we thought it was a
great counter pick but the game never
progressed to a point where she had map
to farm where she could do anything yeah
I think the Quinn queen of pain kind of
popped off yeah massively nothing to say
had a really rough time in the mid lane
and uh Quinn just showing the mid diff
uh he's kind of shown that the entire
lower bracker run I think every game
they play it pretty much ends up being
Quinn just destroys the lane and they
just snowball it throughout the whole
game he took that Pango pick personally
for sure he did I mean tomato also did s
for rotations right because tofu coming
here to the mid lane twice and I mean
this death from the r was just hilarious
but anyways like coming mid twice and
like making that insane Advantage from
the mid lane starting and like TN he
never died like this game he played
perfectly and he was doing so much work
in these fights like we thought Naga
would be a problem but with the way he
played and how how much he was like
scaling and like how many items did he
get like this Naga was not even even be
able to do anything in this game and all
their Heroes allow them to keep pushing
their advantage so so hard like you have
a wraith King like you want to W King
can be quite squishy when he's on the
back foot right but when you're ahead
you're able to use those two lives to
front for your team using Nature's
profet Tri to scout everywhere you're
checking back in your own jungle to make
sure lgd aren't trying to farm there
you're scouting into the enemy jungle to
find people to gank and kill like you're
able to just keep going and going and
going and in the moments where they
thought they might have had something
suddenly gaming are up an item they have
a bkb queen of Pain's able to use her Al
to maybe rebuff the Pango uh you know
ultimate like they have so many tools
from this lead early to just allow them
to Stomp the game mean there's also
these little things that celer does
right you don't notice it in game but
he's like blocking the spawns with the
trees like you newr games and like
denying all the farm from lgd side too
like those little things that he's doing
on the sumon heroes are like very
Flawless as well we heard a little bit
of comments as well throughout this game
Quinn was making the call he said let's
play inform formation let's not play
scared but how do you ensure that not
playing scared doesn't result in a bad
initiation Gunner how do you make sure
or what was their formation to make sure
every team fight was going to go in that
way that they could have the advantage
pretty much what he means is don't make
the same mistake of the diving too far
on The High Ground or diving too far in
that Tri camp in the first game right
where they just stay in a ball and they
just move up slowly slowly they take the
objective that's in front of them they
don't go for more and every fight seemed
like Quinn would just delay the fight
with his ult he would just push back the
pengo roll or whatever initiation there
was from Magnus and once the fight kind
of starts and they get to survive that
initial time and queen of pain gets two
Q's off three Q's off the fight just CR
W is over gaming Gladiators is now a top
two team they're going to be at the
Grand finals I'm sure they're related so
let's hear from them in a little bit
he's actually not ready yet they want to
take some time they want to compose
themselves so we can hear maybe a little
bit more from you sheep about the game I
don't know I just thought it was like so
clean and nice they never really got to
their timings and when they were able to
like skew her back it's like you're too
tanky you're too hard to kill you have
an AIS like they're playing this so
carefully and disciplined like the fact
that they stomped early but the game
still kind of you know dragged a little
bit it's just cuz game are not giving
them any opportunity to throw
it was a hidden counter pick to the to
the Pango as well I didn't know that you
know this queen of pain is such a big
problem to the Pango unit fights because
he couldn't really roll into the fight
and create this Kos because he was
constantly pushing back and they did a
really good job of like stopping Magnus
from initiation because like it was
their only chance of like getting this
two or three man RPS to turn the game
around but they never had a chance to do
that all right well now I know for sure
that they are ready we're going to have
a winners interview we're going to see
how Ace feels about playing in the grand
finals being a top two
team absolutely absolutely ladies and
gentlemen it's Ace from gav
Gladiators Ace you are the rock of this
team you are hardly ever moved by
anything but now you are going to the
Grand finals of the international a
completely dominant year with only the
smallest amount of stumbles and now you
are back and I'd like to see crowd if we
can finally crack this egg can you guys
give it up for ice and get this guy to
get along
excited there it is there it is how does
it feel to be going the grand finals
baby yeah it feels pretty good but uh we
didn't win yet so I'm not I'm not all in
thegu yet you know I'm still down on the
ground still need to be focused oh
that's what your team needs fantastic uh
any words out there for your competitors
you know that have come and gone you
guys have crushed everybody breaking
records potentially one in a million in
history going from lowers to going to
the Grand finals and winning it any
words for the teams that you have
brutally eliminated along the
way sorry boys maybe next
time and of course thank you coming up
to the Grand finals this is a match that
you guys have done many times before how
are you going to beat Team
Spirit they uh hard to crack but we're
just going to play our game do what
we've been doing so far and then adapt
along the way and we'll see we will see
we will see a calm
man but I'm not going to get you let you
get away with that are you going to win
the grand finals coming up my friend I
want to get you hyping up this crowd
just once once in your entire career
with me interviewing hype these people
up are you going to win let's go
let's go
go get the rest baby get in there I got
right thank you so much we'll see them
soon back to you guys thank you so much
slack what a fantastic interview we
finally cracked him we were able to do
it ASA gave us all his emotion in one go
that R off the crowd to get them hyped
for the fact they are going to be going
to the Grand Final it does mean though
lgd their run has fallen a little bit
short they're still third place a top
three team it's an amazing performance
considering this org had a pretty big
roster reshuffle for themselves three
brand new players this was their first
TI and they went the distance res not
the whole way but they went a long way I
think they did amazingly but the only
thing I would like uh suggest them for
the for the future like just like you
know think about their own play style
like uh you know find their their
strategies and like like not respond too
much to the enemies yeah cuz it always
seemed like this entire series and kind
of the entire lower bracket is gaming
forces everyone to play their game and
lgd it seemed like they fell to it
and looking forward there's Spirit which
I think are one of the teams that are
really good at doing their own thing
whether they're winning early game
losing early game they're going to play
their game and they're going to win so
if there's one team that hopefully won't
conform to how gaming plays it will be
spirit in the finals how do you feel
about lgd sheep what's one of your
highlights that you had over the last
three weeks with them I just think I
mean I'm just really happy that they
managed to take it this far I think like
them and Azure R really showing up for
China you know there was this massive
Gap at the beginning of the year where
so many old players did retire
and we had this new players filling in
like we have how now on lgd and then you
know some players came back but they
filled that Gap really well and they got
the experience they needed to bring
themselves to This Ti and to perform and
and so many of these players had their
first lands this year and like to get
third place now at TI like that is
phenomenal like they should be so proud
of themselves and I really hope they
take that to next year and go even
further do you feel like this is the uh
revitalization of the China region where
I think for sure they have like a lot of
motivation right now since two of their
top teams like in the top three and four
so it's it's a really big uh boost for
the region I mean of course it would
have helped if they won the whole thing
right but it's still a very good result
and I'm sure like a lot of people get
inspired by that and you're going to see
a lot of more like Chinese competition
coming into next year and next season
yeah cuz they struggled I think the full
season but now it kind of goes to TI and
this is what matters right so them doing
good at TI is definitely really good for
the region yeah they were within the
region really dominant and then it was
like that 9th 12th throughout so I think
it's a massive feat for themselves a
massive accomplishment so they should be
very happy but uh lgd falling short here
but gaming Gladiators moving on do you
want to talk about the gaming Gladiators
team spirit match up before we get our
exit interview yeah sure all right we're
listening to you so you're the pro um
again I think it's kind of the same
story right it's hopefully the the
drafting you have to solve this early
game issues where gaming Gladiators wins
their Lanes Quinn has won his Lane I
would say probably 80% of the games at
this t 90% to be nice to him and they
kind of just snowball off that every
time and it's also the the supports
rotating I think the supports are
probably the best support Duo at
controlling the early game moving around
controlling runes ganking mid and just
the way that they always set up their
Sidelines as well it's all it's
everything you just have to counter and
so to some extent what reso was saying
was you don't want to purely counter the
enemy draft but I think there's some
limit to kind of finding a balance where
you're doing your own thing that doesn't
get countered by what gaming is
doing yeah I'm definitely bit worried
about Laurel because Quinn is like
showing like every time like every match
up like it doesn't matter who he's
playing against like he's stomping the
the guy and like also with the support
rotations like it's a really big problem
so Spirit needs to be ready for that and
accounting for that you don't have faith
in the growth that L has had over this
year he's been showing up more and more
every event that we see him I think L is
like so stable that if you kind of if
you crush him the way you crush like
nothing to say in that last game right
like I think he'll struggle to find a
game and it will be very hero dependent
on the impact he's able to have for
example in games that they're losing
when he's on cona he's going to play a
lot better than like when he's on his
Viper you know just by way of the hero
by way of his play style so I think it's
going to come down a lot to the draft I
really hope he doesn't get his conquer
game and want to win I hope he does get
it if you want them to win uh but I I do
think he's good enough to like play play
this match easily you know they're in
the grand finals for a reason waiting
yeah I mean they did go through Upper
bracket exactly I was about to say
they're coming in the upper bracket like
they were able to stay up there they
knocked lgd here to be uh then
eventually knocked out by Gaming
Gladiators what's a big takeway from the
lgd team spirit match up that we had in
the upper bracket yesterday that you're
like oh maybe this is something that is
a weakness we haven't seen in team
spirit before well the biggest thing
that excites and worries me is that
there was a 70 minute game which we
really haven't seen gaming play so
either spirit will be able to force
gaming to play this really long game
which I would say favors them or you
know will gaming just destroy the
average game time for Spirit make it
really low and just kind of Crush three
games in a row hey that we kind of have
heard when Ace had his winners interview
that they're going to keep playing their
game maybe it's going to be that Tempo
but right now we do have to close out
this series we want to hear from one of
the lgd plays we have an exit interview
it's tsunami and why you
smile thank you very much yes I am
standing by with why you smile and Jin
will be helping me
translate um smile it's uh kind of
strange to think that you're now very
much a veteran and for a squad like this
with so many players that are kind of
new to an experience like this what was
it like guiding them through such a
high-intensity tournament here at the
international
um it's more of a it feels like a wake
up call to myself as well because just
watching these younger players seeing
that drive seeing the motivation it um
it kind of it's like a wake up call for
me it reminds me of what kind of me
mentality I should be having as well
that's wonderful to hear then also in
terms of maybe reigniting your your
competitive passion obviously here in
this venue even you must have some very
fond memories so was there any
experiences that you had with the fans
or just the being back in Seattle
Sensation that you're hoping to remember
as you leave this
[Music]
event for
um I don't really feel uh much of those
emotions at this very moment because uh
we just lot of series feeling pretty sad
right now however it it is very touching
to see so many fans so many Chinese fans
and international fans here at the arena
cheering for us I think one of the
biggest sense of loss I feel right now
is just not being able to get into the
grand finals not being able to hear them
cheer for us once
more well why I'm sure there's no doubt
in my mind that we will be cheering for
you no matter what happens in the future
shisha appreciate it sh and back to the
panel such a beautiful interview tunami
thank you so much and why Smile as well
there were a lot of fans every time lgd
was playing this crowd was louder than I
felt it could go and it just keeps
pushing itself more and more so why you
smile there's a lot of fans here and I'm
sure that they'll be cheering for you
maybe even later today if they see you
around you know they'll be having a lot
of fun but for now gaming Gladiators
they got a little bit over an hour reso
to reset themselves look towards the
Grand Final you were in a very similar
position not that long ago what did you
do with your owl what what do you think
they doing I mean to me it has been
really tough because the series that we
played before was like three three games
and it was like really like up and go
like you know you you don't really know
if you're going to win or not but for
for game in this time around like there
very confidently taking those two games
so they don't really I think they don't
really wasted allot of their energy so
they don't really need to do anything
other than just like you know prepare
themselves for taking this spirit and
like think about what kind of Heroes
they want to draft for the next
series yeah you don't want to like phase
yourself too much you still have another
game you can feel good but at some point
you have to just reset just all right
started the new game so let's play the
new game well look they're going to have
their time we're going to have some time
as well and to help us fill in the time
there's going to be some more content we
have a very exciting video that we're
going to get to watch right
now please this is not how Heroes act
you both think it's in your nature to
fight but your first and only answer
can't always be violence your sisters
violence is Never My First Choice my
first choice we know it's why you lose
Lena I'm just saying sometimes you got
to burn down if you want to win
except you don't just burn people or
things she starts emotional fires she
knows her stupid real fires can't touch
me are you kidding me emotional damage
doesn't even work on you it hurts my
feelings you don't have feelings seen
warmer eyes on a shark we should really
um and nobody's buying your cute little
smile by the way you look more like a
hell
bear I remember how great it felt when
mom and dad sent you to live in that
desert remember for something I didn't
do would anyone believe you be fair
riy let's
listen
Lena can we talk more about why you had
to leave
[Music]
home she had to leave home because she
burned home down nine times that's a lie
everything you say is a Lie the nth one
wasn't me Mom and Dad said it was my
last chance and I wasn't going to blow
it you're right
I was innocent and no one believed
me it's funny I was scared at first but
now it's my happiest
memory watching you
cry you
coldhearted
I am so sorry about her she's been
that way since you were born before you
came around I was enough
I see a lot of dysfunction walk through
that door believe me your co-workers are
all a mess but somehow you two you take
the agis and the
cheese the good
news there's still
hope you just have to be honest with
yourselves with each other maybe move
forward for a
change maybe you're right
Lena there is something I have never
told
you about house number
nine it was me
[Music]
[Applause]
I was the one who started the
fire and when they asked me who did it I
lied you got sent away because of
me
and
I I would do it again a
[Music]
heartbeat Alina shut
up
I
really respect
that you wait you
what that doesn't sound like
you okay maybe I don't respect it
but I'm
proud you solved a problem with
fire and
lies that's my
playbook you learn that from
me I didn't think you were that smart
that's not the lesson here you need to
work on your problems you can't just
commit arson that's
insane I I I mean it's it's not insane
right what what is saying anyway you
know what doc I think we're just about
out of
time so that's what happened with our
last counselor but I doubt we'll have a
problem with
you that's not a compliment what are you
writing
down say something
yeah you don't want to make my sister
mad
[Laughter]
[Music]
ler and Crystal Maiden definitely some
uh Twisted Sly love going on there I
would not want to be in that Council
seat at all dude I was laughing the
entire time it's like that nin house I
mean the highly flammable war was like I
was going to say that was my favorite
when it rolls past the
newspaper TNT but the highly flamable
water that's dous old like tf2 type
stuff man that's the the good humor that
I love valve for yeah it's the regular
thing to hold that thing in your house
right like at time yeah is that what
your house looks like yeah yeah to have
everything lying around fire in your
loud Dre you don't silly me I put it
elsewhere we're in the USA true that's
the difference being in Australia you
have to hide it you have to Stu it away
look speaking of being in the USA we're
enjoying ti2 here in the arena there's a
lot of fans still sitting around and
there's a lot of fans elsewhere around
the world so we're not just watching ti2
in the United States there's fans
everywhere sheep oh my God but none in
England we have no do players who whoa
whoa whoa whoa TSM will take offense to
that one no I'm just kidding uh yeah no
it's great see all the fans all around
the world enjoying it it's like the time
zones right it's like some of these
people are just going to be up at like
5:00 a.m. 4:00 a.m. just like yes we're
here for the DOTA we care we love it and
shout out to you guys I was going to say
I know a lot of my friends back home in
Australia they're all sitting in Discord
they're watching it together it's an
ungodly hour I think it's actually 4:00
a.m. for them so there's probably not
any uh places for them to watch it out
in town but they're at home I know
they're enjoying it and I'm sure a lot
of sea fans are doing the same as well
from the comfort of their home and
hopefully it's a long night for them I'm
I'm I'm hoping for a really long best of
five some fun games so if it's a late
night for you already I'm sorry about
that but I'm hoping for more we're all
hoping for that one isn't that so res I
mean TI finals is always where you stay
up till the very end and like you you
cheer and you get the energy from like
just watching purely it's just an insane
Journey yeah five games would be
phenomenal there's still a lot of time
before that grand finals you guys know
how else we're going to be filling in
the time H perhaps with film contest
okay that of Cosplay yeah a little bit
of Cosplay do you have a favorite hero
that you would like to be seeing on the
stage in
Cosplay okay someone said Primal Beast
me why did I even ask why did I even
look at you that was so
Sil invoker invoker Alchemist alchemist
that would be a pretty difficult one I
know something I know something you
can't spoil anything yeah I would want
to see a witch Dr one that's that's the
cosplay I would like to see you guys
like the monkey on the shoulder yeah but
an actual monkey I don't want it like
paper maade or anything like that I want
a real monkey hey we'll see if it's
going to happen we're going to see a lot
of costumes though the cosplay contest
is happening we got tsunami on the
stage that's right friends and there's a
very special thing happening on the
stage because if you notice I am flanked
by some cosplayers because we have a
tradition around here it's time for the
international 2023 cosplay competition
presented by Steel series are you guys
ready lovely lovely well I already have
some judges joining me so I would like
to take this opportunity to introduce
them I am joined by fairy fingers as a
crystal Maiden fairy fingers wave to the
crowd wave to the crowd and then how
long have you been cosplaying for I've
been cosplaying for 28 years
a wealth of experience and it shows with
this outfit as well as joined by me it's
anahe from Seattle cosplay where uh I I
suppose like how about uh how about we
just like
um I know right I totally agree I can't
wait for Grand finals also but I want to
do this cosplay competition first and
lastly it's abat cosplay joining me as a
Nature's prophet and this isn't your
first time here is it no I've been
competing on this stage before oo and
now you're ready to judge our
contestants well let's get started then
may I present styro girls as
Alchemists you may remember the name
styro girls from a few years ago because
in 2018 Vancouver the styro girls were
ogre Magi and here they are treating us
to an alchemist
that's our first contestant next up
we've got maab Baka as
Marcy now this Marcy took over 200 hours
to complete and she specifically added
all the bling to her costume to make it
really pop on stage and boy does it look
that way next
up we've got Sunray as anti Mage or way
specifically
so this anti- Mage is a really new skin
it's only 1 month old and she or
designed all the lights that are
programmed in C++ using ardua Arduino we
got the tech over here you know anti
Mage doesn't use magic but he does use
technology next up we've got Kronos
chick as
pugna now this pugna has these beautiful
vibrant colors and all of that was done
with
airbrushing and it pops on the stage for
sure moving on we've got flio as a
vengeful
spirit so this the wings on this costume
alone took 250 hours and it was all hand
dremeled feathers the intricacies are
amazing moving on we've got Tyrant as a
void spirit
his cos cosplay completed within the
month it is a really impressed first
ever cosplay shout out to the
anniversary set it looks incredible as
well as the poses next up we've got
chiun Neco as a skywrath
mage with almost 4 meter wingspan the
6in heel with CLA makes it look like
she's floating in the air almost come
sometimes uh looks a bit like a chicken
sometimes we get
the next up we've got ymr as drown
Ranger the drown Ranger took seven
months to complete using household items
her arrows are actually
Chopsticks that's right even you at home
can find things to cosplay with but it
takes a lot of hours to look at this
intricate after that we've got not in my
house as a phantom
assassin this cosplay took 130 hours of
work 30 hour of work is on the blade
alone and last but certainly not least
we've got Dawn as Crystal
[Music]
Maiden her staff is 3D printed out of
dual color filament that makes it look
like different in various
lightlings all right friends those are
our 10 finalists but we've got a handful
of a Awards to give out so let's start
off with the best technique is Crystal
Maiden
[Applause]
Dawn next up best
transformation could we get some eyes on
the skyre Mage chiun Neco
[Applause]
now we've got a thing called judges
Choice abcat what is judges Choice
exactly judge's Choice was the cosplay
that we were very impressed with that we
really liked the finishing on and that
just had great stage
presence well we can go ahead and hand
that to fivo on the vengeful spirit
Seattle could I get a little drum roll
going as we get ready for beston
[Music]
show the anticipations killing me it's
almost like a unstable concoction
because it's Alchemist the styro girls
what an amazing showcase this year
cosplayers we loved all of the
performances but we've got more
festivities to attend to I appreciate
all the help judges in the prejudging
and joining me up here but are you guys
ready for some short films maybe
absolutely thank you so much tsunami
incredible cosplays that we got to see
here today the community is so creative
and that that's why we love being DOTA
players but as impressive as the
cosplays are one of the most creative
moments that our community has are our
short film contest every single year and
today our top three are some of the best
that we've ever seen so to start things
off may I please present to you the
third place who was a second place
winner at TI 10 let's go on a journey
and see our third place contestant
finally get their prize as they travel
across all all the valve universes in
game
breakers on my way
where's the
C4 good
luck do you know who ate all
the pi up
that up
Where Have You Been middle Tower is
under ATT
[Music]
so many Fantastic references in that one
and a joy to watch what an incredible
journey thank you so much for your
submission but now it is time for our
second place winner the first place of
Tia this one is from Keller Max you guys
ever been in a game where they just keep
Fountain farming you and you can never
get out what do you say of course you
would say finish please
right
[Music]
dire's middle barass has
fallen the radi now
[Music]
God damn those are some big ass boys
those Mega creeps absolutely fantastic
and for the coveted number one slot a
three time winner in fact the winner of
last year's has come once again ladies
and Gentlemen please put your hands
together for four fun who will show you
what it's like to have some chemical
rage
oh
God
damn that's how every single carry
thinks that they feel in your games that
was a wonderful well thank you so much
to everyone that participated so many of
our community members submit short films
and every year they get better so please
if you didn't win this year try again
because we love watching them and they
are such a absolute little Joy all right
anyway there's one more video I think
you guys might want to see something I
forgot perhaps you might want to look at
[Music]
this we've all heard stories of children
running away to join the
circus not in my experience you can't
drag them
away besides you be astonish the length
people go to get a child back people
Miss children
[Music]
but your average run-of-the-mill hero
they're easy to catch easy the
train plus they're all ego Maniacs so
they're natural
[Applause]
performers why not capture Heroes
[Music]
the ring Master coming to you soon you
guys ready for a new
hero I'm left here thinking in honor of
North America of course they would add a
hero for a
circus it only represent has to be
representative of our entire region my
friend you know the question that's in
everyone's mind what kind of hero is it
we got a support we got an offline we
got a mid we got a carry what's
happening uh it looked like it has some
kind of catch so I would say like a
support like a position
for okay okay traps uh the DOTA
Community kind of has a troubled history
with Heroes that make traps you uh you
miss old techies at all uh not at all I
hate old T yeah I really hate
old how about is it public Master what
was that did they take over Heroes that
was sick as hell what are you feel
you're playing a literal game right now
that's this guy's playing DOTA
underlords what the hell what do you
think about that hero reveal what the
hero you were playing underlords do you
even see it yeah they under Lords okay
great thank you what do you guys think
about the new hero
[Music]
[Applause]
look thank you that looks hype as oh
good lore baby the circus is Canon it's
Canon thank you tsunami what is with you
and the lore slacks we you going to do
another L gasm for this hero ring Master
l gasm no self advertisement on the
stream thank you very much for
watching very generous of you all right
all right we can Revel in that but we
got a grand finals to get to we've got a
little bit of time for it
what you think of that lower bracket
final my friend uh it's going to be
amazing but I hope Quinn doesn't
win Boo this man
listen he's trying to improve his entire
image right now all right we know we all
had troubled past do you not believe in
second chances uh it's been a while and
his Persona has been the same so I don't
know if he's going to recover from the
mentality or not
but what's on your mind friend Quinn
will
win yay you think being a TI winner will
change someone's personality for the
better or for the
worse um
better I mean you can talk to S4 after
that it doesn't get much better than
that who are your uh expectations as we
look forward to this Grand Final just a
good final I don't care who wins I just
want good
[Applause]
DOTA who doesn't want some good DOTA but
before we get to the Grand finals we
have a little bit of another treat for
you guys obviously in the grand finals
you get some Champions let me show you
some Champions on the
floor thank you so much tsunami the
enjoyment the content never stops and I
have one of the most decorated panels I
think I've ever seen in my
eyes we're just going to enjoy the
cheers for a while jerx you're joining
us OE FIA dendi you guys all have one
massive thing in common you guys have
won a TI two TI in some cases maybe
different ways too and uh there's 10
players sitting at the back right now
they're about to come on stage they're
about to have their grand final and
hopefully win a TI whichever team it is
I want to start all the way down the end
with dendi you were the beginning of
this you won your ti so many years ago
did you expect ti2 to happen to be in
Seattle to have a crowd like this and
the history and the Legacy that it would
create oh of course not like it's hard
to expect something like this but yeah
back in my days it was a long time ago
and different stories were around
overall I love it like STI is great uh
competition is super high level watching
those teams is amazing good feelings do
you think you'd have nerves if you were
going into this Grand Final either as
gaming Gladiators or team spirit with
the crowd no nerves at all come on look
at this what kind of nerves can it be no
way everyone is cheerful so it's easy
peasy for sure JX we'll move up here
because two-time TI winner Teen Spirit
going into the grand finals they could
be joining you in the ranks of a
two-time TI winner does you like I don't
want to share that title with anyone or
are you hoping that another team is able
to do it too I think there's some
anxiety about it but uh in the end of
the day I feel like we're all cheering
for the best DOTA and uh if that happens
here then doesn't really matter it
doesn't matter at the end of the day
were you more nervous the second time
round when heading into the grand finals
you're like no one else has done this no
one's won two or was it more we've been
here before and we've done it we can win
a grand finals uh I think the emotion
that I had the most is I think we kind
of ran out of the game so that was
frustrating I would say because the
first time we just went through the open
qualifiers all the way and uh I think as
a player you really cherish these
moments when you really get to play on
the highest competitive uh environment
and uh yeah maybe frustrated oh that's
an interesting emotion to feel but how
you've been uh in two grand finals as
well one as a coach one as a player is
it hard being a coach seeing the grand
finals like what would silent and see
why be feeling out there seeing their
five players about to walk on I think as
a coach at this point you're mostly just
proud of what your players have done
what they've come through you've watched
them work hard for so long I think
mostly what you want is for them to be
able to enjoy the moment the best do is
played when you're having
fun and FIA you shared your win with OE
do you want to any any stories any
feelings that you had cuz you're a very
stoic man I think any I think any like
uh finals experience is going to be
different for everyone right but the
when I went into it most I was thinking
there's always going to be nerves of
course but what I always told myself
going into it is just like as long as I
choke less than the other team or I'm
less nervous than the other team that's
good enough you know what I mean cuz
every single time you're going to be a
little bit nervous what was the main
feeling then jerx you were saying
frustrated was that the second time
round or the first time you were saying
was uh that was the second time so just
the lack of games I feel like when it
goes really fast then you don't really
get to prove yourself as to the same
level I don't know I think that's fair
that's a very valid thing to be able to
say yeah of course I'm not that's that's
how I felt so the first win meant just a
little bit more even though both yeah
absolutely yeah interesting what was
your main feeling
OE for for TI 11 either one you can tell
me I mean I think ti5 is definitely more
nervous like as a player than a coach I
think um it's just so much happening you
feel the vibration of the crowd you
don't really know what's going on I
hadn't really experienced anything like
that before for TI 11 was a lot more
calm we worked a lot on like controlling
our emotions to make sure that we were
in the best performance shape I think it
honestly sort of similar to JX like we
wanted to show off our DOTA and I mean
TI 11 maybe similar to ti9 not the best
for that yeah may I don't know I can't
really speak for you but uh for my
that's my only experience yeah mhm what
advice would you give to those 10
players out there right now what is
something that you wish you had have
heard when you were in the tunnels when
you were building up to walk out when
you know you either had the the lower
bracket 1 hour wait or when you were
coming in from the upper bracket if you
want to start dendy sure uh simple
advice play the best daughter of your
life I think this a sort of advice the
crowd would give as well I mean it's
going to be similar for me like you just
don't get this opportunity very often
who knows the next time you'll be in
this position this is like going to be
your opportunity to potentially win a TI
in spirit's case win another TI against
Laurel's first cherish it and take
advantage of this moment and do the best
you possibly can
mhm yeah no same for me I think just
make sure that like the main thing you
have here is making these memories I
think that's the most important thing no
matter what happens win or lose you want
to be proud of what you've accomplished
in
Dota uh personally for me I feel there's
a when the nerves really get to you you
start to really look outside but I think
if you really tune into yourself and
give opportunities to those thoughts of
like okay we have this crazy idea we
don't really feel like pulling it here
in the finals but I I think if you
commit to that I think that goes very
well mhm how much internal pressure did
you guys place on yourself and who was
trying to help you pull that out of you
that you weren't getting too caught up
in your head is that for me yeah all of
you guys um Johan was the very big part
of our energy mhm our flower uh uh I
definitely felt that uh I was very
supported in the team uh and if if that
wasn't the case I don't think I would
have enjoyed as much
I think honestly during T 5 It Was Fear
like he was always a solid rock you
could I feel like fear actually has a
DOTA superpower like he makes all his
teammates feel super comfortable and
able to play at their best cuz he's so
reliable and at TI 11 it was supposed to
be me I think but just I don't know just
a little bit of all of you it was more
chill you know yeah I mean I say that
about fear for for panels as well he
definitely calms the nerves for all of
us well I guess for me then I kind of
felt like on E there it was an unspoken
rule that everyone kind of just had to
play their part you know and just be
confident in what we're doing and just
believe and I didn't really feel like
anyone looked up to anyone personally
speaking and I thought we just like were
just going at it together and we all
knew what we needed to do and just had
to get it done uh I had an amazing team
and I was very unconfident coming to the
ti actually but they all cheered me up
through the entire tournament and coming
to the Grand finals I had the feeling we
cannot lose that's the feeling I got
it's very weird I don't know if I would
ever repeat okay when was the shift for
each of you then that you felt you
cannot lose this at what point in the
tournament if you were coming in nervous
what point was that changing for me it's
if Curtis ever got techies or
nagu I just knew we couldn't lose you
know he was a guaranteed win so yours is
in the draft all right I see I see I
mean we we were so confident that uh we
even pick like in one of the games we
picked P just because we wanted to have
some fun you know like to play it yeah
so it was kind of crazy back in the days
yeah honestly I think as soon as like
Bobba found out they don't play lash
rack that too yeah yeah and S was like
okay free win that was that was good uh
I didn't really think if we going to win
or lose I really just played I don't
know I I just had a lot of fun myself uh
I didn't really get to think that if
we're going to win or lose I didn't yeah
do you guys want to show off your rings
by the way I don't know if everyone in
the audience has seen these before but I
mean you got two J so we'll start with
you we we'll show off both of yours do
you wear it often what was the feeling
when you picked it up as well because
there's going to be five players and a
coach getting to pick up theirs in uh
you know after this one I think they're
getting Dusty most of the
time and uh I I I guess I don't really
have a place to show them except this
yeah you come to TI and you're like oh
hey guys check out the Rings by the way
uh I don't I don't really like leave
offer in I wish I could do that but I I
don't really I don't seem to do that
very well all right then you guys uh
want to quick answer because I know
there's more questions circulating
around the arena uh no I don't leave
home without it yeah I thought so yeah
I've seen you all the time Fe he's
polishing it in the back room in the
Green Room he's just making sure that
that is shiny as we got slack in the
crowd we wanted to ask some more
questions out there there's going to be
some fan questions hey slack give give
us the first one yes yes I've spent a
lot of time finding someone with a real
question that was not trolling thank you
one person in this entire area but we
did get a what was your name sahim all
right fantastic what would you like to
ask these folks for all our Aron Heralds
and Crusaders out here uh what does it
take to be a TI Champion what does it
take TI Champions to be a TI Champion
besides just being one of these Aron
haral Crusader scrubs no offense to 90%
of the audience do you want to go first
JX because you've had to do it twice in
two very different ways a lot of
emotional damage in your public
matchmaking
but that's the solid advice to be a TI
Champion all right all right I don't
think you can make the step from being
archon Herald to TI Champion that can be
your dream your aspirations but I think
the only advice I can give is just play
a lot of DOTA just keep playing and
eventually you'll play with better
players and then you'll play with pros
and then from there you'll get on teams
and then it's a slow process but it will
happen yeah I you were saying the other
day that it's a it's a lot of luck a lot
of things kind of falling into place for
you yeah I think it's a lot of luck
honestly but I think it's you have to
like put yourself in a position to get
lucky think if as Fe said like if you
just keep grinding at it like that's
going to open the opportunities for you
do you want to add anything else to oh
yeah I completely agree with to that you
need to love the game and uh try to not
get frustrated in your Pub games which
is not as simple wish somebody told me
that before yeah then maybe not so much
emotional damage would have occurred
before JX here tsunami is also out there
he is another fan with another
question that's right uh my friend
introduce yourself uh my name is Seth
and you got a question for one of our
panelists of course for fear so my
friends got inspired to play Dota 2
because the North American
representation so how does it feel fear
to be the North American representative
of Dota 2 free to play I mean you were
the main guy for us how does that feel I
just feel honored to give him the
opportunity to like be represented in
free to play like they could have chose
a lot of different people they chose me
I just love DOTA overall and I'm just
very fortunate I feel blessed that I was
just given this opportunity and I just
will run with it for as long as I can
cuz I just love DOTA so I'm just happy
to be
here think we're going to giving you a
big round of applause that that's also
made me think about another question is
at the end of uh the grand finals I'm
sure you guys had a lot of elation a lot
of Joy maybe even relief but when did it
really set in where were you like oh I
wish I had to spent more time in the
moment was it a couple months after or
it still really hasn't every time you
come back to TI you're you're taking it
back to what has happened in your your
past in your history uh I think uh
thinking years back I feel like now it's
maybe coming more than before uh
personally after the especially the
first TI I think it took me like two
weeks to even understand what happened
mhm uh because I was so much in the
moment and I guess that kind of carried
over that you're just not really
thinking what had
happened yeah honestly I think the same
like when you're there like there's just
lights everywhere there's fireworks
you're just like the confetti coming
down you're like oh I guess we lifted
this now but I think as soon as you have
some time and you think about like these
are the memories you'll never forget
like you always remember these moments
oh that's so sweet yeah it took a very
long time for me as well like there's a
lot of people cheering for you you get
you win there's confetti you talk about
you get back home and I'm like all I've
been doing is playing DOTA for years and
years so what did I do when I got back
home I just queued it up and just played
more DOTA so it just felt like nothing
happened I was just back on it and later
onal damage once you start playing less
DOTA you're not playing as competitive
anymore then you really look back and
how special these moments really are um
I had a year for like a week I think and
I was looking in the sky and like oh my
God so good like that happened a lot of
times through that week and trying to uh
work through the information in my head
we actually won TI wow and yeah after a
week get back to normal and just keep
green going such a surreal feeling that
sometimes it's like uh it never really
will set in but we're going to keep
asking some more questions we got slack
out there another fan another question
let's hear what it
is thank you thank you now I did have a
question by the way I I managed to catch
up with a guy who has a or sign earlier
and I said what the hell is that and he
said quote I don't know I just think
it's
funny so thanks a lot all day this guy
about that's a goddamn mad man anyway uh
a real question what is your name Dylan
Dylan what do you have for these Legends
of Dota 2 Legends of Dota 2 what advice
would you give to the teams that have
been vanquished from ti do you disband
do you reform how do you how do you move
forward as an org yeah good luck with
this one owie
me yeah I mean I guess it's it's a tough
question even when you do win TI what
you do with uh the roster after that
[Laughter]
one I don't know I think honestly if you
attend a TI you wash a final you was and
win and it doesn't motivate you then
maybe you take a break but for I think
for like 99% of DOTA players they wash
it and like this is the fire that burns
this is what keeps you going through the
emotional damage and Trauma so yeah just
keep going it's being a spectator at an
event that you were a part of you wanted
to win you had that drive motivation and
passion but you just couldn't get there
in the end then you're not in your head
yeah it's very tough sometimes but it's
good to live in a moment and enjoy
because uh this is also great experience
to watch it from crowd and have a lot of
fun for sure do you want to add F JX
advice for teams that have gotten
knocked out yeah you're pretty normally
brutally honest sure I mean for a lot of
the teams that have got knocked out
they're they're still young like I
didn't even win until I was 27 so just
keep at it keep grinding like it's good
to feel sad in my opinion it's good to
feel that's motivation right so as long
as you don't give up and you still have
the passion as long as you think you can
still win and just don't give up
entirely that's good enough did you know
you're not the oldest uh TI play winner
anymore I know snaking is by a few
months by a few months were you
devastated when you heard the news I
mean he's taking everything from me
that's all I had left that was it that's
the only thing that was keeping you
going was being the oldest TI winner uh
look I'm going to move on to another
question I do know tsunami has one out
there so let's quickly hear what it is
that's right my friend uh introduce
yourself yeah my name is abishek and um
I've been playing uh daa for around 5
years yeah and you have some specific
fond memories from JX specifically uh
what were you hoping to ask him I have
been like astonished with the tiny l in
the ti it's so good and I just wanted to
know like what's your reaction when
Sam uh did the tiny lens to the AR in
the base and um yeah sorry I couldn't
hear the question yeah tsunami can you
please repeat it whenever uh you know
obviously you're very famous for some
tiny Airlines plays JX you're tiny in
general uh does it ever warm your heart
a little to see that play be pulled off
on a high State stage such as previous
TI when maybe SU to RZ or something yeah
sure uh make a trend you
know I'm going to have to startop
getting all the clips and then just put
# JX tiny aines next to it instead I'm
happy to see it anytime
so I love it look we get ning the grand
finals now okay we're only a couple
minutes away so I want to go back to the
teams that we want to focus on team
spirit gaming Gladiators here fear and
Jer this is mainly for you two because
they're such similar things and actually
you as well OE because that ti5 win for
you both both it was you in the upper
bracket you came to that lower bracket
and one day you had to go lower bracket
into Grand finals and you won it so your
advice but gaming Gladiators right now
what would it be how do you contain
these emotions and how do you persevere
through a potential best of
five I guess I'll start I suppose for so
we got knocked down by cedc and went
into the lower bracket we won that match
two I believe and then we went in I
think we just sure we lost to the team
beforehand but we knew we were better we
just had to make a couple adjustments
and if we just made those adjustments we
knew we had to take to win so it was
just confidence really and good
preparation do have anything else you
want to add on to into that one IE no
not really I think that sounds right
like you just go in I think Gladiators
they had a long run this TI you know
they got they start lower back after
losing to Talent they've come all this
way I think it's time like you put all
this work in you got all this experience
in the tournament they've grown a lot if
they feel confident they can just
execute that they should feel really
good about their Series so there weren't
actually that many nerves for you when
you were about to walk out after even
having played a series earlier do you
think the earlier series actually helped
you and could help gaming Gladiators I
thought it was good to play honestly
like you're all warmed up you have the
momentum going I feel like as long as
it's not like some I don't know like two
80 minute games that you just played
it's going to be really good for you
that's true where it's more as the the
40 minutes that we just previously saw
it's a bit better yeah I like it this is
where I say like every finals is going
to be different for everyone cuz we had
a unique situation where we scrim seedak
a lot we always beat them we lost them
that one time and then we had the right
strategy we had this one idea that we
went into and it worked and from there
it just felt easy okay and my one for
you JX is around team spirit winning it
a second time I I already asked you how
you felt there was that little bit of
frustration when you went through the
upper bracket so do you think that drive
right now is going to be higher than it
was in any other day to be able to win
DOTA right now I would imagine it's
actually harder to have Drive night now
uh and I think it's because the first
time it just feels so much more and I I
think if they can really tune into what
they felt back then and try to like
channel that same kind of environment as
a team I think that's what you're
looking for here just put it out of your
mind just think this is a redo of TI 10
if your team
spirit uh yeah yeah yeah just repeat
that's pretty much it vendy for you as
well uh I like that you're very aware of
everything else that's going around you
of this environment of the Arena of the
crowd I know that you love it I know
that they love you so for gaming
Gladiators and Teen Spirit again I ask
you what would you want to hear if you
were back there if you were going to be
in front of this massive Arena In This
Crowd knowing everyone was watching uh I
think sticking to your game plan
sticking to your confidence uh to your
comfort like just give it all in your
games so I don't think I need to hear
much um yeah I'm pretty sure we guys
know very stuff too what we're going to
do we're pretty focused on what it's
coming up to yeah look it's building up
uh I want to show the Rings again for
you guys I want to thank you guys for
coming on it was so invaluable to have
you all talking about I like it it is a
bit cringe but it happens we go to our
grand finals we're building it up our
teams gaming Gladiators and team spirit
let's enjoy the grand finals
[Applause]
look at all that fresh
meat sorry I got carried away okay who's
that handsome devil trick question it's
me I'm that handsome
devil but I want to remind you of one
[Music]
thing there are many Earths but only one
earthshaker
okay I got to stop screwing around get
to work
okay welcome DOTA fans from around the
house around the town around the block
and around the
world to the international Grand
[Applause]
finals this is the ultimate Proving
Ground and together we bear
witness as the agis of
Champions hangs in the
balance please welcome to the stage our
worthy contenders battling all the way
through the lower
bracket
gaming gladiators
[Music]
[Applause]
please
welcome
[Applause]
D CER
Quin poo
[Applause]
and
Ace give it up one more time for game in
gladiators
[Applause]
and continuing their March through the
upper
bracket
team
[Applause]
[Music]
spirit yapo
L there is nothing that stop thisor
[Music]
and
collapse one more time sound off for
team spirit
oh
no there is that stop
this two teams remain
standing only one can claim
immortality who will emerge
Victorious the final
battle
begins the final Proving Ground where 16
teams once
stood all but two have
fallen both have outlasted the finest
adversaries the world could
offer BuyBacks now from liquid side Mega
Creeps in their favor and now it's a
five versus three Toronto Tokyo into the
G and with that b
boom as your right take them down bit by
bit building by building both have fans
still eager for one more reason to
cheer one will join a Pantheon of
greatness the other can hope for better
luck next year
the final showdown for the AIS is upon
us two teams remain
standing only one can seize
immortality who will emerge Victorious
the
battle begins
[Music]
[Applause]
the grand finals of the international
2023 just moments away from happening
here in the climate pledge Arena and I
am so ready for this best of five to
together with my panel I'm joined by
lacost by tlf by eie and I got to say it
eie he did it again ti10 he did it we
see it right now as well yoro has
sacrificed his hair for the DOTA Gods D
this second I saw him walk out I got
chills he shaved his head he sacrificed
his hair that is how he won TI 10 he
started the trend of going bald for TI
and he he came to win today I would be
worried if iway gaming Gladiators other
have tried to copy him others have tried
to go Bard to win a TI they failed but
this morning when I was leaving the
hotel I saw him and I just looked I was
like B and he just gave me that cheeky
little look and I was like oh this is a
guy who wants to win this TI oh and they
have done it before sight CH of course
with naar on the Middle Lane but they're
looking so good their opponents look
fantastic as well though the whole year
Laos gaming Gladiators they've had a
fantastic one absolutely this is the
team that got the top 12 in the previous
year something was missing two missing
pieces were Quinn and SE Wier coach we
think I think we got to give them huge
credit for what they managed to do with
the team because they managed to win
three Majors all upper bracket runs and
suddenly they're in the lower bracket
and we had an interview yesterday with
celer who talked about the importance of
the serious this serious the seating
match against ton how much they learned
from it and ever since that they're just
speeding things up this is the team that
can beat you 19 minutes we saw Flawless
performance yesterday against a ray they
were playing Turbo mode pretty much yeah
they really really were and we must not
forget a ground finals like these it is
not a crowning of a tournament not even
of the year it is a crown of a career
and we have seen most of these faces
lift the ages already t for L will be
the first time but they have tried so
many times they have and for La at least
last year he played on b boom he came
last place and now this time around he's
in the grand finals of course surrounded
by 4 Titi winners as well if they are to
lift this agis first time F second
attempt two time winners potentially for
the other four players it is incredibly
storyline of course but posco he's
attempted this eight times already sure
he's lifted the AIS once but Ace as well
he's attempted eight times but yet to
lift the agis can he do it himself this
time and Quinn let's not forget to talk
about Quinn seven attempts five TI
attempts everyone thought that Quinn you
know was just hanging around the na DOTA
scene wasn't going to make it very far
but he joined gaming Gladiators
something clicked and he proved to the
world the kind of caliber of player he
is he is world class he has been
destroying everyone in his way and he's
here for the Aegis lift he is here for
it we'll see which team will come out
Victorious of course on one side we have
a chance of four fresh two time
Champions on the side of team spirit but
gaming Gladiators they could be having
two crowning achievements in their
finals if they were to lift the ages
first one coming all the way starting
off in the lower brackety yeah I think
so ti9 liquid they got all the way to
the finals but weren't able to win it
but if gaming Gladiators are to win this
TI it'll be the first time a team starts
in the lower bracket and lifts the ages
that's six lower bracket games that they
have to win back time and time again and
not drop a single one and they could do
it that that's that's an incredible and
then also the fact they won three Majors
like so many things going their way yeah
I think L we've heard a lot about the
majors and they all went through the
upper bracket and people like well I
wonder how they fair in the lower
bracket you know everything's different
over there there's so much more pressure
but this team they Thrive under it
absolutely this is the team that powered
up the most I would say throughout the
whole tournament because this team is
not really familiar with the lower
bracket especially when it comes down to
the DPC and the tournament so really
glad that they're showing what they're
really made up they're going to their
own like how they started to dominate
the year with these like uh strength
Heroes these Aura buyers grouping
grouping up S5 and just complete
domination from start to finish I think
coming into this because they just
played two games I think they have
advantage and let's not forget gaming
Gladiators because of their dominance
this year they are the team that shaped
The Meta they are the team that got the
meta nerfed and changed to the way that
it is today so when the initial patch
happened they were the team that was hit
the hardest by it and it took them so
long to adjust everyone thought that
okay it's the ti curse if you're
dominant the entire year there's no way
you win there's no way you get this far
but they said what meta We Are The Meta
and they prove to everybody that they're
not just a patch team strong they're a
strong team and they're here to compete
and they have played the most games out
of everybody here going through the
lower bracket so it's not like they're
saving strats everybody knows what's
coming the question is how are you going
to answer that if you're team spirit I
hope they have something something very
special cooked up for this and this
series there's a little bit of a change
compared to all the series we saw before
it's a best of five and normally you've
got one team coming in thinking oh maybe
they don't have a lot of experience with
best of fives and actually taking them
in the end but both of these teams T
have shown that the adaptation that is
needed in a series like this they got it
yeah and not only they have the
adaptation but kind of play Styles
mirror as well like the spirit they're a
team that have been behind quite a lot
to come back into their games and then
for game of Gladiators you mentioned
that they played the most games 24 games
their average win time is 36 minutes
that's 10 minutes quicker than team
spirit so it really feels like this
whole series will be can Spirit survive
the onslaught of gaming can they find
those moments of collapse Brilliance to
get back into their games and then close
out like this is just two so different
teams it's like a beautiful finals two
different styles because gaming gladers
they've been so dominating and everybody
was focused on them starting from like
the laning stage one of the best you
know everybody was also talking about
the bed boom as a strong laning stage
team but team spirit when it comes down
to the late game decision making the way
they're making their plays they're just
topnotch I I think when it comes down to
super late game team spirit is the best
team in the world they got to get there
first though a lot of teams have failed
to do so against gaming Gladiators I
think that one thing that I've noticed
over the last few days is that there has
been a lot of talk about the offlaners
Fe I feel like we're seeing them be put
in the role to be the star player for
their squad yeah I mean when you look at
uh gaming Gladiators offliner Ace he is
the rock of this team he is their stable
player he is the one that they can
depend on the one that they build around
he's the player that enables Daio to
play in the hyper aggressive sometimes
very risky sometimes very dangerous way
that he plays but he makes it work
because their offlane the offlane of
tofu plus Ace is so strong they're
dominant he picks Heroes that rallies
his team into the game and he never
disappoints I've hardly ever seen Ace
have a bad game whereas collaps he also
fits that role in a similar way where he
is the playmaker of this team and him
and mea have been playing together for
as long as tofu and Ace have but the
special thing to me about collapse is
regardless of what situation you put him
in even if he has a bad net worth lead
even if his Lane goes poorly he finds
the initiation I mean I think collapse
is the best initiator DOTA two has ever
seen yeah collapse has been showing
fantastic work he he brought the Magnus
out again I think that's it must be it's
it's at this point it's a mental story
for the Magnus to be played by collapse
yeah I mean we're probably going to see
collapse at least once in this finals I
want to see at least one ax in this
finals um Mars the is it unpicked still
yeah it's pretty it's unpicked but it
has been banned a couple times if we get
to see that as well but there's so many
Specialties and I think that e
mentioning is beautiful it's like
collaps is the initiator he's the one
that is the one that always needs to
start the fight but Ace he plays quite
different in his offlane style where he
wants people to group around him so he's
not starting the fight through literally
initiating he just more like I'm going
to be in the position where I'll forc
the fight and that kind of differences
could be something that they try to
exploit between the two off laners in
this series and in this series we're
going to see gaming Gladiators go up
against team spirit and that means that
throughout this entire series we want to
we want to learn more and more about all
10 players and their coaches on stage
and we're going to start right now by
learning a little bit more about team
[Music]
spirit I think team spirit probably has
the best understanding of how to win a
game from any point
they prove again and again that they can
they can be behind for 20 minutes 30
minutes and then they can just like
really sit and wait and be patient and
all of a sudden they hit their timing or
they see an angle to to kind of to kind
of turn the game around and they do it
what I might the most about team spirit
is their team fight execution like when
it comes to little skirmishes late game
fights playing around Ops and vision
they really excel at that and for some
reason when they are uh High state
they really know how to perform now K
shows up finds immediately onto him yo
dies but the it's almost enough it is
and I think against them you can't
really afford to be salty uh because
anytime you make a mistake against them
I think they they punish you severely uh
and I also think individually they're
amazing I think yor is you know he's up
there with with the best of him uh he's
he's so consistent and yeah always
always delivers and I think they're
Supporting Cast uh the four rest of them
combin really well to to make space for
him and enable him and yeah they're just
a very well jelled uh kind of
[Music]
team team spirit versus gaming
Gladiators Grand and
Finals game
[Applause]
one it's big brain time everybody
Welcome to the draft panel for the grand
finals you heard AI you heard dendy you
heard fear earlier talk about you know
previous experience with ti finals now
it's time to get into the nitty-gritty
of this one you guys you've been there
before you know what the stakes are you
know what to do so let's get going um
these two teams have had very different
styles as was pointed out by the panel
going into this uh this Grand finals
what are you guys looking for who's
going to throw the first curve ball it's
a good question I think the one thing
that you do really have to look out for
is going to be the Magnus right it's
collabs Magnus he only just showed it
yesterday his first time playing it and
this is what they won TI 10 off this is
something you've got to be afraid of do
you have the confidence if you're gaming
gliders to leave in the pool that's what
I'm mainly looking for in this series uh
I'm I'm looking at how both Styles going
to co and uh you know meet each other in
terms of like uh gaming GL where
apply a lot of pressure on all stages of
game especially starting from early we
have very strong Lanes very Tempo drafts
and as pel said like team spirit we have
longer games when we win so I'm curious
if we come up with some ideas and plan
how to stop it how we're going to deal
with man collapse apparently On
LAN
yeah yeah I think uh team spirit they
have a lot of info on gaming gliders
they watch so many other the games they
have a lot of data there I think
honestly going into the best of you have
a lot of games you have some room for
not experimentation but to test your
limits I think they should sort of try
to pick a gaming glider strategy that
they want to play against where the an
Chen pangier necro and they should try
to break that early in the bestel 5 I
think that's what gives them the best
shot of like sort of getting a draft
advantage in the series it sounds like a
lot of the heroes you're talking about
overlap with are healing based ancient
apparation still in the pool is that a
potential overall first pick for team
spirit do you think that's a an angle to
try to to Target what gaming gliders
have been running I would really like
like the a I think MOS is actually the
first player to start playing a I think
he was playing a bit before R and pubs
and they even ran a couple official they
actually go with the Weaver which I mean
it's a bit flexible but honestly I'm a
bit surprised I thought this Weaver it's
a bit weaker into sort of gaming gladi
Ball but what it can do is it can break
down the laning stage a lot if you get
ahead of these ball lineups into Lanes
often times they can't group up in this
way that they want to yeah the way I
look at this Weaver a little bit is team
Spirits they're playing against gaming
gladi right and what I've noticed a lot
from gaming gladers right now is you
want Dau on the CK or Weaver so they ban
the CK they B they take the Weaver away
and datu's he's really good but he's
really good at playing these aggressive
stle carries that's mainly because we
see Ace playing a little bit greedy too
right so drao can play a little bit
faster so I think this is very targeted
to just take it away from gaming
gladers yeah both teams have uh very
similar like three course idea which all
threee cor is getting big but compared
for example to gaming the ru is doing
more space creating stuff and in team
Spirits it's Soo so it's a little bit
different for both teams so it's very
interesting that team spirit is stealing
this Weaver away like from Gladiators
and yoro played an amazing Weaver like a
few days ago like it was very very
strong I think we might be seeing a Toro
on Weaver youan on here as like
bloodseeker I think the support Weaver
like I mean you care about rupture but
then you're just rupturing a support I
think you would only ban this type of
hero if you want to play the Weaver on
core T was also getting like his 89th
Mor game of the tourament so I think
that's like gaming gladers they should
actually feel really comfortable right
now with this opening I guess another
thing about the bloodseeker band is that
it kind of feeds into gaming glider's
General approach to the game in terms of
pace right this is a very aggressive
carry that wants to fight and bring that
pressure early uh it doesn't mind diving
Towers which I would say game gliders
have done more than any team in this
tournament so it's very clear here that
the teams are targeting different
players you pointed out you're Banning
carries when you're Spirit here and
you're stealing one away whereas as as
Denny was talking about laurl is playing
more of the aggressive style for for
team spirit do you think gaming
Gladiators would be wise to try to match
that idea so to speak by targeting LL as
much as Spirit are targeting um Doro
here I think uh the best idea would be
to pick extremely strong laner for Queen
which usually Gaming Goat is do in every
game and it working perfectly because
Queen is one of the best laners out
there for sure without D so I think this
this is a part of a uh plan which should
be to look down a little bit on W so he
doesn't have a good game yeah I think if
they go with that plan they can probably
look for the enchantress here I'm
honestly surprised that they're giving
it to Gladiators on second phase I think
both en and Chen are two Heroes that if
you have the winning mid you can
snowball a match up really hard yeah
it's one of the best heroes to rotate
for 5 minutes seon create insane amount
of pressure and we saw how gaming lators
to taking Towers from their enemies like
if you look almost every game like
minute 10 12 there is no tier one Towers
on all three lanes so it's crazy yeah
yeah I think just going into the series
in general gaming gladers they like tofu
playing this Mor because gives Ace a
good game they can get the enchanters
you mentioned that way they can Snowball
the game it's very clear how G wants to
play they're going to want to play fast
if you be greedy they want to punish it
right away and team they seem a bit more
flexible on what they want to do in
their draft and they kind of want to
just take strategy away and they're
versatile enough to do it this is a
quite the curveball right picking hango
in this slot is very early on in the
draft uh as much as I'm sure all the
meme enjoyers out there are happy to see
Quinn play the Pango for the nth time
this tournament um you're effectively
offering team spirit the possibility of
truly counterpicking mid here we've seen
uh Laurel and a hero such as Dazzle
destroy mid melee Heroes is that a good
match up against Pango or is he one of
the heroes that can kind of float that
lane uh it's pretty good Daz is
destroying almost every M Hero on Lane
but I don't think that team spirit want
to go for that puff because that will uh
switch them from the more of a comfort
strategy even F I'm pretty sure we can
uh make it but uh yeah like we putting
water in a situation where uh I think we
will need to decide with more limited
like hero pool against this Pango
because you want to punish this hero but
at the same time uh what kind of Heroes
left here to punish it from uh comfort
zone yeah it's definitely a little bit
different cuz like if I'm Weaver in this
situation I don't find Pango to be an
issue for me right like you can get away
should Pango for sure yeah yeah and then
now you get the tree to lock down the
Pango and the these earlier fights and
also you get a counter pick in the
lightning stage so it's already not a
good Pango game by any means but they're
just showing that Quinn is just super
confident on this hero and that's about
it for me on this pick okay here I can
talk a lot or I can just be quiet I I
played around 80 games last month of PK
and I enjoy this hero a lot and I really
like how L played even though he have a
bit different uh interesting ideas on it
like it's uh he's wishing to physical
car and it's actually pretty good answer
to Pango because for p you cannot win
your lane but if you do 50/50 you're
very happy and Pango one of those Heroes
that you can do actually 50/50 nowadays
so I believe it's great answer uh in
addition to uh against Pango against m
is tricky
but honestly I'm a bit worried for the
lane I feel like quid has played this
matchup like every single Pub since he
picks Pango every single game but I
think Puck he has like Zero armor right
once you get level three angle you start
spamming him I think it's a very very SC
dependent match up and team spirit stat
what I'm looking for at from them is I
think they watched the liquid series
that gliders played and that's the
series where gliders look the most
vulnerable and liquid strategy coming
into that was picking as strong a safe
Lane as you can so that's why they pick
the trient this Weaver might be carry
I'm not too sure the match up against L
at all but I assume it's fine for Weaver
L is sort of a scary laner but I'm not
too sure if like Puck fits into that
that well because if you're shutting
down the safe Lane
like I don't know like I'm not the
biggest fan of the puck hero I think he
sort of lacks some damage and I feel
like he's a hero that can actually get
run over on Mid uh absolutely what can
happen this hero cannot is not very
effective into helping Sidelines so you
really need to make sure your Sidelines
are extremely strong because he's just
you know getting bigger himself and
actually Puck is uh getting strong now
more late game so um I also agree with
uh it's kind of like might be a problem
to stop gaming Gladiators like fresh
because it's not a hero with stopping
pressure for sure so for a lot of teams
I feel like this L TR could be
considered a flex here between caran off
Lane I don't think we've seen Doro play
lre this tournament at all right no
saying that so does that mean what angle
could team spirit take here are you
trying to now specifically counter an
offlane loan Dr because you could put
the Weaver on support like AI was
pointing out or you kind of committed at
this point to putting a carry cuz in
reality is there a safe Lane hero that
can truly challenge l in the lane
together with tri is that possible I
think Weaver's fine and I think you pick
the strongest off laner here most likely
cuz they're going to Target it next so
like the Weaver tree match up versus
lone drud it should be perfectly fine
cuz one rotation or if you manage to get
on top of the lone dr's real hero and
you suuchi in with bugs he could die
pretty easily but lone no one's going to
like just straight out out CSS Z that's
why he's so strong in the landing stage
but there's definitely threat to kill
him and Weaver doesn't have problems
like csing cuz you have the gyate attack
you also have like the aikuchi you're
going to get csing just fine against the
lone Dr at least go even with kill
threat so I think it should be good
enough where did this hero go he was
pretty much top tier a couple of weeks
ago and we we barely seen him on the
main stage at all so what makes this a
good Beast Master game and the her got
some pretty significant Nerfs I think
the haulk especially level one is it
used to be completely op and now sort of
pathetic early um I think it's a really
good pick here though I think generally
when the like if you just look at
gliders lmes in general but also this
one a lot of times you can run out of
damage we've heard from the Quin Clips
like something they talk a lot about is
like keeping the formation and when you
play on that s the enemy tends to you
know you try to burst one guy they save
him and then you let run out of damage
you don't have enough to keep going but
Beast Master sort of like one of those
unlimited damage Heroes you can keep the
fight going keep throwing these axes
your damage keeps ramping up your
summoned is also like sort of a classic
counter to silencer just because if you
get to the levels on Beast Master sanser
doesn't really do anything to your
summons curse doesn't do much damage
it's too much mana and once you kick a
sort of weak laner like s Beast Master
it's one of the offers that really
snowball really hard take over the map I
think Willow one would Fenix be a good
ban here too I know silencer is good
versus Phoenix but I know ler hates
playing the ad hero and I think spirit's
looking for position four here as well
to Lane with that Beast Master most
likely do do you even feel like part of
the silencer pick here was a protection
pick so to speak against a potential
Phoenix coming out when they picked it
on gameing seconds remain hard to say
because like yeah you can silence them
but at the same time you could buy ways
to get out of it and you don't have a
good way to kill egg cuz Pango is just
rolling he can't attack lone Drew bear
is ineffective versus the egg Mor can
sort of do it but that's like going to
be your support most likely so team I
don't think they have enough but they're
going to leave it anyway so we'll see
what team spirit wants to pick up here
uh I feel like team spirit need a
partner for Puck to make some place on
the map because if Trent it's going to
be complicated and we will need
something to be happening for sure maybe
we don't need to do anything and
Gladiator is just going to run it them
and we're going to just skyra maybe I
can see Sky working I think the number
one party for team right now is making
sure the Beast Master is a good Lane if
Beast Master does not have a good Lane
against silencer then often times it can
be hard to fight into especially versus
pangle another match up where yes you
can roar his roll but if you cannot like
burst him in that then pangular becomes
very good against Beast Master in the
fights so I think the lane comes first
and then they can look at options after
that yeah for sure we aiming some good
carries against this master right now
too like with one terab and this looks
interesting I guess we'll see if the
Weaver will be on that position for or
not here if they're going to go for a
carry cuz that option does exist if they
want to go in I wouldn't mind a weaver
carry at all I think the lane would be
pretty strong for sanser Weaver doesn't
have to like commit I mean I think it
might depend what car they predicting
gladers to pick but I'm just not too
sure like what carry they're looking at
honestly in my head I'm like some drw
Ranger but that hero is not very strong
right now I just see yoro you know and
I'm like oh TI yoro drw Ranger it might
come
back nobody's been picking that hero
though right but it is a really good
game for it it's super good vers Pango
so annoying for L I feel like it's
probably not good enough of a hero but
if they would pick a new carry like I
want something like that with really
high damage oh to okay is this um I
think they're just punishing the
silencer right in the rning so on on
team spirit I think they've been playing
moska on the Tusk more so than mea if
I'm not mistaken is there a world that
this is a for Triant or do you think you
just have to put the Tusk for here with
Beast Master and how good is that lane
against what you're supposedly facing
here especially considering it's a blind
carry so far remain
I mean I wouldn't mind the tri four I
think like honestly committing really
hard into the Beast Master's Lane making
sure he secures it he can take over the
game is a good idea but I think dry
copter that's an old weaver really
really good for Beast Master too some
just die the Hulk is free golden exp
double melee versus double range that's
scary don't you guys just love when you
go into the finals and there's like
multiple Heroes that you haven't seen
for a week that come out in the very
first game amazing stuff so yeah beast
and Gyro
dare I say it's their first appearances
on the main stage I think so probably
haven't seen chyro on the main stage
since
ti5 he's back awesome uh what do you
guys make of this overall like if you do
you feel like there's any sort of
advantage that you can infer from
specific Lanes or you know what you've
seen from the team so far in the
tournament that makes you lean one way
or the other I think this game's going
to be completely decided in spirit safe
Lane like I think they picked this
Weaver and Trent just to be strong and L
is honestly sort of the same like this
hero really wants to win his Lane
depending on which way that lane goes I
think he'll determine a tempo for the
Post Lane phase I also feel the same
about gaming glader safe Lane as well if
it doesn't go well and Gyro doesn't have
a good laning stage and collapse can
manage to get kills with meor that could
change spirit's momentum a lot with this
Beast yeah very very depending on Lanes
right now how the lanes go will decide a
lot in this
game so how's the mid lane match up
going to go dendi uh to me it's may be a
little bit favorable for Pango but it's
still pretty good game for Puck but uh
it's pretty risky in my eyes to pick
buck so early like usually you want to
see more Heroes there is still two
silences so you want to buy a defensive
item which slows down other like
aggressive items that you might go for
so a bit scary for p yeah honestly I'm
really worried for a lot of this game I
feel like the gangs from tofu can come
in L is a hero you know he can just pull
away with his bear you can sort of leave
him alone and hopefully like that's why
I feel like if they don't win the yoro
MOs Lane it's going to like bleed really
hard into mid they can't keep the mort
there what do you guys make of the uh
the the Tusk here that Spirit ended up
going for into silencer who's
notoriously a really good anti- saave
hero and a big part of the Tusk is
saving allies with snowball do you think
that's maybe a little bit on the risky
side or I think he wants to kill the
silencer I think this is a hero that can
just like get on him and kill him right
away it's going to be more of aggressive
t Team instead of a defensive one yeah
for sure we're going to double jump with
Puck that's where going to be where
Target number
one all right thank you guys very much
with for your insights we are ready to
get into the game but before that that
we're going to a coach's interview with
silent from team spirit thank you very
much yes I am joined by silent of team
spirit as we get ready for this Grand
Final a best of five grand final not
many teams get the privilege of playing
best of fives but you've been to many of
them so to you is there any difference
between best of three DOTA versus best
of five DOTA uh for me you have uh more
chances to do a mistake best of three
you can really don't figure out how to
play against your enemy and what might
cost you serious
uh but here uh lucky it's best uh best
of five because uh Gladiators have
some we we play way too fast and I think
we need to adapt somehow for that uh
that's the point all right well we got
to get that data with a game number one
so Seattle are you ready to start Grand
finals that's what I like to hear let's
get into it with game number one
that's right it's time to make our grand
finals head underway on one side we have
a team that is absolutely the best team
of the year but on the other side the
strongest team of the tournament on one
side we have three time te major winners
and on the other side TI winners but
only one can claim the ages I've seen a
lot of TI cap we are going back 12
editions of this right now we have seen
lower bracket runs we've seen upper
bracket runs we have seen first Bloods
we have seen Roshan but one thing is
absolutely clear to me right now at ti2
in the heart of DOTA and Seattle these
two teams are undoubtedly the best two
teams in the world right now and both of
them are absolutely terrifying and
that's exactly why gaming Gladiators
stack the Bounty runes but they failed
to be able to claim the first blood they
wanted to be able to get that early
momentum over a team that is so scary I
mean team spirit have demolished every
team that has stood in their way gaming
Gladiators though have had to make the
long run through the lower bracket and
there's something special about that
lower bracket momentum you cannot
underestimate how much this team has
gone through especially going to their
fourth valavan Grand final of the year
no team has made a complete sweep and
usually the team that is favored in that
sense can't even make that type of run
so this team cannot be underestimated at
the same time all of us here watching
when you see a Toro come out of that
player walkway with a shaved head the
amount of fear that instills into you
the amount this man is willing to
sacrifice to claim a second agis and
join that limited Pantheon of two time
TI
winners you can't not help but be a
little afraid of what he's willing to do
here in a best of five both these teams
are capable of anything the greatest
question however if you watch the lower
bracket run from gaming is can team
spirit put a stop to the speed and the
tempo in which they are playing these
games cuz right now nobody across all of
those Series has been able to do it how
a lot of these games have not gone past
the 25-minute mark so you need to slow
it down you need to play your game or at
least take it back to them if there is
one team in the world that can
accomplish that it is team spirit who
have shown that they are no slouches
when it comes to the first 10 minutes
particularly the laning phase yes this
laning phase is going to be the ultimate
test for this best of five it's going to
be a long journey to get through this
finals and who walks away winning this
laning phase could just end up winning
the entire thing as moska will end up
going down kofu finally claims first
blood for gaming Gladiator and this is a
familiar story acceleration for Ace on
the off Lane lone Drew this is a hero
that has demolish the lower bracket
along with all the buildings in those
series a scary hero to give a lead off
to here especially when once more gam
have a lot of tempo that can just go
with Ace go through these objectives
play with that Bear's timings but I like
what Spirit have brought out here in
game one right these are a lot of Heroes
that are not afraid to Skirmish early
and straight back death against tofu
will end up helping to get the kill on
to tofu but will end up falling in the
end Ace is gladly going to be able to
dive a bit more onto moska they are
definitely winning this Lane they're
walking away with it a bit and that's
going to be fast over corrosion for the
faar that's going to give them a lot of
Chase down potential on this Lane
aska oh he has that extra little bit of
heal end up dying the bear that's going
to be three out gold over to utoro but
AIDS can keep up that pressure with a
fresh reub big turnaround for yoro
honestly this Lane was looking a little
grm if you get Ace to that fast over
corrosion which has just taken over a
lot of these Lanes all of a sudden you
get a bear kill back lot of golden XP
for yoro he can start the regain
momentum in this Lane this is a very
strong Lane for for team spirit tree
Weaver there's not much that beats us so
this just shows how strong this offing
is for gaming as well they're com a
massive win if they could actually bring
down Ace but yoro is going to have to
try and go for tofu instead who gave up
his own life to be able to kill the bug
on Ace to protect his core he do die but
if utoro gets caught by an entangle here
it's going to be a heavy punish But Not
Afraid turns around battles back against
that be knowing Ace still has some time
before he has another resummon available
still a lot of gold going to yoro here
as he takes a net worth lead good sign
for team spirit is I mean Weaver has to
be one of the fastest carries in this
met I think CK is the other one that I
had point to of course brisac he's a
pseudo carry getting banned out this is
a hero that team spirit first pick for a
reason if they get him to a good
position he can go and defend all these
towers you can take every single fight
with this carry hero try and match Dao's
Pace where I almost feel like it doesn't
matter what hero Dao's playing this guy
is going to run at you he's going to
join all the skirmishes with Quinn you
have to be ready for the fan collapse at
a certain point either get get some
trades be ready to defend them at the
towers this Beast Master can trade on
the map that's another objective that
team spirit can look for as this game
progresses I feel like out of all the
players on gameing Gladiators it's
definitely dorio that's a resummon yeah
it is Ace he'll lose yet another bear
yoro is just climbing up the network
chart now a laning face that started off
a bit bad for them but now they've got a
full 20 second window with no bear so
they should easily be able to get most
of the Cs and also the the Bounty man he
is sitting at 3K net worth already way
ahead of anybody else in this game it
adds up real fast these bears are worth
a lot it's also extra damage going into
Ace you're not healing while the faar is
on cool down there's a lot going wrong
in this off lane for gaming right now
for the hero that's supposed to give
them that lead at least comparatively to
those other games right this is still a
very even game but if you watched any of
these Series yesterday particularly the
azer one I guess you're not down 5K at
the 5 minute Mark you're doing pretty
well yeah seriously you cannot let
gaming Gladiators run away with the
laning ph and that when we were talking
about a backstage and so many else so
many other people that we talked to
Backstage everybody was saying team
spirit is not going to get run over the
landing won't let that happen you can
make these kind of rotations pick up on
the snowball they have three Heroes to
all bang onto this jar copter but it's
not quite good enough tofu protecting
them nicely they'll get some damage in
return but team spirit are going to
remain relatively healthy nice missile
Dodge on the snowball mea he's going to
be able to make some really nice plays
this game this Tusk is a hero that can
not only give him the physical burst to
go through the bear at the later stages
but the snowball Dodge on Heroes like
gyro and pangle have to throw out their
Spells at the start of the fight it can
get you your core bkbs off it can stall
out the fight get you a roar off of you
know collapse coming back out of it
something that could be really
instrumental as this game progresses
here and once more Spirit making the
first moov poka has been really active
in this laning phase trying to skew it
as much as possible to team spirit's
Advantage give them that breathing room
and of course this is a tri and
protector lineup we're talking about
these objectives something Gaming's
focused on you can keep your Towers up
Living Armor it double blows are going
to help here and Quinn's going to come
back into this place se's an opportunity
but Z is the two supports are already
dead though and there's no way for this
Puck to change the match up now plus two
in on the board for celery glaes already
getting some extra work done will leave
solo Lanes on these side so yoro going
to try and make the most of it he gets
rooted oh you know he wanted another
bear kill on this Lane man he has been
taken it to Ace level Advantage already
going y Toro's way it look like it'll
just be the Dragon Land so defensive
oriented build here from the Toro get
the high HP up don't get bursted in this
game man he is just chunking haste down
this is Rome opportunity up here right
like this is a Great Hero for team
spirit the Roman you can keep chipping
Ace's HP pool cuz every time you kill
this bear he has to resummon he's
susceptible again and you don't really
take the ult too early Laur he's going
to try and bait it out here by using the
illusion Rune the first Power Rune was
an illusion Rune not necessarily one
that you feel the best about but he's
going to try and bait It Out by showing
his illusion mid and seeing if they can
catch something in this Top Lane tofu
he's going to be marked there couldn't
get there in time to snag away the
wisdom Rune but they can get this one
kill Ace is around laurl he'll back away
so will Ace he's ready for the push
that's coming in in fact he knows he's
kind of surrounded by Heroes so he wants
to play defensively but LL already back
to the mid lane doesn't want to miss out
on too much of his CS nice heads up
smoke by Spirit uh they are a team that
will happily smoke to any of these
wisdom runes and if you studied them you
know it's coming the seven the 14 the 21
especially is one of their big power
moves they really want this XP advantage
and again rotating to Ace's Lane I think
is a ree for success the other move
you're going to make is to collapse when
that Helm is up to try and push this
Tower or kick to watch you out of the
lane but I feel like every time you make
one of these aggressive moves on gaming
in the early game you're pretty happy
with it right cuz it means they're not
going to ace they're not pushing your
Tower and then things like this can
start to happen where another kill for
yoro he is absolutely out of control oh
and there car's going to be in trouble
as well p is in big trouble here on the
side of gaming Gladiators and no TP
rotation coming in so they're just going
to run down Daio do they dive the tower
though it's a bit scary and they've run
out of Reon ources so drau lives but
only on the sliver of HP and it's not
doing him much good either cuz he's
going to have to make a run back to the
Fountain very likely you can see the
sidelane pressure here this is another
thing that's causing gam some issues
right now because they want to rotate
towards mid play around Quinn so every
time you bring supports off the side
Lanes it's up to Spirit to recreate the
pressure there and not let Quinn get
away with these skirmishes with the
power runes however gaming rotating
supports mid will secure that power room
for Quinn now it's a question of what he
can do with it here I mean can you
rotate into y tor's lane is this Weaver
killable in the very early game calling
plus some Roots it's
doable and in fact they're just going to
bring everybody up here try and go on
Ace again this is one the lone Drew is
susceptible perfect opportunity with the
bear now being put on cool down they
have done serious damage to Ace killing
him so many times and even maybe
catching tofu here C is going to try and
slow him down but that's two supports
without a real stun they're just going
to back away though bottom Lane that was
the rotation coming out from Quinn mea
left a bit alone here as the Beast
Master went for the Lotus instead good
separation there with Shard and Quinn
doesn't feel like diving too deep and
this is the helm coming out finished for
collapse so now you have a second
pressure point of the map if your team
spirit you've got through this early
game in a pretty decent spot yoro well
ahead of the pack so if he wants to
rotate play with collapse start pushing
some of these towers you can start to
take Gaming's game plan against them
here as they are still struggling to
keep Ace in that offlane this bear has
just been exploited in the early game so
much extra golden XP
gets back to the safety of the trees
gaming Gladiators are here in force but
fortunately the Pango versus the Beast
Masters doesn't necessarily leave you
the most options can't really put to use
that Rolling Thunder super well he's
going to try for it anyway perhaps going
to force out the par La Roar collapse
now going to try and back away with that
extra bit of movement speed does get hit
by the jar copter ultimate that's going
to slow him down enough good snowball
pickup from meor that buys him a couple
seconds but Quinn is going to follow
that ball he is perfectly be able to hit
him both wasb it enough though and Daio
and Quinn are now in trouble top of the
coil Laurel going to lock him down and
there's not much these supports can do
to stop it in fact they're just going to
feed right alongside the other two of
gaming Gladiators as team spirit in a
fiveman move sweep over gaming
Gladiators run them down underneath
their towers and even through the portal
kku will be denied that exit instead
he'll head back to the Fountain after a
triple kill for yoro and yoro straight
back to the Top Lane doesn't miss a beat
the down side of all that off lane going
wrong for Game and his Ace didn't even
have a bear during all that so you
cannot bring the numbers to that fight
just an overextension on collapse that
yoro is happy to join and get the big
swarm turnaround kill of course with a
beautiful coil just lock him in place
let the Weaver do the damage here this
is very deep it feels like a for yeah
forc play if anything right and you know
the snowball save is going to come out
here this is what I'm saying you
disjoint the missile you disjoint some
of the gyro damage that turnaround is
deadly tri's going to give you sustain
to just push through a lot of this poke
damage you're also missing the supportal
like w and silence are not too strong
when they don't got the silence on him
if they can keep him in place the dead
shot moves him back in they have to use
the global but it will get the job done
a huge kill streak going the way of Ace
his Networth just shot right back up as
he got 587 gold for just himself off
that kill I mean we're 11 minutes in the
game and yor already had a 6X streak so
Ace absolutely happy to pick that up
that's the the global vers the Weaver
before he has any sort of dispel item
which looks like it's going to become
very late in this game as yoro opted for
a deso buildup another reason that kill
was pretty valuable right you slow down
the death so limit the charges he get in
these early exchanges the slower it is
the worst it's going to be cuz his pace
is very strong right now of course Daio
we have not seen gyro too much to this
tournament but the big upside for this
hero is the stacking right it's not
something we've seen gaming go back to a
lot as the games been very fast but this
triangle is getting stacked and is
waiting for gyro to come and collect the
other ancients are also doubled up right
now so this is a lot of golden XP
sitting in the bank for gam if they can
move Dau over there start to clear
through with the max FL Cannon something
that team spirit might think about
contesting depending on how fast they
can push these towers down yeah
absolutely I think that that in this
game it's funny but I feel like the game
plan is kind of swamped where team
spirit want to be able to run over game
Gladiators take these outer Towers so
they can disrupt that ancient farming
and they're going to go straight to it
no hesitant SE whatsoever immediate coil
put on to Quinn but they don't really
have the strength to be able to bring
him down just yet protected by all of
gaming Gladiators who again they saw
team SP in the bottom Lane show up as
five they will do the same here in the
mid lane Quinn looks to find his Mark
looks to see if he can drive right on
through and straight to moska he'll find
him here in the corner clear out most of
the trees but L is actually going to
bounce back in here OPP but PO is going
to stand and fight as best he can but
off Ace immediately Laurel trying to
make his way out and oh the silent maybe
he gets clipped again he's dead couldn't
jump to his orb in
time yeah they get Ace but it does cost
them quite a bit as lurl was a big piece
of the momentum for team spirit here
tofu coming up big calling is just going
to be their biggest way to deal with
puck in these team fights if you can
land it it's probably a dead Puck you
dead shot him back into it it's an
extended duration here once more that
fight got dragged out really nice
disengage from Spirit draw them back up
the ramp waste this Rolling Thunder
chasing moska on The Cliff yoro gets
another pretty good angle you can see
the aggressiveness they're trying to
play with this Beast Master right now
they're taking the push to gaming not
playing defensive at all and once more
the aggression continues no rolling
thunder for Quinn right here to try and
protect him another swashbuckle up at a
second he's actually going to turn and
fight as best as possible but the puck
is going to be the end of Quinn I
thought he was going to swash buckle
down and away from the trees maybe that
was an error this is looking all spirit
in this first 50 minutes here they're
getting a lot for their Beast the start
for yoro and now it's just going to have
to come back back down to the FL and
clearing through the Ancients to put
tachu in a spot where he can start to
take these fights this is a position
we've not seen gaming in in a while
right in this tournament especially they
are usually the ones with a very strong
lead going into this 15 20 minute mid
game period all of a sudden they're on
the back fo double damage definitely
going to help accelerate Theo here but
we talked about the resiliency of this
team right there's a reason they're here
in this Grand finals there's a reason
they've been in a lot of them too this
is not a team that can only play from
ahead they're going to have to show some
resiliency here and playing a little bit
from behind particularly with I mean
maybe Ace's times but honestly he's
found a lot given his start I'm
surprised at how rich he is yeah he's
got three deaths I think his bear has
died like five different times in this
game but still second in the network
chart still though Spirit clearly
holding the tempo control of this game
they're up by 3K they're got to be
feeling pretty good about it even if
they couldn't stop the jyro copter from
clearing out Stacks they don't have to
do it the first time around just taking
these outer towers and trying to scrunch
in the map a little bit yeah take
advantage of the fact that they is not
ready and it is dead even that would
have been my prediction before this
series as
well goes to show I mean respecting the
ace timing as well too like this
Radiance on the bear we have seen them
do an incredible amount of work with it
and it's coming soon I think team spirit
really want to finish off this mid Tower
before those timings reach the agonum
scepter on Danio the radiance on Ace
here and these are acceleration items
that's the thing if if you give gam in
time to their big farm in the radiance
and the agum SE on Daio those let you
fight but they also let you just clear
the map so holding these Tower UPS if
you can limit the space they can use
these farming items on in terms of the
sides of the map that's going to feel
really nice with this tream protect
their lineup moska did not go for Living
Armor points early hasn't even needed
them at this point and all three tier
ones are up another aggressive kofu with
the calling trying to protect mea just
outside of that silence use the snowball
trying to get some distance nice dead
shot though actually hit laurl in the
background yeah but the the exchange on
the other side of the map Ace going down
to yoro again with this desolator
instant reveal gets two charges on it
plus a bear kill as he was just pushing
towards that Radiance 700 off and this
Tower dies this is an influential tower
for what gaming want to do on the map
because now both ancients are exposed
and Y Toro straight in there he would
have liked to have found that stack but
he will be happy to take the net worth
away from Dario a hero that just needs
these camps
up now you're going to have to need a
bit of a backup plan if you're gaming
Gladiators you no longer have that good
control over the double ancient Stacks
like you're talking about and look at
this fast Shard for yoro 2 yeah this is
where Weaver is absolutely terrifying
you're getting the extra geminate hit
off the suuchi going through everybody
with an early desolator these Heroes
just don't have the armor to deal with
this right now you don't burst him he
wants to play Super aggressive and like
get on top of people which against these
kind of silences could play against them
that's why it's very important for them
to get this a just get this second life
it gives them time to get bkb up on
utoro so he can't get punished just yet
I mean this man has absolutely no chill
he's not here to win an AIS he's here to
take it away from you and right now he
is controlling the tempo of this game
it's going to force g into a smoke that
yields nothing right there nowhere here
in time and still missing those big core
items to take the fight anyway you're
still 300 gold off this Radiance for Ace
that's your big 5v5
timing just an awkward Point yoro
playing this game way too fast right now
and the Beast Master from collapse
speeding everything up Helm of the
overlord is already done by the way so
this map pressure is going to
escalate gaming Gladiators really not
able to do much besides just kind of
make sure Danio doesn't get smoke ganked
playing around him heavily here comes
the pressure from team spirit though
radiant's done this is a good point to
get it done if you want to defend this
tier one mid a really fast time lapse
there you could really y Toro I think
felt like he was overextended there if
he gets caught once by the silences or
chances he just dies behind the tower
and then that agis may be useless he may
just die twice in a row and that's why
this build is starting to come together
for the ages right cuz yoro still
doesn't have a defensive item the global
still very effective here against Spirit
Laurel also considering a bkb this game
on Puck early just to deal with the
calling and the global silence that's
coming out G have a lot of tools to lock
down these Mobility Heroes if they can
find them right now moska just doing
some scouting do manka but there's
nowhere for him to really run he knows
it too he's definitely been caught but
he got some good information information
that'll lead to the pick off on Ace he
saw all those Heroes and he said guys
this lone Druid is alone in the Top Lane
again kill him the single Target
physical first is way too fast for this
true form to even be considered in terms
of casting it they just had AES
number Radiance reveal down the drain as
his timings are going to get prolonged
yet again and collapse he's just Bing it
up not too worried about playing on game
inside of the map right now just wants
to hit his own bkb it looks like team
spirit they're just going to work
towards a triple bkb timing eventually
look towards that second ran with it get
the spell and debuff Immunity up for the
silences that are causing them problems
in the fight then you're not too worried
about anything as Quinn is getting
shredded by the death yeah even if you
get out the Rolling Thunder the physical
damage from yoro is too much for him to
handle tofu was kind of desperate wanted
to be able to get that kill on mea maybe
trying to take away the Aegis but
frankly he doesn't do nearly enough
damage right now to deal with this carry
even on low HP like this missed the dead
shot on miror managed to side step that
one and they'll dive tofu pretty easily
ataro does be to get off the timeline
Serv so barely meanwhile salary's picked
off in mid team spirit they are
absolutely outplaying gaming Gladiators
right now on the map they just know all
of these heroes are getting picked apart
there's just seems to be no response
whatsoever from these Gladiators I mean
there's nowhere to run right you you
need to combine the damage here on gam
to get anything done right now and
instead it's just team spirit going on
you on multiple Lanes so you can't group
up a is still up for 2 minutes here
eight deso charges already done for y
too as he is just slowly claiming your
soul this is going to escalate fast this
is a scaling lineup too with all the
oras they can bring to the table the
swarm's going to go through you have
tusk physical damage to pour in on top
of it all and a crystal is for yoro I
mean how many aggressive items does he
need in this
game I love the fact he's like yeah I I
don't need that b KB yet still have to
just for another minute and a half and
considering the pace of game right now
it does kind of feel like he's going to
get that bkb once the agents expires
because this is going to be another team
fight and perhaps another objective
taken 21 minute wisdom room coming up
Tormentor an object as well silence
already going out they're trying to lock
down this Weaver trying to stop him from
killing anybody it gets off the time
lapse though horses a little bit of a
resources out of gaming Gladiators they
just throwing some damage around barl
looking at that back line you got to be
be careful of giving Dao these good
black targets up front as they're going
to trade a bunch of the Bears HP they're
still looking for over here they the
detection catch him out something is
going wrong with the detection on this
Tre and for sure he's just getting way
too much information way too deep right
now you spirit will play it safe play it
slow agis out in 50 seconds so you have
to think about the timer here look at
that first damage Quinn caught by the
coil and instantly killed by utoro and
you can feel it utoro is seeing an
opportunity going to be able to cut down
celery and now he goes in for the kill
the AG of Stills expired but the rest of
his team provides the disabl so the
second life comes back up he's going to
shred through a looks over to tofu next
now last left perhaps Daio trying to run
him down Daio doing his best he can but
it againsts three different cores he
can't actually fight back he has to Oh
missing out of the Dead Shot y Toro is
Unstoppable he's just diving into the
base like it's nothing you just think
about it again 30 HP is the only thing
that'll save you from this man right now
he's just running Rampages through the
fight 12 in two at 22 minutes he is just
taking everything and more he has the
ORS to back him up this aggressive item
build has paid off in
Spades the aggressiveness of yoro I've
seen in very few players at TI before I
mean that play when he was he was more
playing get skewed into the base and
then he waveforms deeper into the base
that's the kind of aggression this guy's
playing with right now you got to play
to win you play not to lose it
eventually will happen right now team
spear just taking over the map really
good Wards on those fights will get Deed
from gaming but that's the power of what
moska is providing them with this tree
all of these fights and pickoffs they've
been scouted he's been on gaming side of
the map for a lot of it it's paid off to
a large degree this early Tre and
Shard doing some work and of course the
vision's really nice versus these
silencer lineups cuz if you're the one
initiating on gaming forcing out awkward
globals taking some damage on your
backline the fight gets very weird very
fast and suddenly Doro goes in he kills
somebody time lapses out there's a black
dragon porns fire on somebody else too
many fires to put out quite literally
here and once more moska just scouting
out the moves from gam gives him all the
setup in the
world is deadly man the cores from
Spirit are converging on Top Lane look
at moska man he doesn't care if he gets
caught as long as he gets information
for his team he knows all five Heroes of
game of Gladiators are up here so team
spirit are going to slowly approach
they're going to group up together and
take this fight yoro just timelaps to
the Fountain and back to get his bkb you
will not have time lapse for this fight
say I don't with the thre man coil it's
looking beautiful and you T right in
there with this fresh bkb to lay the
damage in these cores once again Ace has
no chance with the bear and of course
the Beast Master's going to lock down
that ball you're not going anywhere
Quinn they're going to catch more tofu
is going to be the last one down datu
only survives because of his TP
everything coming together triple bkb
instantly revealed all together on the
exact fight maposa sets up it's just
just beautiful gameplay here from team
spirit and gaming still searching for
answers because the second these fights
start they're already over they don't
even know they're coming yep yoro he
does not need an ultimate at all to take
these engagements when they are
completely one side it'll be more
objective pushing this is just a
beautiful Forman overgo setup you cannot
ask for anything more swarm hits
everybody and then you get to save Roar
for the Rolling Thunder after Ace goes
down to just right clicks I mean making
it look easy out here the item timings
the position
all of it is just so perfect for team
spirit That's The Power of vision this
is a team that won a TI previously off
of vision advantage and they're showing
why the Beast Master might have got
nerfed in this regard but moska doing
his best Hawk
impersonation if you want to be worried
about uh the Chen of gaming Gladiators I
think it's the train protector of team
spirit that may become a problem in this
series maybe there's just not enough
centuries in the world for you to buy to
catch this guy he's dewarding them too
that's the problem
they are lacking sries they are lacking
the detection no one wants to buy a gem
right now I you don't want to have to
buy a gem for a Tre protector but we're
getting to that point and every time one
of these fights goes wrong you fall a
little bit more behind with the I mean
core Heroes that don't want to function
in these team fights from behind right
particularly the gyropter this it here
you want to accelerate with the triangle
accelerate with the ancient camps put
him in a prime position like a Luna or
something where he goes in that fight
he's the absolute raid boss Daio has
escaped these fights but across his
teammates tombstones as he cannot output
the Firepower to match what team spirit
are bringing with the ball right now and
everything is looking towards this next
ran which team spirit would be very very
happy to collect and put an AIS on yoro
with his aggressive DPS build not to
mention I mean I mean Laurel is picking
up the speed right he's just going for
the melom right click Puck it's also a
fearsome late game Beast especially when
you have that Beast Master or pumping in
attack speed to everybody on this lineup
you have tag teams above the physical
you're going to have multiple scaling
right click cores here for team spirit
you're going to need on gaming at some
point you're going to need survivability
satanics AC anything that buys you time
in this
fight gaming Gladiators getting caught
there the overgrowth not quite landing
on to Quinn he'll survive as a result of
that utoro still going to have a poke at
them though quickly time lapses away
before the silences catch him
out he's just so aggressive man he's
going to start back away with the rest
of his team as you said 19,000 net worth
lead they're very comfortable it's
really just not slipping up at this
point in time that starts with being
able to get the second ran of the game
and then comes The High Ground push
which gam of Gladiators I don't know how
do you what do you feel better about a
Roshan contest or a high ground play
uh maybe game two High Ground Play for
sure right you let him go into you abuse
the fact that the callings a really
strong defensive spell you catch the
tree and first that's a nice pickoff
that is actually really nice with the
gem on the ground yeah okay so needed a
gem in this game moska will give it to
you that's a big pick up limit the
vision limit Mosa's aggressive
positioning that was very deep right
especially for team spirit looking
towards this next row Sean they have the
Beast Master creep in the pit scouting
it out a rich man's Hawk for lack of
anything
better just waiting waiting on their
Vision yeah the sad part for game of
Gladiators is they can't actually do
anything off of that play besides
getting a little bit more farmed than
normal they'll be able to push out some
of the Sid Lanes I assume they know know
that team spirit's going to be doing
Roshan sometime soon of course they're
doing it right now and it happens so
quickly it gives you such a small window
if you're uh gaming Gladiators to
actually be able to contest so you're
right they're going to play For The High
Ground they're going to try and see if
they can make team spirit slip on that
staircase just a question what are they
going to get up for that High Ground
defense right it's the datalis on datu
that's going to be the big DPS item here
Ace is just I mean he's just going
wraith bands he didn't even get to
anything else in this time period it's
just going to be armor up try and
survive the initial burst now these W BS
are pretty nice first team Spirits minus
on the R so they are very good value I
don't blame him for doing this but in
that other lone Drew game we saw I mean
he had a full Harpoon before he went
back for these waii bands so tells you
how far behind he is off that you know
first 15 minutes team spirit shutting
him down right now and the question is
how do you want to go High Ground cuz
there is a calling to fight into there
is a rolling thunder that can abuse you
on the choke points there's the radiance
burn with mischance and a resummon
assuming it's hard to jump Ace initially
and of course Global can bail out any
sort of initiation from the tus for the
Beast see how strong yoro really feels
he is if he thinks he can just walk up
and start hitting this tier three
wouldn't surprise me maybe that's why
he's gone Scotty here level 20 done for
the Weaver with Scotty completed a
double damage Rune and a quiver oh yeah
I I mean if you get hit once by this
Weaver I think you're gone on the
supports and that's a huge problem for
Dao as well because he doesn't have that
satanic buildup yet so he doesn't have
sustain to be able to stand toe against
the Weaver for too long Ace I don't know
if you know what's coming for you right
now but you're not going to like
it it's going to be a shot to the back
of the head he
gone Blown Away by yoro and they catch
Quinn in the mid lane they don't need
utoro to make this kind of play Laurel
activates his bkb to catch the opposing
mid laner and with two dead a double
damage activated team Spirits are all
but just waiting for the creep wave to
catch up with them well that's one way
to break The High Ground just one shot
an enemy off Lane carry here oh and uh
force it with a double damage here the
Toro has AC Ora behind him now as well
so that deso plus the stor plus the AC
is just going to amp this physical
through the roof right now which makes
this High Ground Siege a lot more
tempting here it goes through the jump
bkb immediately activated by Daio but
there's that physical damage Daio he can
actually stand up against yoro and has
backo yeah he's just going to go for it
t already got it oh No Way the final
little bit of damage required yoro can
claim it yoro boss this man knows no
fear no limits right now he's just
taking your base at 30 minutes a
position Gan is used to putting their
opponents in the news has been full
taught here as team spe have just given
them nothing to the map it feels like
for 15 20 minutes Ace can't even escape
the tier 3es right now just going to
have to take a high ground defense
without your carry watch another Lane
disappear would not be surprised they
stop this without Daio I mean I think
Vera can also jump if he really wants to
just force the issue his tusar is hella
tanky right now gossamer cave drum happy
to start the engagement particularly if
you can find a good core Target he got
feared on the jump that was that was
incredibly impressive actually but it
will not yield them the fight and it'll
be a second
lane two lanes Barracks up for team
spirits and they still have a minute and
a half left on that second line for the
Weaver that final push I mean if you're
team spirit you're here playing a full
best of five against gaming Gladiators
why not make the first game quick just
for your own sake yeah give them a taste
of their own medicine
uh-huh and show that the zoo is indeed
not dead that's the scary part of this
game for me you have collapsed on a hero
that I mean they have been incredibly
proficient with right this was a first
phase ban at Riad for a reason it is a
collapse signature hero but it's not one
of those big jump stunners that
everybody is afraid of they're afraid of
the collapse Magnus the the collapse
stunners this is a hero that just took
over the map he farmed he played his
game with the atoro and it was the raw
aggression of objective taking the put
gaming on the back foot it's a scary
thought if team spirit are taking he's
doing it again isn't he own Strat
against you and yeah time lap to the
base for some datal
action it's your own x marks the
spot that is so much burst damage when
he's got he's got the enchanted quiver
on top of that this is an insane like
single hit right it doesn't take much he
just suuchi and hits you instantly can
start to run away you're just getting
chunked this is the strength of Weaver
right now 15 and two for yoro mea
looking for his opening gameing
Gladiators it team's pretty clear they
can't take an honest fight against team
TRD anymore they're going to have to
play around the fountain here as to jump
forward the dream coil is slowly taking
them out tofu does manage to live for
now gets back to the Fountain but team
spirit they still have more
opportunities coming the agis is going
to expire so gaming Gladiators manag to
weather that storm and it's possible
that team spirit may decide that it's
best just to wait for a third ran before
they end it think yoro is happy to give
the Aegis up it'll free up another slot
for him at the rate he's going yeah
seriously he just wants more damage more
survivability everything is great for
him right now the scary part is you can
still work towards a Tusk a in this game
I Mir is quite farmed oh yeah you're
talking about a high ground break
mechanism they really getting a
stalemate and need it he's going to kick
someone out Andor just runs straight
into them BPS bkb turns around oh man
that damage is just building up so
quickly Quinn's got in so is the bear
Dario battling up against Laurel but the
big bad boss of the the fight is
definitely in Toro and once he turns his
eye on a hero abely over game over for
this one the team Spirits making
absolutely no qualms about shutting
gaming Gladiators out in their own style
33 minutes and it's done such a onesided
game one I mean nice lower bracket run
right welcome to the Grand finals here
welcome to the ultimate boss of DOTA
right now as you might have won three
Majors you might have made it all the
way here but if you can't find a way to
break this team which nobody else has
been able to do you're going to go home
empty-handed and game gladi like they
had such a good run leading up to this
right they lost one game in this playoff
run of theirs and that was against Team
Liquid the only team who managed to take
it until they run into team spirit and
they they kind of look shook right oh
yeah that's what they want their
opponents to feel a 30-minute High
Ground GG make it look easy just run
away with the lanes you had a couple
power runes go Quinn's way but he
couldn't find anything on these side
Lanes the mid Clash didn't work the side
lane pressure mounted way too quickly
yet ancients to fall back on for
collapse yoro is just slaying people
ends this game 18 and two this man's
just padding his legacy stats at this
point I mean seriously he's trying to
make a a name for him himself here as he
already did once before a TI 10 but if
he could become a two time alongside his
team it would be something magical but
that game one that might have been
convincing we've seen plenty of
convincing games in TI it's the best of
five for a reason right Avery there's
some changes we can make strategy wise
in particular what was one thing you
would point for gaming Gladiators that
you would like to see heading forward in
this series I mean you have to think
about the lanes going a bit better for
you and how who you're going to play
around right now because it felt like
they left Ace on an island for a lot of
that offline early game and TP just
abused it especially with this Weaver
pick it's basically the most aggressive
carry you give you a Toro start like
that he's just going to pop off on it
and never look back he's the best carry
of the tournament so far showing why
absolutely showing why in the panel will
sure be able to talk more about that as
we head into game
two thank you very much CVG team spirit
take game number one here in the ground
finals of the international
2023 and it was uh it was almost almost
as if team spirit just taken a page out
of gaming gladiator's book and uh
basically was the oppressor in this game
I'm joined by F by T but he also had a
change on the panel as we now have
insania weighing in for the inside and
you said this is oppressive game play
coming out from team spirit here yeah I
feel like normally when you play against
Gladiators they tend to Corner you into
taking a lot of bad fights I'm sure
anyone that's watched this play like why
are you guys fighting them like it's so
obvious you're going to lose this fight
but I feel like what Spirit did this
game was they they brought the numbers
really early on and made sure that
wasn't going to happen yeah it happened
at the 9 Minute 50 Mark for me when they
take this fight bottom miror he holds a
snowball he kind of baits G to take this
fight meanwhile Ace is in the mid lane
playing L like how does he rotate to
this bot fight and contribute to these
quick early engagements and that was the
story of the game for Spirit just
constantly Dodge take away the fights
away from LD but also when he's by
himself trying to recover you K him as
well he had eight deaths by the 30
minute mark it was the most times Ace
has died on Lone DD so far at the
international he was just completely
shut down yeah and on the topic of that
ler that game felt impossible for ler to
ever recover because I think that Spirit
had a genius Lane versus lro and that
came after it that's the interesting
thing they picked lro after they saw
Weaver and Tran I mean conceptually when
you have these very high damage out
Heroes like Weaver and TR on the lane
you should be able to kill the bear over
and over again and that's what happened
they killed the bear a couple of times
on Lane they were able to constantly
pressure and dive the lone Druid and it
made it so that because that Lane run so
poorly there was no way for Quinn on the
Pango to rotate top and correct it in
any way yeah it was a strong performance
that it definitely looked like team
spirit was very well prepared for what
gaming Gladiators was going to bring to
the table in the first game of the best
of five inania you've been against these
two teams in the grand finals several
times this year yeah unsuccessfully so
well what makes these two teams be the
grand finals raid boss if you will I
think they they're both teams that have
pretty strong identities and usually by
the time that they get to Grand finals
theyve really figured out what makes
their identity work so um they're not
really I would say like the most
adaptive teams but they're really good
at figuring out how can we enable
ourselves to play our own game so it
wouldn't surprise me if Gladiators you
know they swap up some Heroes and then
they go look to do the same thing again
it's probably going to be a battle of
like two very specific Styles and if
Gladiators can take control of the map
and really like force you into a corner
then they'll probably be Victorious and
if is able to like hold that away hold
the aggression off then I think they'll
have the edge yeah I feel like as well
for team spirit they're coming to this
series they pick Beast Master hear that
we haven't seen them play at the
international so far of course they do
play it multiple times a fall but it's
the fact that Spirit they look at gaming
they read them and go you know what
rather than trying to be defensive let's
just overwhelm you as well with our own
level of pressure a lot of teams have
tried to delay prolong and survive that
Onslaught but it was refreshing to see
Spirit just change up the style and go
no this is how you beat gaming yeah and
they close out their second pH is with
that Beast Master right and back when
Beast Master was very broken that was
the most difficult part of drafting is
you very concerned for those Goa 18 pick
on the Beast Masters or the storm
spirits and they picked that Beast
Master when they saw the silencer and
the MUA two supports that can't do
anything versus the zoo So Not only was
that pick genius but I really feel that
having this Weaver in the first phase
for yoro is going to be something to
look out for in the series because if
they can bring the aggression to G
Gladiators from their safe Lane early on
G might not be able to ever play for the
tempo that they're looking for yeah we
mentioned that the off laners were going
to play a big role here today uh inia I
don't know if you've noticed that as
well I mean for us on the panel we talk
about the the the best looking stats if
that makes sense and it's been very
often this International the off laner
why is that yeah I mean I think um so I
feel like there's been like multiple
metas like the group stage it was one
meta now it's another but the the off
Lanes seem to be like the general place
where you get a lot of pressure and with
how the portals Now work on the map
where you can like kind of portal around
and you can want one lane to go to the
off Lane seems to be like the easier
place to connect to and then like get
that thing going so having strong off
Lanes sets up for like your position
five to rotate and like everybody to
come in and create a lot of pressure and
both these teams are very like offlane
uh heavy teams you know like collaps and
Ace they're yeah two star players for
these teams very much so and we heard
our draft penel at the end there as well
at the end of the draft they mentioned
how important that Top Lane was going to
be and I think that's where we saw the
Weaver just pop off yoro had a fantastic
game yeah there is nothing really to
stop that we Weaver like I mentioned
before and pairing it up with the Triant
made it so that Not only was it a strong
kill threat Lane but it worked perfectly
in playing against the lone Droid that
they didn't even have to prepare for or
think about or maybe they did it in the
preparation knowing that lro might be
run by Gan because of their Series
yesterday but if lro can't have a good
start in the lane and his mid laner
cannot enable him by maybe getting some
cleanup kills after he's fed a couple of
bears then where do you go from there
because T was mentioning there's no way
for ler to rotate bottom when there's a
team fight going on he's too busy
recovering in the mid lane yeah and
recover gaming Gladiators never really
did do that so they're now one game down
in a best of five grand finals they have
some time to reset and while they do
that we are going to check in with ques
somewhere in the crowd yeah oh yeah what
[Music]
up wow Grandma's here trying to look hip
sorry about that everybody all right we
are coming in to talk to some crowd get
away from me oh hi I'm sitting down my
God you're making me nervous sir I have
yeah I'm talking to you I have several
questions for you um I'm not sure
whether I should put the microphone in
front of your face but I'll give you one
chance uh hey I'm sorry I lost my voice
from screaming at the game so loud he
Spirit lgd well luckily you're drinking
tea and getting better
[Applause]
all right what was the
hello do you really think I can't see
you why you always pick the drunkest
people why you do
this what was the best part of that
first
game shoro just deleting everybody
oh you know yoro it's funny you say that
that is what we call a sexy transition
to what slack was going to talk
absolutely I asked these peeps up here
who was the biggest yataro fan you guys
said you were yo fans right oh yeah he's
getting me all my fantasy points right
now all the fantasy points thank you
thank you and you especially when I said
is anyone a yatro fan this guy ran off
of three levels up and he just starts
sprinting why do you like yatro yatro is
the best carrier ever gold let's go yoro
am is watching it let's go am is
watching it yes that's right poor a
we're so sorry aturo about
a keep trying my friend nothing is
forever okay wait what the car Beast
said that they were the biggest Yuro fan
yes we have to find some way to find out
who is the biggest Yuro fan now if you
know the Lor yo lore he does one thing
before he goes in the grand finals
now you guys said you were the biggest
fans who's willing to shave their head
for yoro
I'll do it no
no no no no no
no just a little bit okay just a little
bit wherever you want no no however you
want it however you want it just a
little bit just a little bit we got it
we got it all right right
here just a
love
you back to
you thank you very much casy and slack
have you ever tried that you know maybe
something's lacking with the squad
little bit we had this last year you
know our coach said if we get top four
atti I will shave my head William looked
us in our eyes and said I promise you
guys if we get to four I will shave my
head yeah so we top four and then we're
like all right William you know we got
four days where is it let's shave it and
he's like no no no no no I said top
three but we had Vlog footage so we went
back and watched the Vlog and it's very
clearly top four but you guys also got
top three and then we got top three and
we're like William shave your head and
he's like you know like he William's out
of it and then uh yeah no shaving your
head I think probably would have is the
reason we didn't do better at this yeah
I mean next year there's always a chance
so maybe you know there's a 15minute
break in the the meantime Maybe ging
Gladiators is finding a razor as we
speak for their head that is
and that was very Grim that's not why I
wanted to go with that what I do want to
say isan we've got some very dat vated
FS I am sure that if slack push it that
uh there would have been a bald head
behind us and while they we have very
dedicated fans all around the world
there are venues packed with dedicated
fans watching the Dota 2 from afar you
guys are all with us here in spirit in
the climate pledge Arena and a lot of
you are also with Spirit as we saw a lot
of Cheers there where team spirit take
the first game of this best of five
grand finals and we we got to talk about
adaptations because it's a best of five
both of these teams have been here
before both of these teams have shown
that they have what it takes to be able
to adapt on the fly in the break that
they get the question is where are they
going to go with the adaptations I have
to address a little bit it's not really
an elephant it's more like horse size in
the room I want to talk about the gyro
copter that came out as the overall last
pick e it's not a hero that we've seen
do very well or has been very popular
over these last few weeks why why was
this attempted and why didn't it work
out I mean it was just a response to the
Beast Master right it's like at that
point what do you do you're playing
against a summons hero you don't have
anything to address it your pangali is
going to be a little bit busy because
he's playing against the puck Pango
alone isn't enough you go for gyro who's
typically the AOE clear type of carry
but in this her fell out of meta for
many reasons I feel like he plays a
little bit too slowly if the aggression
is brought to you in the way team spirit
brought it with that Weaver gyro does
not have enough time to respond to that
he needs to sit in his entrance needs to
farm up like two or three items and they
couldn't reach that point yeah I feel
like maybe the main question for me is
going to be lered I don't think gaming
will pick it so openly now knowing that
Spirit are going to be able to play such
a high Pace game kind of abuse the fact
that he's on one side of the map you can
only bring four and then on top of that
like e was mentioning if you have a jar
copter as well who also wants to hit
ancients like lenid wants a lane jar
wants ancients what three hero is going
to do everything else for you so I think
for gaming LD that's going to be the big
question mark for me maybe they pick it
on like 18 or kind of a closing part of
the phase rather than so openly yeah
with LD alone drew it there indeed the
offliner for Ace didn't have didn't have
a great game and overall it felt like
then the the plan insania that gaming
Gladiators had it was very different
from the style that we've seen them play
because if they are playing for the
later stages of the game they're not
going to be able to do their aggression
ball that we've seen them be very
dominant with I think the idea was to
try to set up like the same thing where
they have the SL and amera do very well
on the off lane and then you know we
have tofu running mid we call it
cringing in our team it's like when the
two supports show up mid and they just
cringe the mid laner um so I think they
wanted to cringe Laurel you know make
sure his game is terrible but it kind of
uh relies on the laning phase going well
and I think the gyro copter in many ways
is picked to enable that you want the
safe Lane to be strong you just want the
lane to go well to free up Celery free
up uh tofu to then go pressure mid lane
and enable Quinn to then you know get
the ball rolling but in this game it
just I don't think the lanes really
played out the way they expected them to
no I do I do think we should mention the
mid lane a little bit because we've
talked a lot about Pango this entire
weekend and this entire event so far in
other people's hands other than Quinn
the hero has not looked great overall
he's had a fantastic win rate with it
this time around TV this game though he
wasn't able to get the ball rolling
yeah no he he kind of fell flat thank
you thank thank you audible sigh um but
no I think the early game for Quinn he
was able to make a couple of those moves
he was punishing the supports from
Spirit but then it got to the point
where he was making so many rotations
that eventually Spirit knew which one to
capitalize on which one to punish so I
think we they shouldn't be deterred from
picking this hero it is a matter of
there so many other factors laying into
it but yeah the Quinn panglea it's
probably a hero that he would want to
play a couple more times if he's going
to try and secure this uh this AIS I
mean the issue was he couldn't rotate on
the lane that he needed to rotate which
was the Weaver Lane right if he's
consistently putting all of his efforts
in playing on the Beast Master Lane
you're not really solving the Crux of
the problem because even if you can get
a couple of kills on that lane Beast
Master is just going to sit in the
jungle and farm for a little bit while
the Weaver is playing a supremely
aggressive game versus your lone Dr and
not allowing him to come back but when
Quinn has looked good with the Pango
this tournament it's usually come out
later in the draft right yesterday they
had it close out their second phase
versus azer Ray when they saw the
enchantress in the
and it looked great there today they
brought it out after the Weaver and is
seeing a weaver enough to pick a pangier
that early I don't think so I also like
the fact that they picked so on the on
the flip side with the Weaver you have a
Tusk and a tree so when things are going
kind of chaotic whatever of these melee
Heroes wants to go to the weav it's
going to be a kill Lane right it's like
you can use that twin gate get a kill so
it's a bit difficult for that it's a bit
difficult indeed and you see a lot of
thoughtful faces there for gaming
Gladiators and uh we have a lot of data
on them they've played a lot of games
the most games played here at the
international making it all the way
through a full best of three lower
bracket means that team spirit has a lot
of data to go off of as well insia how
much in a best of five do you really put
stock into the game that has been played
um not just today this morning but
throughout the entire tournament because
I know a best of five generally also has
like its own meta developing yeah I mean
usually what's going to end up happening
is you kind of get a good understanding
for what it is the other team trying to
accomplish in the draft and then how to
adjust to it is usually the at least for
us I think it's been a trickier part
Delta year so um yeah you definitely
like develop your own meta you kind of
like usually game one is like a feel
your opponent out kind of game and you
get understanding of like this is the
idea I had prepared this is the idea you
had prepared how do these two Clash so
now Gladiators kind of have to you know
show their hand they have to kind of mix
something up probably won't be seeing
gyro again might see some adjustments to
the bands so they don't feel like
they're in a position where they need to
force the gyro
um yeah as a gyro Enthusiast myself I
don't mind seeing the hero it's nice do
you think they misclick this one or no I
think they wanted it okay yeah would you
have chosen the same cosmetic H I don't
I'm not really sure what gyro Cosmetics
he had the the Cosmetic that he had was
the one that makes FL Cannon incredibly
visible like it was disco show out there
yeah that's a good
one all right awesome why not but I I am
actually curious aen so when we're
talking about this pangier coming out
early and when when it doesn't look good
how much stock did you guys put into
thinking about this pengle because
obviously you're going to consider it it
is gaming gladiators but you did let it
through a few times I think we've been
letting it through all year long um I
remember I had a I had a conversation
with I think thundra at some point and
they were like just bam Pango and you
win against Quinn uh but it's like the
hero doesn't feel that good so when you
play it yourself and like it doesn't
seem to work you're kind of surprised
cuz every time you play against it
you're like oh this is you know free
Lane for Nisha and then somehow like he
makes it makes magic happen but I think
the point about the Weaver is true like
it's very difficult for Pango to like
run to Weaver's Lane roll up and then
look to do something and then that I
feel like every time they make the
pengle work usually they manage to bring
the to sports mid Snowball the game and
then like you're scared on both Sid
Lanes well we're going to find out what
is happening in game number two as the
draft for it is right around the corner
climate pledge Arena DOTA FS around the
world get
ready team spirit versus game in
Gladiators Grand
Finals game
two welcome back to the draft panel
everybody this is going to be game
number two between spirit and gaming
Gladiators game one team spirit kind of
ran them over I think is fair to say so
that begs the question you know the
teams are feeling each other out it's a
best of five what is the adjustment
going to be for gaming I what would you
like to see them do first honestly I
would really like them to not Target
collapse as much in the bands I think
that they should play more to the
strengths then what I felt was like a
little bit of fear of the opponent I
feel like the Magnus man was maybe a bit
overboard I'm not too sure maybe it have
some scrim experience ver or something
but I think gaming strength has always
been playing through Quinn in the mid
lane and the way that you have to do
that is that you need stronger s lane
supports they target their band towards
maybe a bit of L maybe a bit of the
spirit safe Lane I think they were to
rotate on Mid a lot
easier uh to me it looked actually
pretty decent at the beginning for
gaming Gladiators like lanes were not
that bad and as soon as Spirits start
rotating super hard like and being super
active especially on car Weaver like
this 10 minute rotation like kind of
break the game apart for gaming
Gladiators at that point maybe we were
uh we should have not reacted to that at
some point or ignore something and find
a better like fight a bit later on like
so we don't lose the phase of game yeah
yeah I think my theory so far of like
what team spirit's trying to do looks
true with these bands like they don't
want Daio to play CK they don't want him
to play Weaver he has played other
Heroes like Alchemist Razer but those
are much later picks and if they are on
the first pick by the way gaming gliders
they chose first pick this game so they
wanted to change just the draft order up
just a little bit here and it's pretty
clear yoro is going to be like I will
take these away from you these Heroes I
don't play a lot of them but I'll play
them I'll play them just as good as you
if not better which is getting into your
head for sure but now you're in a
situation where drao he's been playing a
bunch of Weaver a bunch of CK and then
later on the draft this Al gets banned
it has to be a perfect razor game I
think datu's Hero's been very key for
gaming Gladiator success here and team
spirit is really focusing it down this
opening pick from gaming Gladiators
we've seen quite a lot it's been respect
banned against them a ton of games in
this tournament but obviously at some
point it will make its way through uh
this is not the first time they get to
play it on the main stage and you know
that's that's usually what happens when
teams get all the way to the Grand
finals is they just have so many good
strategies that you pick your poison
right and you see here Ace with a three
in one score line on the Primal beast
and you know Spirit probably feeling
pretty good about breaking his zero loss
streak on the lry it was four on0 before
the last game uh they took that one out
now it's time to take out arguably maybe
his second best hero of the tournament
yeah I think that just speaks of
confidence of team spirit I think last
game they left the pangular in they left
the lone in they will have something
prepared for each of the heroes
something to know is like they've sort
of been chilling for a bit you know they
get to watch gladers play a lot of games
they're going to have the time to
develop a counter trat for each one of
these picks I think what Fier said was
right on the mark like making sure that
daa doesn't play these aggressive
carries and keeping off the Weaver and
CK it looks really good for so I think
they'll continue to want to do the same
line of thought like just make sure that
your dur game's a bit so slow down
ooh and this was definitely a change
that they made in the draft they decided
to collaps Magnus will let it through
they played it only one single time at
this TI and that was in their last
series and collaps was an absolute
madman in that series doing what he was
doing at TI 10 just getting all the
skewers in the world here he didn't have
the strongest early game and I think if
you do put this in the off Lane I
correct me if I'm wrong probably not the
strongest off laner right now with the
way he builds but they played with a
Shadow Demon last time they just got a
lot of stacks up so maybe we can look
for them to ban out the Shadow Demon so
mag doesn't have that recovery option
yeah Shadow Demon is one of the best
heroes to counter Primal B Primal Primal
also is like it's countering him on all
stages of a game like it doesn't let him
get STS it's canceling his ulti you can
hide him when he get BB you hide your
teammate It's actually an amazing uh
hero against this I think it's probably
one of the best support counters to
Primal is there anything else you think
gaming are debating here that could be
an even more important ban like you know
the classic if if you haven't watched
DOTA for a bit you're like oh Magnus now
there's going to be an Empower carry is
there anything that is a really strong
Empower carry that's also good against
Primal no it's going to be the Shadow
Demons right on point there um what are
you thinking for Spirit here are you
saving your Tauros hero until the very
end or is there something valuable you
could grab now against the Primal and on
top of that do you expect this go off
Lane even Quinn has played Primal as
well um I would probably think they want
to wait just because there is that
potential of the flex I think when you
play with Magnus you actually don't need
to think FL down power too much for
example if you play some PA with Magnus
usually you actually still buy a battle
Fury just because dota's there's just a
lot of camps you don't want to make one
of your other cores run to another core
in order just to empower you I think
right now they should think that they've
given the Primal Beast right now they
need something that does enough damage
to kill I think probably do you know if
a was banned last game or is it just
I I think that's sort of rare for this
tournament honestly I think it was
picked and Bann pretty much first phase
in like most of the other games I've
seen I think they could look at
something a you see Phoenix is already
out and um the shallow Demon's out so I
think they want to make sure that they
get a support who can deal with this
Primal a looks pretty interesting like
um but it's also need a good partner on
Lane because it's not the strongest
laner I guess on uh easy Lane but moska
plays it very very good like on next
level Gladiators turn to enchantress
that's a five that is strong in Lane
I've heard um we going to do a cringey
me they're going to cringe the mid this
one with enchantress for sure this is
one of Mosa's like signature Heroes he's
really good at this and I think when you
do play a hero like Magnus who will take
a little more time might be a little bit
slower having that early game pressure
can help a lot and we'll have to see
like I believe barl probably still can
play the Magnus if they want to go that
route but normally when you do see it on
Spirit you have to automatically think
collapse but will G also automatically
think collapse as well or are they going
to respect it and think that it could be
a potential midliner yeah I think
enchantra is also one of the supports
eventually you're actually the one who
can kill the tanky Heroes moso he pretty
much always plays for the hurricane Pike
plus um moonshard and bkb like I saw sou
seller he's playing for like the solar
CR pipe but I usually don't see go go
for that type of build something
interesting to that point is we've uh I
was reading over a breakdown of Team
Farm distribution and for team spirit I
think moska has a higher average gold
per game than mea does right so they're
it's clearly by design that they're
giving uh moska a lot of space in the
game as position five and obviously this
as you guys pointed out can turn into a
carry do you think there's like a
specific type of four that is perfect
for that mindset that okay if an needs
to take some space at some point in the
game and get strong this is the type of
four you want to pair it with or is it
kind of not really that relevant and
you're just counterpicking specific
Heroes rather than making it du I think
it's mostly mirror play style like they
both share the responsibilities of four
and five in a way so it it kind of looks
like we're both playing four and five
and even sharing Waring a lot of times
so I think any hero mirror when to play
is going to fit with troll yeah and I
think Mir in general he just likes to
play the damage that just follows up he
plays a lot dark Willow um he plays the
Phoenix as well with the grimstroke
skywrath these types of heroes that
don't Farm very fast but they go for
kills and of course enchantress you know
how fast this hero can Farm as well so
poto just gets more gold by nature of
the heroes he plays but I do like how
gaming gladers they're sticking to their
guns quite literally here with the morta
yet again for tofu here and I like this
combination a lot with the Nature's
profit as well you just come in you
sprout them you get a free Deadshot
Target on the Sprout and you just push
them back so a lot of synergy there do
you think there is going to be the
necessity for nous profit maybe even to
rotate like how does this Lane match up
go between what we're assuming is a 5%
position Edge playing in the safe Lane
versus a for mua off Lane is that is
that one of the matchups that mua will
struggle in or can she hold her own I
think it's a pretty St B Ling for Mora
it always depends a little bit for ench
there's a little bit element of RNG
sometimes you want the hard Camp to
spawn even if you're playing against
ench cuz you think you can control as
side but then it spawns wildkins and
you're like oh I guess I lost a lane but
I think especially with a fa void who's
like a more stable laner that you don't
harass as much you can actually use this
to your advantage on Morton side I think
most likely this is going to be ace
Primal if you have Primal Beast
together you can like um P has to be
really careful on the edge he can get
100 to zero really quickly in the
lane and there's the Grim stroke that
you are mentioning fear coming out to be
expected on mirror great partner for
magnos and overall it's pretty good hero
against Primal to overall void and
magnos is one of the best like partners
and this this is looking scary if it's
the game get delayed a bit because we
have insane amount of AI BB control
and I think if you're gaming gliders
here if you're fitting the bill of like
meeting Dao as hero the hero that kind
of stands out the most that they're
successful with this would be an
alchemist around this point and a lot of
the other Heroes he might want to go for
like the Razer you're not going to pick
that versus Faceless Void potentially if
they want to it could be an okay wraith
King game the carry it would be a bit
faster so I really like The Wraith King
actually I think it'd be really stable
in Lane right now I think they should
want something that they can leave alone
in the safe Lane if you have the W King
in the safe Lane even if your lane start
to go slightly bad you can just go to
the bat camps and this allows Fon to
make the plays I think right now their
number one priority is making sure that
their supports are freed up to rotate
onto
Med will this fit the bill though for
how Dasio has been playing in your face
hitting these really fast timings and
running at you definitely the same style
as like an alchemist but probably comes
on a little bit slower because you don't
get that blink as early but if he has
good laning stage they could do what
they need him to do are we getting a
little bit ahead of ahead of ourselves
here is this guarant to be Cari King
we've seen gaming glad off lane and they
could put the Primal mid I feel like the
flex is still there uh what would you
guys rather like to see if it was if you
were in their shoes right now do you
think The Wraith King one or the three
fits the Bild better here 10 second uh
I'd be really happy with the prim be on
three and W King on one but they
definitely could do it they could switch
it up if they even like at the end of
the draft they could pick another hero
that's flexible to our roll and just
keep Spirit guessing it wouldn't be a
bad idea I think personally though like
the only other her I can see sort of
slotting into the safe Lane would be the
alchemist that Fe mentioned and I'm not
too sure like if he does that job better
than King I think he's a bit more
susceptible pressure so they are so they
are thinking that it can be an offline
raing in mid
Primal yeah we can still Pi carry hero
too but we are not really flexing that
much because losp is still on Tim Spirit
I'm just looking at what carry heroes
are left that if they get banned here
that's going to be good vers void is rth
King going to be the most punishing hero
for a Faceless Void in the laning stage
as well these are all the decisions that
they
to with already greedy if it's an off
laner which would give you more
techically as carry to things but a lot
of the good ones that can be faster are
probably just going to get removed this
is quite a rare sight in the last phase
right to see a team ban one carry and
one off laner I think most of the time
you kind of commit to the one idea okay
this is the biggest threat is that they
put the heroes in this way but the way
Spirit seems to be approaching this is
these are the two specific Heroes that
cause the most problem for our Faceless
Void it seems like um do you guys think
this lone Droid B would have been or
this l Droid would have been a really
big problem for their safe Lane to deal
with I feel like that should have been a
spectre maybe to be honest you yeah also
watching a spect I thought to to point
it out like it uh it might give the
tempo what we needed because this hero
now like is really really aggressive and
it cannot add up to the F on global
pressure can't really get chronoed
either right like Magnus initiations
kind of get ruined by this hero it's a
little bit different you don't have the
global until you get the agms but still
whenever you think about playing verus a
face of void you want to play a hero
that just doesn't show up to the fights
with Illusions or has two lives or can
just have infinite jump from like
anywhere on the map so that could be a
good choice if they do want to put this
Primal into the mid lane these actually
are two pretty decent mid bands for
Primal as well both necr invoker I think
have pretty good match ups for S so I
think they might be looking to get a new
carry
here
10er B protecting against the EMP for
The Wraith King regardless of role team
I think it's it's their okay more
FL well this her is like pretty decent
in Lane versus the Magnus cuz you can
match his hum long his base damage
there's really no kill threat as well
with the Magnus against the morling so
that does help a lot and of course the
attribute shift will help what if you
get Chronos spared but this hero is slow
and this is not how G has been winning
most of their games by Dau just sitting
back and hitting timings they've been in
your face so it looks like game's
adapting to the series they might sort
of have a read cuz they have a furin
versus grimstroke which I think is a
very favorable
support coming Circle here um but I
think if morling wins his Lane then he
can actually be a hero that's sort of
impossible to kill on the map and he's
actually pressuring a safe Lane but you
have to win your lane in order for that
to happen uh I believe this match up the
morphling against Magnus was the exact
one that Spirit played against lgd in
the upper bracket is that correct I
think that was how they tried to solve
nothing to say Magnus do you think the
conditions here are equally good
obviously Spirit did come out ahead in
that game with yoro on the morph uh or
is there something to be worried about
for Dau
it's a different type of game I would
say because in the last game like
collaps was playing CK just crushing the
lanes which allowed joro to get the farm
and spirit has proven that in late game
they're that type of team to take
it all right that is uh that's going to
conclude the draft for us here we are
going to go over to a coach interview
with seey from gaming
Gladiators thank you very much yes I am
joined by see why of a gameing
Gladiators a tough game one but whenever
these these post game discussions happen
you're obviously being able to say
everything that we see the entire game
your players only have half the
information so whenever you're
debriefing do you spend much time
telling them this is why things went
wrong based off of all the information I
have or do you mainly focus on forget
about it here's what we're going to do
for game two uh it depends a bit
sometimes you need to readjust like um
how you value certain Heroes for example
in the draft but it also depends a bit
on Lanes let's say the lanes go bad okay
it's reset go next game right you don't
want to be too affected about it also
depends like this tournament I can hear
the communication so I can hear it's
like chill still like we're like not
stressed or anything like that so I
don't really need to do any work in that
regard so I kind of consider what I have
to say and what I don't have to say and
then take it from there how about the
lanes for this game we got good
expectations on how the first seven
minutes are going to go for you I have
good expectations so uh I hope my boys
can live up to it I hope you guys are up
for it also cuz we're getting ready for
game number
two this game needs to start off very
well for gaming Gladiators because while
this may be a best of five this game too
feels particularly important Avery I
mean last game Spirit they took your
best trait your speed took it away from
you and turned it right back around they
ended that game so fast and this time
they're going to take the late game and
the scale right void Magnus this is a
lineup that is very happy to go into
that late game and particularly when you
have your Toro in the range of this face
is voided is a fearsome Beast this is a
strat that goes all the way back to I
remember TI 6 ti5 era where people are
developing the Magnus Wings gaming were
a team that took this Strat all the way
to the Grand finals we're happy to play
this Magnus with the void particularly
on Shadow so this is a throwback for me
being back in Seattle seeing this once
more on the main stage here we're going
to see what team spirit can do to get to
that late game once again against gaming
who have continually punish teams for
the Greed for the slowness for the uh
willingness to go to 60 to 70 minutes
they just don't let want to let you get
there but here they've gone for kind of
a hybrid draft right going for more in
their own hands on Daio a hero he is
perhaps more Infamous more than Infamous
more than for than famous for yeah in
some sense well I mean a uh the right
kind of performance on a TI final that
could change the entire narrative about
his morphling he's going to try and do
just that by taking away and taking down
y Toro's Faceless Void but there's also
some other notable Heroes I feel like we
focused a lot on Yuro in that last game
for a good reason he had a monster
performance but there's also some other
big ones here for team spirit I'm
looking at that mosa enchantress man I
feel like this is enchantress and Chens
they are really scary in this current
Meta Even if we don't see them all the
time I mean we saw the way that Chen
work for G Gladiators and moska is going
to try and make that enchantress work
for the laning phase enchantress is here
both these teams really highly value and
contest her's been banned against gaming
a lot so they opted to take it away here
it's also her can deal pretty well with
Primal beast in those mid games with the
enchant ruining his charge in I don't
know when I saw that inch come out it
gave them the tempo they needed with a
Magnus opener to feel really good about
it so they just don't fall behind too
much on the lanes and a quick little
body block to push it under the tower
here to try and secure the equilibrium
very heads up play Dao Reddit got a
block of his own and it will end up
outside the tower so nice headit up play
by Dau to counteract that as they're
going to start three top maybe looking
for a cheeky kill on the furion who's TP
up
here yeah that would actually be uh an
interesting idea but they quickly
abandoned that celery waves goodbye to
the enchantress as moska heads back down
to that bottom Lane which is going to be
ace and tofu in the muera plus wraith
King the double Undead hero Against The
Faceless Void of yoro and a very deadly
Lane as well we've seen a lot of like
the waith king Dark Willow come back
that was a classic a couple TI ago
wraith King Mor equally as strong you
get the insta stun into silence into
Deadshot pushes you back in your attack
speed so you can't fight skeletons are
hitting you very high kill threat on
this Lane and a lot of pushing power if
you start to run away with it so this is
an off Lan for G they want to go very
well they want Ace to drive the tempo
and the objective control of the game
which is something he didn't get to do
last time because team spe brought the
gank parade to him right so that's a big
question as well do Spirit decide to
commit the same resources into shutting
Ace down this time around and does that
just inadvertently free up more room for
Daio on a hero that I feel like has a
better time this game than the gyro did
in that last one it's a stronger hero
The Meta and decent matchups and yep
already on the board yeah you said this
combo is deadly any sort of four
position that can output some good
damage off that R fire blast you got to
be careful if you're a support in Lane
gaming Gladiators will find the opening
kill and this early game is going to be
a question for gaming in terms of how
much they get out of it because they
have the fury on the can TP accelerate
the lane ganks they have a primal Beast
who can just gobble up runes gang s side
Lanes very early he is the king of it
maybe not a hero we've seen Quinn play a
lot but one he is practiced very well in
pubs recently and is very comfortable on
so this could be an incredibly fast
early game just in terms of the gank
potential not necessarily just taking
your Towers which is also a reason if
that r King Lane goes really well for
gaming it's a lane they can easily
rotate to cuz again the kill thrat is so
damn High the heal too much and now
they're going to turn back around with
the Nature's attendance leveled
up and Ace will take a bit of damage as
he heads back in but yoro doesn't want
to miss his CS right now lanes are going
pretty well for uh despite that early
First Blood we got the Pango taking the
top spot on the Cs chart nice
Deadshot see how much Laurel can do with
this it was kind of a quiet Pango game
last time around right I I think Quinn
was struggling to to find his openings
and if this is a hero you can get to
play your Tempo game to control the
runes combat where Quinn wants to go
with the final Beast you can definitely
turn some of those ganks around I think
that's what L's looking more more than
being the aggressive right I think him
just going in these Lanes is going to be
difficult cuz you don't have a lot of
damage W but if gam over extend dive you
under one of these s side L tier ones
then suddenly the Pango can come in with
a counter gank and the ring Thunder and
turn things around you're really happy
with that type of gameplay here cuz
again you're farming it up you got
Magnus Faceless Void you know gaming are
going to go into you this is a hard Duo
to match up against you throw that
Inkwell on the Magnus he pulls you
closer with the shock wave you get hit
by the stun and then that stun leads
into a free skewer back so even
underneath your Tower you are not safe
and the Grim Shard could be really nice
as game as well just throwing it on
these cores that want to jump in get the
extra you know debuff them out reset the
the fight or the Primal these types of
interactions could help them take the
team fights in the mid game when they're
likely going to be behind a little bit
in terms of the speed right cuz gaming
are pulling a decent position out in
terms of the lane phase here doing
pretty well on their cores in terms of
Cs they gave him the harpy that's going
to make a big difference in this bottom
Lane going to die now but does some
decent economic damage and he's got a
small little hell bear to work too I
mean it's also just time time yor gets
to sit down here vers that eventually
will kick him out qu amping up the
pressure here has a little bit of an XP
Advantage pushing this triple ranged
wave I mean this is it's pretty rare you
get three range creeps being pushed into
the tower L will clean it all up no Rome
coming in early here just way too high
on the the HP to make it look enticing
and of course these Sid Lanes vital to
your game plan still he's just going to
go for it here comes the rotation though
miror gives him the in swell under under
the tower but he stops him Midway
through the charge and Quinn caught
underneath the tower will
die sometimes greed is good and
sometimes you get punished for it mea
happy to counter that push Laurel ahead
in the XP now you're going to have a
rolling thunder what a sprout collapse
cut down a tree but he was still stuck
on the corner there did have some stick
charges to work with though and so he
will survive for now they wanted to be
able to punish the fact that mea had to
TP into that mid lane but couldn't quite
finish the job it's a game about
pressure every time one of these
supports makes a move you need to create
the pressure somewhere else so the enemy
just can't Clump on you get the numbers
you too gets pushed back into the
silence oh he time walks up now he's
still kind of in a sticky spot here
gaming Gladiators are going to try and
run him down look at him throw the blood
grenade but he'll make the difference
he's going to show up with that Rolling
Thunder do manage to finish him up with
the two supports but laurl he'll be
collecting some heads here even the wolf
gets a couple hits in stuck there on the
corner but that's okay the swash Buckle
will finish the job a lot of XP going
into the Pango on the down here yoro
little sad he died there and doesn't get
it for himself but I mean that's
sometimes the life of a Faceless Void
versus a lineup that is going to
pressure you is going to go for that
kill and if it was a lot cleaner maybe
gaming can just walk that off but team
spirit they get the rotation in suddenly
these Pango having a terrific game off
of that in the turn around mid and those
are those counter turns that lel's
looking for right yeah Force the ra King
in force this moring into an aggressive
situation maybe Quinn Dives you and
that's when you get the strike here
Arcane Rune picked up for Quinn this is
a really nice Rune on the hero see IFC
pops it here to try and deal with mea
the silence is going to last a while can
he get it yes Quinn very fast with the
trigger there does manage to get him
collapse going to try and dissuade Quinn
of that notion and he does manage to do
so successfully keeping him off his
support and the quelling saving me at
the end from the Sprout so value pick up
already for him Tower Arcane run still
in the bottle so Quin can still look for
a rotation off this and he probably
wants to I mean his early game is
getting a little slow here and you have
threat on the sidelines right this is
where the prime will be break really
hard really fast gets momentum going for
the team that's your theoretical ideal
you just shove in mid make the move wisd
run there is a
furrion there is there's always the
opportunity of the celery to try and
make a move but I feel like the teams
have been really good at protecting
their wisdom runes against invasions
particularly against the Nature's profit
more times than not it seems like
Nature's profet tries to make that kind
of move he just walks into a trap just a
hard gamble if you use your teleport for
that you're dead on the map for 60
seconds and your chances to get it
should be minimal in a TI Grand Final I
want to say yeah good deward there
that'll help because Quinn wants to be
able to make moves particularly with
this Arcane Rune which he's going to put
to use now caught a mid Shield crash so
that ability no longer there with the
two support rotations it's easy to kill
Laurel exactly what they're looking for
combine the calling Deadshot with this
Primal Beast anybody goes down to it at
this point and this is where you want to
ramp up the speed start getting the map
in a position where you can can just
guarantee the power runes for Quinn and
get the connections going and hopefully
lead to like jungle Invasion right
because the one thing you have to think
about with the Magnus is the stacks and
if their carry just gets to sit in
Triangle on double ancients and clear
through them at that point in time the
earlier you take down these tier ones
the earlier you get aggressive OBS out
the happier you're going to be when that
period comes another Power Rune should
be secure from Quinn here oh these runes
are getting a little crazy no that
skewer plays against collapse as he does
a ton of damage onto himself thanks to
the trample from Quin blocked out by his
own Sprout though he's going to try and
get to the other side of this Cliff LL
does hop down to chase after him though
LL showing the power of a non-real hero
in his hands as he will take that Rune
away from Quinn no haste I mean that
that's what of those situations you
almost rather take the haste R it's so
damn good on your hero collapse will
suicide himself to take Quinn out in the
process yeah got to have to be careful
with those skewers against the Primal
Beast that kind of movement could be
deadly look at this just a quick
rotation from the supports power of
enchantress early creep takes down 2/3
this tier one mid yeah didn't even feel
like that was a real move but they still
got a lot of this tier one Tower damage
out from it once again it's G responding
to some early objective pressure the
whole time this is happening it's also
space on the sidelanes which means the
atoro got the catch up a bit he's not
the one getting ganked or killed by the
calling here very happy with that Ace
not able to force him off Lane yet
however gaming doing a bit of stacking
of their own and maybe that selling they
took out of that game one right like you
go in game one you try and run Spirit
over instead they run you over okay this
is not a team we're going to be in 20
minutes not a team we're going to beat
in 25 maybe we go back to some of other
tricks other things up Our Sleeve like
the efficiency on the map this is a team
that is stacked their whole way through
the season going back to it now when it
matters and particular particular
strength of Western Europe in general so
I love those DPC matches throughout the
year stacking was a big factor for all
of those teams Ace he does have The
Reincarnation here but it looks like
team spirit want to try and burn it away
from him the skeletons will push back
though
is chased away brother against brother
here who skeletons are better well right
now it's going to be Quinn trying to
jump in but immediately stopped by
Laurel once again with the counter
initiation Quinn's trying to get out of
here but he's going to be cough inks
well plus the sil is going to try and
trample his way over the left hand side
and he is slowed down pull back in by
collapse though oh and a chronosphere
actually locking away these two other
cores right in Fr this Tower celer he's
trying to stop him now as they turn back
around on Ace trying to finish him up
there goes that reincarnation Daio
doesn't have much man to work with and
on the Fresh Life a going to be pulled
back underneath that Tower again just
like Quinn they are in trouble now Dao's
under this one as well surrounded by
five Heroes he's going to start
desperately morphing in his strength and
try and wait for him over the left hand
side but with all of this damage he just
cannot get far enough away gaming
Gladiators will lose all three of their
cores and that attempt at a fight at
bottom Lane that is the danger of making
an aggressive move into this pangle
grimstroke the turn around potential is
just so damn high and time dilate
absolutely ruined Daio as he goes in
that engagement gets time dilated can't
do anything for the rest of the fight
and of course Quinn he ate the big ult
still trying to make something happen in
this early game with a very aggressive
mid that can do it but he's just
struggling her's a bit too tanky for him
to bring down alone and the combinations
they haven't been exactly on point for
gaming this will give a really nice bump
to Laurel who is just beasting on these
early game fights it's going to be a
very fast pangle diffusal in this game
and these are some Heroes that are
susceptible to Mana right you're looking
at two strengthes and a morphing that
also doesn't like his Mana getting
burned with an early diffusal back to
clearing some Stacks the net worth still
looking pretty good for ging but the
fights fights are just not going their
way particularly when you know The
Wraith King wants to rush this Radiance
as quick as possible we which means an A
Shard he really doesn't want to have to
buy that until at least after the
radiance there's definitely in timing
here where this Pango could punish Ace
heavily especially since it's just done
is 1130 Arcane Boo diffusal this is
crazy fast in a game where they maybe
expected Laurel to not have the freest
time right up against the Primal Beast
with a furion who can
rotate they're supposed to shut him out
early win that lane and then later on to
the game as a primal Beast you could
just bkb and grab the Rolling Thunder
ball and stop it immediately right look
what's waiting for him some good old
stacks for the mag lineup this is
another downside of gam not securing
those early team fight wins you can't
invade enemy side of the map this early
and Laurel's just going to clear through
it all diffusal going to help him he's
so big right now he's got a shield Rune
to boot so they're going to be looking
to take a fight it's also going to be
the blink timing for collapse he's going
to finish this off off the stack just
rush it out here look for a big blink RP
skew on a core continue to slow the pace
down here spear are going to be happy to
use their SS for big core kills so the
question on gaming side is what do you
do when those Els are on cool down right
how much can you get off the map how
much can you push the lanes and look for
kills Quinn once more looking for
something to get his game going here
just can't find anything good read by
moska di away into the trees there out
of sight from
Quinn and as a result that's going to be
yet another rotation that fails one way
or another gaming Gladiators whether
it's running into a five stack of Team
spirits and they lose the fight or the
Smoke's just not working out for them so
much of their early aggression with this
Primal Beast has been completely SED and
now team Spirits are sitting in a pretty
happy position I would say the net worth
is dead even but it does feel like team
spirit have answered gaming Gladiators
in all the moves they wanted to make
early I mean there's a lot of Magnus
teams over the history T I think all of
them will say if you are even at the
15-minute Mark with a MAG lineup you're
winning the game like you're happy cuz
you know this game is going to get
extended you're going to out Farm the
enemy you're going to in the outscale
him now a lot can happen in those fights
and this lineup from gaming can scale
very hard we've seen Primal Beast go
very deep in these later
games follow up silence
Heroes that can also happen yeah this is
the move the game of Gladiators they
they were trying to play off this being
able to get numbers movement right like
the Primal Beast and the Nature's profit
offer so much Mobility around the map
they should be able to outnumber team
spirit and find openings like that it's
what Cel wants to do for sure every time
you get one of these pickoffs with the
fear on you get to farm their side of
the map you get deep Wards up it's going
to set up for your next play and then
your econom is just going to explode and
you get some extra items on this fear
and he can control the fight the a very
good this game with the Roo and disarm
right this is a great fury on a game
nature is going to do some mad work here
if he can get anything else to help his
team survive in the Chrono in the RP Cel
is going to be a force to be reckoned
with and he can continue to shove these
waves in as well as Spirit continu to
play this game slow continue to farm up
Laurel with their Empower going to
work but that is a successful move for
gaming and a period where collaps didn't
really find that opening with the
blink we'll have to settle for some Farm
find an interesting note there just no
hand amidases in this game wraith King
Faceless Void both Heroes that have
bought it throughout this tournament
sometimes but feels like as the
tournament's gone on particularly
probably because the way the game of
Gladiators has stomped through some
games their are teams who've been a bit
wary about picking up that greedy item I
mean Midas is a crutch item let's be
honest M Midas is an item for you know
the bottom 14 teams it's not really a
grand finals item you know you got to if
you're worthy of a true Pantheon and you
don't need the extra GPM you're going to
collect it off your enemies
here see can can do that he's still
trying to find something with this blink
or maybe he's just happy empowering his
other cores and letting them take the
bulk of the net worth yoro still pretty
much untouched during this period just
going Mas Manus into the melstrom and
Power on top of it I mean this void is
going to keep up and farm even with a
Radiance Skeleton King am I allowed to
say that farming up the entire
map he will match him oh laurl is
essentially there they grab him mea can
stop some of this though throws out in
silent thinks well oh so much burst
damage though zeler hit him big with
that one he got off the shield crash
though and those Shields are keeping him
alive they need a bit more damage but
now he's deeping away
goodbye oh no gaming Gladiators got to
feel so bad about that a pickoff on
Laurel the highest net worth in this
game would been a dream opening for them
and that was one of the few openings
you'll have against this guy because he
closing in on the Lincoln fast just not
crisp enough La walks it off I think he
even misclicked his swashbuckle there
Dano on the edge of the Chronos sphere
now that's an idea team spirit said oh
used all those resources bottom Lane huh
it'd be a shame if your car got picked
off wouldn't
it a heavy cost indeed to missing this
gank as lurl just plays with his food
and they're going to put those SS to use
on Daio every time anytime you can just
collect the morphle in this game you're
super happy about about Itor will just
continue to farm says give me the
freebie and back to the Jungle it's
coming down to Ace right now right I
mean it feels like it comes down to Ace
in a lot of game games but yeah
particularly right now he's the
strongest her on the map he can create
the pressure he can do things like this
where just solo create an opportunity
they're going to find both
supports will walk it off yeah he's got
it back away he showed so many Heroes up
there killing moska earlier moska again
continued to play very aggressively I
mean the train protector he was on
gaming glass Gladiator side of the map
all the time because he was invisible
but this enchantress seems to have a
similar game plan he's going to be
playing up in gaming Gladiator face and
that does even if it costs him a death
every once in a while it does create
information and space for his cor
particularly when the Chrono and the RP
are down this is where gam can pretty
much Run the game of the map choose
which objective they want and claim it
for free there's no way you're fighting
them without those big olds all cool
down without collapse being stronger
skewer on skewer play you're coming with
me up into the TP point from Quinn
collaps as long as he keeps the damage
on him he's not going to be able to
Blink away and Quinn will finish the job
great move from gerio those are the kind
of plays you need to see here if you
want to be able to take down the best
team at this tournament you need to be
able to pull off some solar moves like
that and create the pressure that's
going to create openings elsewhere and
suddenly toio this stolen power is
pretty damn nice he can throw it on the
ra King he can throw it on the Primal
especially bonus damage on Primal Quinn
is going to be very happy with that that
is something we can see in a lot of
these fights probably going to be the
best steal for Dau out side of maybe
time dilation throwing back against team
spirit or just creating his own
grimstroke
combination these are good morphling
combos he can use for the fights and the
team Quinn starting to pick up the pace
and instantly silenced and Beautiful
Soul bite and now it ink swell up
pinball coming through Straight to the
heart of gaming Gladiators Dau is
already burned out of most of his Mana
pops his wand but Daio he needs to be
able to get away from both and yoro and
he's been burned out no chance there
game Gladiator still have a chance
though would be able to fight back
around ace in his Radiance but without
their carry it's not looking great is
Ace going to be burned out of his first
life can they fight around this second
one Quinn sticking around they certainly
don't want to be given up Ace like this
fear shot back coming up at 2 seconds
here yeah yoro says my cool Down's back
can push
this just not enough reach not necessary
really for team spirit right no no
reason to give them an opportunity like
that he could stretch out claim all of
this map space you've just fought for
and farm away now I do think this late
game is not 100% right we're talking
about mag void it is very powerful
you're going to get some pickoffs like
this for sure and Empower is going to
clean up the map but there's like some
weird things that can happen with raai
King a there there's some weird things
that happen if theu gets a free angle in
the fight and can like clean up the
backline with morling first and power
himself you know grimstroke SW himself
yep it's going to be tier one down in
the bottom Lane as Laurel marches
forward confidently with his lincol
because what's really going to catch him
it feels like he's most of the time
going to have a chance to be able to
escape if gaming Gladiators ever try and
jump him here it's a really fast Lincoln
as well this is mag Pango in its prime I
think a hero that is not afraid to fight
off cool they're really going toy the
Tormentor right in front of gaming
gladiator's base that is crazy but they
just did it four Heroes that's all they
needed meanwhile celery being G on by
utoro he just gets a bit of a poke gets
reaction out of gaming Gladiators Ace
will try and punish him but just no
followup yeah he needs a lot more celer
is going to try and Chase up the TPS are
coming in here tries to block him out
with the Sprout but yoro is running free
Dao chases after him gets him with the
time dilation though but it is a very
very CL from tachio but he gets it he
gets that kill now turns back around on
the collapse oh RP right in front of
that tier two but silenced up just in
the nick of time before his secur he
wants more yeah he does he sees this
opportunity what a beautiful entrance
from Daio into this game that is the
power of stolen time dilation plus the
time walk right infinite Chase potential
suddenly faceless vo can't do the same
back and Dao says two can play at that
game yoro I can get aggressive too and
make it work just creates an opening out
of nothing there off a chase that felt
you know like what is Ace doing here
he's wasting his time not at all
everything coming together going to
propel celery up that board as well
imagine you have that a Wrath of nature
here right suddenly chases like this
become a lot easier oh yeah and yoro
he's just still looking for that big
dispel item his choice will be Mana
first over the bkb but until that's outu
has decent opening in these fights and
you got the RP out of that yeah it
actually just leads gaming Gladiators
into more opportunities
perhaps that a finished for celery if he
can fly it out okay that is something
that can bounce through lock these
Heroes down create more openings for the
r King Primal to just get in there and
set up that front line Second Tormentor
will go team spirit's Way With A
Shard so now they've got a Shard on both
of their
supports that's pretty funny I think
that the miror one grimstroke that's so
much better for them hard dispel to be
able to help save this Pango or this
Faceless Void when they need it most but
maybe there's just too much Firepower
some of these times as we can see from
gaming Gladiators when their cor start
linking up and they're picking up the
pace now Daio he's just swarming forward
seeing if there's anybody else to be
able to catch
deep on team spirit side of the map and
this is the part where team spirit needs
to be able to slow down the game the
momentum is beginning to play against
them this is where the map becomes
difficult you have skeleton shoving in
one wave you have wrath and nature
pushing all the lanes the morphling is
not afraid to show right now he has
manions on top of it and the Primal if
he's in the fog it creates a scary
situation with the pickoff potential
they're just getting more information
than team spirit right now there are
still very deep Observer WS them a
potion got out but you can't really get
there and use them and they're not
scouting any right now is every's on top
of him that uh that Shard is pretty
helpful when it comes to the Sprouts but
it may not save him from this he's going
to be surrounded he'll create a little
bit more time a little bit more space in
fact he's going to go for the TP away
and there it is okay they do managed to
stop that that would have hurt gaming
Gladiators a lot if they let him get
away from that solid space I'm sure is
what he'll say yeah absolutely time to
try and get to the dispel item on yoro
as collapse will finish
Harpoon so he can't really deal with
time dilation in the fight if it comes
out it's a very aggressive item he can
lock people down guarantee the skewer
better but if the fight starts on him
could backfire and Quinn's still working
towards that
heart so gam looking for the next big
damage items that are going to let them
ramp this game up and of course Ace
still sitting top at fretty here he's
the big objective driver so if he
decides that they need to force tier two
go for Roshan where they want to watch
fight and how it's up to Ace right now
as he is the front line calling for a
smoke looking for some kind of pick off
here the right kind of opening they
could translate this into a quick roast
T exactly they're looking at the corner
of the map so anybody that dies down
here yor is instantly going to go in the
pit he might just do it anyway yeah
gaming Gladiators say they look inside
see if it's actually gam who's taking
that ran that's going to be pretty tough
to deal with you Toro with that Shard
jumping around with ink swell on top of
him so even if you catch him Midway
through his time walk and stop him from
leaping back back into play there is
that disbel that can come out that's why
you want to create a situation where he
has to choose between Chrono in the
front line in the heart Primal or you
know the ra King with two lives oh if
they make this move fast enough it could
be massive for gaming Gladiators they
have a double damage in more flings
bottle and taking to this fight in time
team spirit may get wiped and lose the
Roshan fight and they are not doing this
fast enough gaming Gladiators are going
to get here and it looks like team
spirit have made the right Le they're
going to smoke backing themselves away
see if they can fin the opening on
gaming
Gladiator on The High Ground bkb
immediately goes out now he has to turn
and Chase but he's not going to be close
enough team spirit got something big out
of they do that's going to be able to
hit all those Heroes the RP do lock down
the two Heroes they jumped into the RP
dato dies immediately going to have to
do all the damage from here on out but
the Rolling Thunder is dangerous and
slows him down with the bashes and the
Rolling Thunder hits and there's no
chance and now they leave Quinn yeah
trap him inside that chronosphere his
bkb is gone get the rest oh it's gameing
Gladiators who had an opportunity there
to be able to upset but now just what
they feared the most which was losing a
fight and giving the ran to team spirit
that may have just occurred it's going
to switch the side so they're going to
have to run up top they might not have
enough time before gaming respond I mean
you got to remember they can TP to this
dire Outpost up here as well if they
still have off cool down but damn what a
heads up RP from collapse that is a team
fight salvaging RP as the wrath of
nature just got him all on the backside
and dilation was thrown out early here
so right there it goes on Quinn but that
opens the fight for Daio by a decent
margin just didn't I don't know I mean
he just RPD him there's no way around it
yeah they only had one stun to work with
Dao just makes a complete misread of the
situation there maybe thought the stun
was going to latch and be longer but
there's a lot of bailout here in the
second that goes wrong on the morphling
this fight is just completely over yoro
is going to clean house you cannot give
too many of these openings upside though
like we said is this Ro on switch sides
and the respawn timers were not too long
here so dire side going to work for G as
they come back into this map and stall
out the RO a second time I think you
just man up for it here because you know
RP and krono are on cool down yeah 100%
And team spirit I mean it would be a
pretty bold move to try and take this
fight without their ultimates no they're
just looking for the pickoff they not
going to find it clear the wave but this
contest it's all on Lael with the
Rolling Thunder maybe they can take the
afterwards he's thinking about going in
with this in well he tries jump in see
if they can get the skewer pickoff no
such luck gaming Gladiators Retreat very
defensively after claiming that agis
they know team spirit are bold enough to
make a move like that they respect
it now'll back away Daio they'll try and
get his farm into the silver Edge which
is a great way to be able to find some
of those backline Heroes I mean I think
that that grimstroke is a big problem
for them it is the link and the dispel
off the swell are both really nice here
especially when you just throw the cell
onto the Faceless Void or the Magnus
they get a free jump and if they get
stun you just bail them out right I
think we're going to see that the whole
game it's going to make sure that both
collaps andoro can hold their bkbs or
the mantha for as long as they want here
and Mira can bail them out of course you
can also just throw it on the Pango and
let him roll in yeah speaking of the
Pango his item timing was definitely
delayed quite a bit but he's finally
going to get there he got that Lincoln a
while ago but the agony scepter that he
was looking for next will finally be
complete hurricane Pike for moska so the
damage starting to heat up here for
Spirit as they're going to spread it AC
Cross Four effective cores going into
this late game that is why they love the
enchantress mka is going to start to
cause his own Mischief in the fight and
that pushes the question back to game in
in terms of how are you scaling in this
game right cuz right now you have an
Aegis you have a morling pushing towards
silver Edge a just hit his bkb timing
here and the heart is a couple hundred
off for Quinn so you have some really
strong fighting items coming out all in
the same interval here for gaming you
would really like a good team fight out
of this especially if the Chrono the RP
gets
or if you trade an AIS for it you might
be okay with that in the long run you
can at least find something on the back
side cuz right now you're looking at
yoro he has a mantha that's it he did
not go for bkb on the face of boy this
game he's just hyping up the damage here
abusing the fact he has a power going to
go for a later Lincoln sphere but it
will be collapsed with that bkb so it's
a question of who do you want to start
off and maybe the silver Edge is going
to give to rachio the option to put his
aggression to use and just start on a
support start on a cor give the vision
for a r King jump Vision means
everything here for gladiators as they
try and take these next few fights yeah
which means moska is a particular
nuisance to them as he once again leads
forward just using the creep to be able
to find information they got the har and
skewer back now we does have bkb locked
down by the RP but maybe the damage is
going to be enough it's going to be
close call Quinn starts walk it away
celer is going to jump in with the wrath
of nature soon coming out he tries to
use the ogre seal totem to get away from
the Rolling Thunder or they jump forward
on Daio they want to get something out
of this they see an opportunity surely
but they couldn't actually grab anybody
just lacking the disables glimmer C
posing problems for tachu as well and
just can't see anything to hit and team
spirit able to disengage after that
wrath of nature rooted them all which
means too wants to go back he's got an
opening here looks for it with the
chronosphere there were so grouped up on
gaming gladiators but he doesn't have
the vision he's now been grabbed
disabled they actually have that the
calling goes out he's on the other side
he actually gets away thanks well Time
Walk undo so much of the damage and now
gaming Gladiators have to play it a
little bit slow have to respect that
Soul bind they cleans themselves of the
ghost that silence is now gone the soul
bind is away he's still waiting for his
opportunity to get that c out two three
one in the back two in the front that's
going to be the aeges down for the
morling a second life for both him and
Ace though can yoro fight through this
one is he going to be able to get away
the shot R the entangle as well that's
enough they bring down the carry now for
the rest team spirit playing back into
this one one the end inks well now sker
locking him together Lao maybe he can
fight this one out Daio wave fors over
it trying to separate from his team a
little bit make sure this watch bule
doesn't edly decimate them like it does
tofu in the back lines Ace trying to
chase down the out but Daio dies as snor
he does manage to finish him off just on
the very tip just to be able to get that
kill before he falls goaps tries to skew
her away but locked down by quen in the
end cannot escape the inevitable which
is just too many lives on the side of
game and a buyback from gets another
Wrath of nature through that fight
lasted so damn long and of course you
had the Aegis on Daio the reincar on Ace
and Quinn just abusing This Heart region
on the back side of that fight the
Chrono was absolutely beautiful and you
say buyback on c three lives yeah game
of Gladiators just brought more numbers
than team spirit could possibly even
dream of it's like an eight on five here
right so you kill three or two and a
half in the Chrono you're going to take
Ace on the other side and they're all
coming back I mean that's exactly what
you want to use this AIS and
reincarnation
cre a situation where you set the fight
up towards the end the ult on cool down
and you just get an even Man fight and
that is when Daio can start to clean
house this morling he do some serious
DPS but damn were those ink swells a
problem they were catching so many
Heroes collapse gets to survive the
entire fight just right clicking people
the entire time and I thought LL was
maybe going to carry the end of this
Pango is doing so much DPS yeah but coll
I think saves so much of this fight
because if datu manag to live through it
then who knows how much damage they do
while team is dead but theing is gone
there goes a decent amount of their
pushing and threat for the ground
instead it's the fury gun and the
skeletons that push out it'll be ace who
collects it and this ra King is just
turning into a straight carry right now
this is not even a bad carry match up
vers the faces void if you have help to
do it just going to be an AC for Ace
here Shard to boot so you cannot mana
burn him out and he's going to be a
problem he's going to deal enough damage
create enough threat that you're going
to have to think about him first or at
least maybe skewer him in deep take him
out for free and think about when you
commit the cron or the RP cuz it's not
so straightforward anymore you can play
off some pangle or pokes
but the damage in the front Line's
coming through for gaman right now and a
lot of it does come down to Daio how
does he find the angle into the fight
who does he start on and does he get
caught in those ultimates cuz this Moran
is still incredibly susceptible to time
dilation post man he susceptable to just
getting Ed without that morph going out
if that happens so much your DPS goes
out the window soly that long fight is
no longer favorable for you it's so wild
to me how much utoro trusts his team in
this situation I feel like so many other
carries especially carries in this
tournament would have gone for a bkb to
help protect themselves but he seems to
just fully trust that Mera is going to
be able to back him up right I mean you
you think your Toro God is going to buy
a
bkb haven't been watching this man he's
going to go for Scotty up next which is
going to make him very tanky gaming
Gladiators may not let him get to this
point smoked for very very far forward
here yeah Radiance turned off for Ace
they're not showing too much on these
waves they wanted something so badly out
of that they used double scans to try
and find some sort of pickoff but
they're left with nothing team spirit
holding around their tier two they saw
something on that Ward and they'll
counter smoke it instead they're missing
the Scotty from yoro Big item versus
morling but he's happy to fight without
it
Tri we'll see nothing
how closely were you looking at the body
blocks here and AIS could depend on it
as they will bypass the vision
mechanisms level 20 for yoro he has
Chrono attack speed here plus this full
meon you get caught in this Chrono it's
a very different story than the last
fight how much room are you willing to
give up right now that charge they spot
celery chronosphere on the two of them
so he's going to bring down the support
first nice use to the dead shot there
that'll make sure Ace doesn't get
punished too much but chronosphere for a
f position I don't think G and
Gladiators mind that too much as long as
they don't lose control of the Roshan
pit during this window the upside is
that buyback still on cool down for
celery so they know they're getting the
4v5 out of that if they take down the
fury on first there's no way you're
committing for the r King there Deadshot
will prevent it
anyway another quick pick off for yoro
more gold into his pocket will finish up
to
Scotty now what about this next part of
this match up The Wraith King versus The
Faceless Void especially this wraith
King off Lane always going to be going
the agonum scepter at some point in time
that that Agony scepter is pretty
interesting against the burst that yoro
wants to be able to employ right he
wants to quos spere make sure that
there's one hero or maybe two that gets
no impact from the fight just like it
looks like Quinn oh he barely gets off
that but he is going to be slowed down
as soon as the dkb is worn away the time
dation kicks in a play and yeah team
spirit have caught him just good Vision
on the map let set up for this kill and
just to he was pushing towards that
Agony SE there you're talking about the
ra King eyes the Primal a will also play
a big part in these fights just breaking
these down removing some of the passes
letting them get easy kills on things
like the enchantress removing some of
the time off from the faces void any
extra bit you can gain an advantage for
Dao in these man fights is going to be
nice but I mean the ra King a is great
versus the SS it's just a question of
can you do anything with like the 5
Seconds you have afterwards right d
going to man up they're going to jump
onto this face vo team they can burst
him down once again there's that ink
swell heart dis spell time and attempts
collaps turn around get that RP on the
two of them locking down to Roi un
finishing off and now Ace going to come
back into this with not much the port
with no Quinn they knew they had the
numbers advantage and they take the bite
in the gameing Gladiators no matter the
cost he gets a jump away for stab helps
him out but it's not far enough there is
nowhere you can go the collaps and utoro
cannot follow that is a very bold move
when your Primal is dead he so much of
your damage so much of your burst damage
I mean again they're very close to
bursting yoro but the man knows his
limits Elvin T help tofu yeah a shot
from downtown claims the life of
utoro just as I cter curs the hell out
of him he gets shot
down well the man knows his limits but I
guess not every limit in Dota the
Tormentor are new will cut him some
slack but what a f from tofu just claims
it all there and now the Tormentor did
go to radiant so they get the kill on
yoro collapse gets The Shard that's a
1500 gold kill yeah that's a that's the
final Shard by the way team s to 36
minutes in have all the shards for their
team because they've claimed every
single Tormentor this is
crazy of course the Chrono was off cool
down so you're going to have some
downtime for your Toro where he would
have liked to have been up on the map
and used it surprised it burst
him he must have like time lock hit the
torment there I mean At Last At least he
can lap it off here cuz there's nothing
else you can
do back game though they still don't
have Ace they're still looking forward
with this smoke there's
thereo yeah this is I'm surprised gaming
Gladiators they're surprised that even
out
here up on The High
Ground he doesn't have a TP why are you
Quinn he's going to be able to get a
fource stab down to low ground but that
was an opportunity to get the pick off
and instead it's collapse who finds the
pickoff another ogre seal totem for
celer trying to keep him alive bump back
in oh the swashbuckle just outside of
the range there and they
do back into it D will be the first one
down Quinn he has bkb can he get it off
no too many stuns this D damage is
ramped up so damn fast oh colls got him
on the ink well yoro says you had your
fun you had your Cliff Walk but I'm here
to clean it up and Ace trying to get
away desperately blink is up he will get
out yes oh they got a scan on him yeah
turn that Radiance off son you need to
get the hell out of there you got to
hide you got to hide you can't be
farming right now there's that Shard
collaps pulls him back in a little bit
no Harpoon just yet though so he
couldn't get him any further yoro knows
what he wants right now and that is an
Aegis that is a RH fight that gam could
have just committed to it's also a fight
that 30 seconds of it had no yoro they
couldn't find anything they found an
inch off of double die between the
morling and the Primal beast and that's
it team spirit just way too good at
kiing these fights out not giving you an
opening that hame Pike did some serious
work sent Quinn back to na with his pal
RZ stuck up there but what else you
supposed to do you have to find the
openings you have to dive you only had
20 seconds without
yoro just none of it went your way and
now it's going to be AIS into his pocket
a cheese on the back and I guess
everybody can buy bkb at some point
it'll be his next item here at last to
seal the
deal he really wanted to save that
double damage rune for Laurel or for
yoro but uh little Triant will deny them
that opportunity still though team
spirit got to feel very good about this
next four minutes they've been winning a
lot of Team fights lately with that
extra life on your Toro he's already
been very aggressive leading a lot of
the charges for team spirit giving
information to collapse to follow it up
the second life I feel like there is
nothing to stop this man no if you get
caught in the Chrono you're gone yeah
that's it even if you're morphing I mean
who cares right the second you come out
of it you're basically dead this aags
from celery can only do so much and
suddenly the lanes are not getting
pushed in as deep as they once were
because this ow is just going to work on
these cores they're just mopping it up
at this point the skeletons and the TR
are just extra gold into their pocket
we're looking at 4 40 CS for yoro right
now just cleaning up these Lanes 500 for
Laurel by the way who has been swashed
by it feels like the entire map still
been a tremendous game here on the
pangle year he is and look at the
difference in the last hit Manan I mean
that is what Empower does that's what an
early mask of Manis into the the
melstrom does but it's also all these
summons going down the lanes so it's
inflated a bit but that's extra gold and
now Meo with an a this is a great dark
forra game right and these Soul lines
have been Landing there's not a lot to
block them you get the ri King you get
that Ora going back it's a great
illusion you get the morphling you're
going to clear house on the backline so
suddenly the scale from team spirit
starting to pick up the pace on their
supports and these are scary ones RP
straight up in the Top Lane he got
caught trying to hit that tier two you
can get nothing for free against team
spirit collaps and ni Daio that
opportunity Daio compliments on the
initiation but the damage is done gaming
Gladiators without their carry for for
70 seconds there's going to be some
serious damage coming their way that
just feels like a move that's it's based
on pressure right they feel like this
game is slipping away from they feel
like the scale is going to be instrum
animal Daio trying to make something
happen on the map and find a tier two
instead he will pay the price only for
an RP in exchange which is going to be
up pretty much when he's back up how
much do you want to push with this AIS
right now level 25 on the Faceless Void
already he already has the backtrack P
just going to make that bur even harder
and says this is enough farming I want
to end this game I want to end it now
how much do you have to take the fight
on your High Ground look at them they're
just trying to catch whatever they can
in the side lanes because well you don't
have a carry so there's not much point
in acting like you're going to defend
this mid lane just have to use Ace's
strength you have to find a way to use
this ra King a and the radiance burn get
something going in the fight over the
long
duration that is where the painer shines
and I mean Laurel has had to jump in
aggressively yet he's just playing
behind his other cores yeah be a free
Lane of racks here they're going to go
for number two Daio 3 seconds on the
spawn butterfly completed for yoro now
no mkb in sight you're going to have to
do this the hard way just charge in and
hope it goes your direction checking it
out seeing who's tping in Toro with the
Lincoln he's got an extra life he's got
a bkb in his back pack for that second
life and they got an opportunity from
collapse P celery out of position roio
going to try and use that Faceless Void
for to be able to help out but the
chronosphere goes work the old not
actually grabbing the real but still up
and he finishes off the morlix so easily
now the RP get the other two cores team
spirit so clean the extra goats come out
from the race King but doesn't really do
anything Ace just pops bkb on the second
life they do manage to get another pick
here on his celeries he tries to jump
forward they've got nothing left in the
tank on gaming Gladiators they are all
going to fall they're going to throw
their damage around the getting
popped as collapse got a little bit low
but in the fountain Marl
goes t a rampage maybe a double no
tofu's going to deny him that they're
going to call the GG andless pulled back
in a this one is a second Rampage to
finally close it off I mean why not add
to his total right this is the player
with the most Rampages in a single TI
run in history and he will add some more
to the stat page here as yoro just mops
them up at the end with way too much Dam
damage and once more G are sitting here
thinking what the hell are we supposed
to do against this team we can't outpace
him we can't push him we can't outscale
him we're having troubles in the team
fights we're losing the towers first
this man's playing Faceless Void in a
meta where no one else was really
willing he got you on the Weaver he got
you on the Faceless Void team spirit got
you on the Peno on both sides they
defeated the Panko and Laurel took it
into his own hands I mean there was so
much in that early game where Laurel he
was controlling so much of the tempo and
he knows it too and the crowd knows it
too they're going to thank team spirit
for an excellent performance in this
game too but it might be a fast close
out to the night the way team spirit
looks utterly Unstoppable they are speed
running this Grand Final right now and
the scary part is at 30 minutes gon had
a lead in that game that game was not
some super one-sided netw wor stomp even
with a Magnus void farming it up it's
just it felt inevitable right like how
are you taking these late game fights
even with a ra King a you're respawning
just to watch the corpses of your
teammates fall right where you were
there's no real burst there's no real
push Tempo here yeah nothing going their
way in that game too well I mean they at
least were able to even out the net
worth a little bit there have to be
small things that went the way of
gameing Gladiators are there any
highlights you can point to I mean I
think the laning phase was a bit better
for them but the point in their laning
phase that they wanted to work the most
that I feel has worked for them all year
has been Quinn on Mid and that lane was
the one that felt a little lackluster to
me right the Primal Beast had a very
slow start he didn't get to use the
power runes it all to come together if
you're going to beat this team spirit
team in a grand final at TI you need to
pull out all of your tricks get all the
cylinders firing and make it synergized
at its peak he they have played so many
games having to go through the lower
bracket the entire time does gaming
Gladiators have anything left in the
tank B back to the panel thank you very
much Captain SVG we'll find that answer
in game number three because right now
team spirit is on Match Point one more
game away from being crowned second time
TI champion and what a game they did it
on here it was a very back and forth a
lot of fights in this one we have a
little bit of a change on the panel
storm Stormer welcome joining us as well
I want to dive right into it what did
you make of this game thank you sh um
yeah I mean this game was actually quite
a treat to watch for a long time I think
there was some really really cool place
coming off from both sides I think L
played exceptionally well on his pangier
like there was like some situation where
they went on in three Heroes and he just
barely got out I think he carried the
game on his uh the team on his back for
quite some time until the and caught up
but um yeah definitely a two to watch
yeah I mean for La at least in regards
to net worth I think I saw a tweet from
KN where it's like it's the fifth
highest net worth of any Pang on land
and it's like he had diffusal he had
link like pre 20 minutes and just it was
just an incredible start for he was so
fed yeah so farmed and it is really hard
to top the Network's leaderboards as a
pangal right you usually never see that
happen but it's also due to the Magnus
that they were able to play around they
had three melee cores with a Magnus and
when the game stagnated they were just
collecting that netw worth lead every
time that Gman weren't making any moves
or any plays that benefited team spirit
entirely so if you're playing this game
to scale all of a sudden team spirit
they've got the superior team fight
right they've got the chronosphere
they've got the Rolling Thunder they've
got the uh RP so it made it so that
gaming Gladiators couldn't ever really
look for those fights later on as the
netw worth lead was built up yeah it
felt like at some point both teams
wanted to look for the fights both teams
were ready to fight but you only want to
really fight when you know you have the
advantage and I think T that led to some
pretty quite quite cool but that's some
pretty uh pretty surprising locations
where fights were actually happening
because we had both teams trying to
surprise the enemy team in Final
locations yeah it happened a lot you had
for in the bot side of the map you had
like this awkward rosam where Spirit
started it but they weren't strong
enough and then they baited out with the
fight and then we had a Pick Off on to
Primal and then it's near tormenta where
theosu is just free farming Top Lane
hitting a tower and then the rest of
spirits just slaughtering the entirety
of gaming Gladiator so I feel like this
entire game was gaming trying to
construct a fight where they could
survive the big spells while Spirit was
always chasing oh look we have our
spells available let's just win every
single fight cuz we know if we have the
Crono if we have the RP we're going to
hit these big spells and just Crush
every single engagement yeah and it's
hard because they didn't really have
that overwhelming team fight ability on
ging because even when they did have
that Aegis on morphling they couldn't
really ever make anything happen the
fight that they did finally manage to
force versus Spirit when morling had the
Aegis and they tried to burst The
Faceless Void they couldn't he time
walks away he Chronos they end up
killing the void in the end but they
didn't really get much in return I mean
they traded off one of their heroes
everyone else disengaged and they
couldn't turn that winning fight when
they got the void down into anything
because they committed too much and they
didn't get enough back and that really
was the story of the
game yeah it really really was and I
feel like we saw team spirit you we okay
so for people that have been uh
following their Vlogs they have a lot of
them they they show a lot of their
in-game communication uh of their Vlogs
and those fights that we see them take
here on the ti stage they seem very calm
and collected storm stor there's like oh
I guys I killed that dude yeah I got
stunned used my ultimate oh you used
this it's like they you know like you're
walking in a park like a bird you know
nice nice tree it's literally very cool
yeah I mean uh it's it's definitely what
you want to stay for as well I think
it's also something that team Tundra was
exceptionally good as when they won TI
last year it just shows that you're
confident what you're saying you're not
over emotional about things and also but
I think what I love about this team is
that even if they die you can see Smiles
in their face you know like this Yuro
he's dying at the Tormentor you might
think like oh I just fed 2K C to tofu
but then he's just smiling you know and
all the team like I think they're having
such a great time right now which makes
it look even scarier to beat this team I
think it's worth so much that like no
what is happening they're keeping it
calm head and this this calm
communication that you said like I think
is really really good to point out
because it just shows um that they're
really focus really in zone about the
most important things you don't overc
communicate you don't talk louder to
make sure your voice is being heard
everybody's on the same level yeah and
that combine that with the with the fun
they happening at the same time and that
is a skill ex I think they have like the
perfect balance honestly and together
that with how good they play Da right
now this team is just really scary is
really scary I bet the whole team was uh
was having a lot of fun actually in one
particular moment and we talked about it
a couple times already and you've seen
it in the highlights as well the Great
Escape from lurl Purge is going to talk
about it now
too thank you shiver yeah the Pango
survive was very very important for
gaming glad or for uh team spirit
because he had the most net worth on his
team if he gets killed it's a big
comeback momentum potential for gaming
Gladiators they spotted him farming up
above they saw his invis run so they
place the Sentry now and they are
looking to chain disable him here now
the uh AOE The Remnant here for for tofu
it does a little circular thing and
every ghost that passes through him is
going to silence him and if they can
chain disable him it's a really really
crucial Hill here but unfortunately the
Primal Beast charge is going to push him
back outside of the radius of this next
coming ghost that means the second
silence doesn't hit the push back does
but he's disabled still in this very
moment and he gets pushed slightly to
the left here by the fear now before
peno's uh ability here this one the uh
the the roll thing whatever it's called
it used to give damage reduction now it
gives you a barrier so because there was
three Heroes he gets 600 hp from this
which buys him time to survive and one
other moment that was really really cool
here because he was in trouble and Mir
was on the right he puts ink swell on
him it's uh this little animation I know
there's a lot of stuff going on in this
clip the ink swell on him he pops this
the moment before he dies if he doesn't
do this celery here on the Nature's
profit attacks him one time a second
Auto attack would have killed him but
because these two guys were stunned he
ends up Surviving all these things going
together to keep L alive to keep his net
worth high and waste gaming Gladiators
time on the map just a incredibly
important
moment an incredibly important moment
for sure and I bet there were a lot of
people in the crowd cheering I know in
The Green Room people like oh my God he
got away from that one and I think a lot
of people around the world and all the
different versions that people are
watching DOTA we have had people
cheering their M this is from Chicago
where the Vibes and the atmosphere is
definitely very high we'll see you get a
Pon stage I don't know maybe not today
here but we can only hope it was uh it
was very dominant towards the end of
course from team spirit but it was at
the start of the game incredibly back
and forth we heard our drafting penals
say the first seven minutes are going to
be really important uh that's what the
coach said as well and gaming Gladiator
survived that and it looked okay it just
they couldn't get that final push to get
the advantage and that is something that
they're surely going to work on for the
next game which is coming your way very
soon this particular point though T it's
it's it's all or nothing right now
they're two games down gaming Gladiators
has been in this situation before but
that was an online tournament this is
very different it isn't I'm going just
say that I don't want to see morling you
know this hero is artey got eliminated
with it m Nightfall got eliminated with
it now Theo wants to play it and he lost
game too like this here it's the bane of
these low bracket teams life and
unfortunately I don't think it's the the
the one that you want to bring out when
your life's on the line well you know I
could only imagine they're going to have
something something out different plan
that they have to have and while they're
planning that we are going to see where
Casey's hiding I think she's in the
crowd somewhere where are you Casey I'm
way up here I'm sorry I'm turning away
from the camera I'm way up here how's
everybody doing okay so usually as I
move my cord out I'm such a professional
usually when we ask people is this your
first TI we get a lot of yeah it's my
first TI I got a very different answer
when I came up here how many have you
been to you know I'm not sure 14 15 16
went to Canada was the last one and now
I'm back so I'm super excited and the
three of you have been to most of those
together a couple I would say like half
of them all the Seattle
ones I soloed in
Canada I've been to two this one this
one in I think 2017 and then we were
talking just a few minutes ago about the
way that this Grand Final is going and
you heard Sher say like this is do or
game three how's everybody feeling you
sir are feeling very well want to tell
everybody why uh I bet on team spirit on
the
compendium
so I'm sorry what is wrong with this
crowd that like three of you are like
yay okay I want to hear from the from
the gabing
Gladiators wow I think this section can
do better all right I want I hear you as
loud do you see now this is what slack
should do when he starts talking louder
you hold the microphone further away
like this all right come on upper
Rafters let's hear
it I'm going to have my amazing
photographer Phil spin around and show
you how great this view is from up here
you were saying this is like the best
seats in the house right been here for
three
days best seats in the House
nice oh oh I hear a I hear a cheer
starting three people all
right thank you very much Casey I mean
that does look magical I will say that
is definitely one of the better seats in
the House although I must say there's a
lot of good seats the screens are
fantastic the DOTA has been fantastic
but I
would I I'm going to show a little bias
here I would really like this series to
not be in three so I'm rooting for
gaming Gladiators in the next one and I
I wanted I know one more Dota 2 coming
into the climate pledge Arena here
tonight and I want to know for my panel
storm stor what do gamer Gladiators need
to do ah I mean I think first of all
don't let it get to your head I think
they are respecting T maybe a little bit
too much as well they're not showing the
same gaming Gladiator far that they show
the entire lower bracket run you have to
remember this team stting lower bracket
and now beat how many teams six seven
teams in a row to get here I just think
they have to get spur out of their head
and uh just focus on the own daughter
again maybe adjust the drafting a little
bit and and then just you know keep the
ball roll uh rolling again get back to
your seat get back to your seat I think
everybody should get back to their seats
right about now because ladies and
gentlemen we want some more DOTA to be
played we have got team spirit two games
up can gaming Gladiators push him back
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen team spirit gaming
Gladiators game number three of this
best of five grand finals here with team
spirit two games up gaming Gladiators
need all all the help they can get right
now and that means every single person
in this climate pledge Arena we need you
to be extra loud I know you've been
saving your voice for game number five
but come on you need to get there first
so I want to have no voices left by the
end of this one I know a lot of people
have already spent everything they had
but I know we got to lead a little bit
more coming out for game number three we
know they can do what they've been in
Grand finals so many times and every
single L event this year in the DPC
gaming Gladiators has come out on top
team spirit they started really clicking
te at riab Masters and they have not
dropped the ball since and the fact that
they coming into this Grand finals that
like each draft is completely different
in game one Weaver Beast Master they
swarm them map they the aggressors game
two they got big cooldowns Magnus void
like being the team down to O and having
to try and work out how do we do with
aggression how do we do with the skan
like you don't know what's going to come
at you in this game so for gaming it's
not about team spirit at this point it's
about what can they bring themselves
what is their draft to get them through
the laning phase and set themselves up a
game that they can actually dictate cuz
right now they're just victim to team
spirit two times in a row yeah but also
I I just want to have storm uh elaborate
a little bit more and what he was
talking about when he said they need to
get Spirit out of their heads and how do
you feel like that what what does that
mean when you say that the enemy team is
in your head are you drafting
differently are you playing differently
can you speak to it from your personal
experience yes I think both of it I
think like um I think first of all all
the gaming players just play the heroes
that they're most comfortable with that
they don't like for example draft Heroes
cuz they want to block pick them from
the enemy team or something like that
they should just play their own game in
regardless of who the who they're
playing against and I know that some
players on gaming like it is good to
have healthy respect towards the enemy
team on team spirit but I don't think it
should like affect your own gameplay too
much you should respect what the enemy
team is doing you should know their
strengths and weaknesses but it should
not cause yourself to have more
weaknesses if that makes sense just
basically reset don't care who you play
play against remember all the games that
got you to this point got you through
the entire lower bracket to this game
three and make it like a home run again
got to remember as well team spirit when
they won TI 10 back then right they were
also two games ahead and then it still
went to a five game series against PSG
lgd back then so this is not over yet
whatsoever and I hope gaming Gladiators
also have that in their head right now
that like you know it's maybe a longer
day for them as well they also have to
play the lower bracket finals against uh
I forgot just now I bad bad memory lgd
lgd okay it's okay with lgd right and
now they here again so it is a a longer
day for them but I all just hope they
like whatever it was they they got the
energy running again and they just go in
into R yeah we're going to find now can
gaming Gladiators Force out a next game
or will team spirit be the two time
champion and let's hear it for game
three team spirit versus game in
Gladiators Grand
Finals game three has turn to B welcome
back to the draft panel for game number
three everybody this is everything on
the line for gaming gliders down zero to
team spirit have been crushing so far
seems like they have all the answers
they have all the strategies that they
need to become Champions once again just
like back two years ago what do you guys
want to see gaming gliders I feel like
I'm repeating myself after game number
one but it really is the story here how
can gaming gliders dig themselves out of
the strategical hold they found
themselves in honestly I thought their
draft last game they had a really good
shot I I think they identified that they
want to Target a little bit more of non
collapse Heroes they let collapse guys
Magnus and I thought that it was not a
bad idea I don't think collapse had the
usual Magnus impact maybe he didn't need
it maybe he didn't get there uh T was
able to pick up a early uter but I think
I just want them to do that but there
was a time where like they had the
triple wave with Quinn I want them to
play even more for the mid pressure cuz
L just see it I don't know the guy's too
good he had too good a
game uh I would like uh greaters uh
get back to the idea of super pressure
super Tempo crazy super fast uh super
strong Lanes I think uh but potentially
might work yeah something like this you
you need to risk at some point right
you're
02 they definitely have it like we
definitely gave a very good fights in
both games like both games we actually
gave good fights we had good lanes and
stuff yeah but uh this last game was
rough to play after some point because
vo Magnus is just too strong like when
it come to late game so I hope this time
maybe we just you know go super
Tempo I definitely agree D on that one
the way gaming gladers got here was with
that Tempo pushing The High Ground it
felt like in that last game they kind of
fell back like we don't really want to
do that and instead we're going to try
and matchu in the late game pick up a
Daio morling he played pretty amazing
for the most part had a couple bad
deaths but overall like you're playing
into how team spirit wants to play at
that point you're not really playing the
game that got you into this Grand finals
in particular so we'll see if they go
ahead and do that but the problem is I
think when you play against team spirit
right now there's like a triple threat
here it's like you have to deal with
collapse which they've been trying to do
through bands and then I think what
really leveled up spirit is Laurel he's
just playing so good every game and you
see Quinn he's normally taking control
of the map he's like making moves he
hasn't been able to in these last two
games cuz L's having a great laning
stage and of course there's always yoro
who's going to pick the CK but you don't
even know if it's his he's strategically
taking away a lot of daos Heroes making
them feel a bit uncomfortable so there's
a lot of things they're doing Strat
level and in game that it's just really
hard for gaming to address so what do
you think uh gaming if we want to see
this early aggression from them what is
the first pick of the game do you just
go for the celery end chair and you're
like okay full focus on early laning
stage and putting that pressure your gen
was obviously banned that you've had a
great success within that macro strategy
is the en into CK even appealing to
start off I think it's a it's normally
like a decent match up for CK cuz he's
actually one of the heroes that can kill
pretty easily when you bring her
position but honestly I sort of like
that line of thought uh I think at this
tournament they usually pick ench with
Weaver um just because it gives the an a
really strong Lane once you give an a
strong Lane you can Snowball the other
lane you can leave it alone but I don't
mind that if they pick another strong
carry with it okay there's the AA we
were looking for in both of the previous
games and this time gam are going to
bring it out does this fit the bill for
you guys not a strong laner not a strong
laner not a fast tempo hero but it can
buff really well like other Heroes that
you can have in a draft uh Vortex is
extremely strong also shut down a lot of
like fat Heroes with B her ofas and
stuff so might see something if you
build up a strong like uh carry that
fits a on Lane it's can still be pretty
strong Lane yeah I think the hero he
just has a lot of range so he keeps
clicking right if the lane is stable and
you get to just keep clicking your
opponent his Lane's like not weak or
anything he's going to constantly harass
on the region I think generally what a
picks mean is that they want to play
with their mid generally when you pick a
you pick some high damage mid and they
just sort of run around together you get
stacks and then they play together you
get Stacks you get play together and I
think that's also something that we saw
a lot from gladers in this tournament
they would play a lot off these Stacks I
think the AA could be a good start for
that look at that stat this is their
first time playing the hero this
tournament they haven't brought out the
AA a single time so really digging deep
here in the final game and or I say the
final game what could be the final game
for them um to look at it from the other
perspective team spirit this is probably
a surprise for them given the
circumstances that there hasn't been a
single AA from Gladiators do you change
any sort of approach on the spirit side
I guess like you guys said maybe you
want to keep the CK Flex what are your
what are your next two go-to picks to
make this a feel bad laning stage I
think the last time they ran this
they're probably looking at a dark
Willow for Spirit to Lane it that lane
seemed incredibly strong I'm not sure
who's going to play the CK they might
keep it open for a while it is a little
Annoying to play CK vers a in some ways
cuz the armlet issue you can't really
toggle that so that could be annoying
but then again the fantasm does delete
AA pretty quickly so I could see this
being an offlane CK if yoro finds a
better pick for himself but I think the
dark Willow is definitely something
they're looking at I would really like
if they pick dark will I think what you
said about the three CK sounds good as
well because a can keep clicking the CK
but as soon as he it's level three or
four these clicks aren't going to do
anything to him at
all yeah uh a afraid of mobile heroes
and heroes who are very fast and can
jump uh back lines and stuff like this
so we can see already Primal and P BS
and uh CK is one of those Heroes
actually it's pretty like Fast hero it
gets into back lines pretty fast so uh
Heroes who doesn't have a in some sense
maybe TB can work again for spirit
because uh you always can swap HP like
even even if you under
ay yeah I think they're going to pick 18
Spectre like they should start to look
at it I don't know if they will for sure
but I liked what you said about like
getting these backline jumpers I think
yoro he played a lot of Spectre I mean
he played some at this tournament but he
was playing a lot of Spectre and pubs he
always goes for some really high damage
builds you go like bloodthorn uh Manta
like he never goes for some like tanky
buat at all he just looks to kill the
backline I guess grimo does something
similar that you were saying as well
right just giving a really high kill
threat Lane you want to make sure that
the CK is at least open as a flex for
the 18 pick yeah I think they go for
that because it's a lot better ver a
pangle than the willow would be right
you can get the leash on him and then he
can get stuck so same thing in the
laning stage though it's really strong
get on top of him lots of damage just
Grim is better for this particular game
Trant is in again this was a hero Spirit
ran against Pango last time uh but they
are going to go for the Tusk
tusy are we are we committed here to a
five Tusk for this reason has mea been
playing Grim he has right they've both
played both of these Heroes so this for
team spirit I believe is a complete Flex
among their support players uh mea has
not play Tusk so it's most like 100% in
poska so far did he not play Tusk in
game one am I oh he played it in the
last game but outside of that I outside
of this series okay got it yeah my notes
are outdated from the last I'm sure they
can Flex it perfectly well um I think
actually a Mor is not banned in this
series which is sort of surprising cuz I
mean they broke gam confidence and the
hero a bit because I think I don't know
I think tofu played literally every game
on this hero before
that you just go back for it yeah
because it does what need him to do
right I feel like you just have so many
issues with gon's other Heroes that you
feel like you don't have to ban it cuz
you have to ban so many other things in
this game like the necro the Phoenix the
chin all these heals and this is really
good Banning I think by team spirit even
the conka these lineups where you see
them group up be able to push they're
not being able to get them because you
have to deal with the Heroes that you
see in front of you and some of your
best heroes to do these pushes are just
being banned out by team spirit so
they're going to play the brew master
the only question I do have yet again is
is this Pango too early is it too early
of a Pango game will we have a game
right now it looks like they only have
one answer for him but I expect more to
come is there any mid laners potentially
dendy that can punish that left in the
pool uh for sure for sure there's a
bunch like this this hero become not as
strong as it used to be it's actually
pretty strong Lane Ste
like here we go the lane Punisher if I
decide to put it mid we can still think
about it it's weird to see sometimes H
picked into a but I think the purpose is
is especially like having this insanely
strong Lanes we can still do Post free
dazle if we decide I don't know like if
collabs uh going to play it or not uh
I'm I'm curious because one hero that
comes to my mind that both teams
ignoring uh second I think uh po games
is Spirit breaker right we all talked
how imbalanced and broken with hero is
and now we don't see it much because
even here I saw okay we have green
stroke maybe potentially who knows
there's not so many Heroes to stop it if
you think about it yeah yeah I can see
the spear breaker especially since I
think there's like a mechanic with BR
Master where the brings take the creep
damage from the charge so you actually
kill like over half their HP even after
brw Master's 20 time one interaction
with the Dazzle versus a I think swings
the match up a little bit is you can
actually perr someone if they get AED
well as soon as you have 18 on Dazzle so
it's not as much of like a oh they can
all in no matter what with this AO on
one target what do you guys make of uh
Spirits approach to dealing with gaming
Gladiators which I mean if you look at
the game in lineup it seems very team
fight Centric right you got Pango you
got brew master Al are you a little
concerned for gaming Gladiators having
downtime when they have cool down on
this uh you look at Spirits lineup it
seems very fast very low cool down it
can play in Duos trios uh do you think
By Design This Dazzle fits that play
style really well uh for sure and I
would add up up here that both previous
game and this game so far uh what
bothers me in gaming draft is uh we
don't really have a saves in their
lineup if you look at team spirit lineup
where you already have two and usually
on like middle game late game this is
one of the most important things that
you have in your lineups so not only
like big cool Downs like on bre or
something like this but also like uh
saves I think it's often can be like
Game
Changer speaking of saves I think Gman
probably needs to ban C in this game
this could be a really good hero like
you see the Roll come out you see the
split come out some Centaur Stampede can
disengage that really well I think they
need another hero that I'm was kind of
looking at yur's hero pool not seeing
anything much better versus the brew
master than the CK right now potentially
it was like a morphling but then you're
playing versus AA Weaver's band it's
like a nightstalker carry yeah I think
Nightfall pulled out out a couple pits I
I could actually see yoro playing in a
game like this it's actually a really
good night socer carry game
agree on that that looks amazing if we
go for it it's very hard to play with
this lineup so far against ni stalker
carry you don't have so many uh reliable
stuns I would say on gladi yet like you
have a lot of some skill shots that you
need to aim so it can create a problem
yeah also by way Grim is also safe if
you think about it right his Shard is
used so efficiently at ti so far yeah we
saw that last game as well like I guess
the only question is like they probably
are wanting a range cuz you have tusk
potentially five and I don't know if CK
Tusk Lane is going to cut it I guess
they could do it I think just because
they see the AA they might feel like
they can greed it out like they have a
five that doesn't really prevent the
carry from getting all in and that can't
protect themselves so you can like play
for the kills in with something like the
CK Tusk I could see them just go for the
range rout with the tusar 5 though I
think they'd have really strong lanes
that way as well it seems like gaming
gliders have the same mindset with this
uh Dawn breaker B right this is a hero
combination that we saw other teams run
earlier in the tournament the Tusk Dawn
as a dual Lane just absolutely
obliterating weak F so it does seem like
gam are still in that mindset of this CK
is going to be the carry um but as you
guys pointed out I don't I don't even
think CK Tusk is going to struggle here
unless that carry last pick from gaming
really solves that lane AA does not like
this match up honestly I just like this
last H from T Spirit to sort of solidify
their team fights I feel like right now
they actually have a chance that they
get run over in team fights I think
Pango brw master and morto are all
really strong
oh oh it was time dend he wanted it he
got it
oh it's a beautiful lineup here Spirit
breaker green looks very scary very
scary also it's a bigy pierce once again
which is very strong in a lot of
situations remain yeah I think the carry
pull I think the troll being banned and
the void kind of can signify that you
want this CK to be your carry so they're
going for the offline rout not going for
the center going for the spear breaker
which brew master I guess you have a
dispel which helps a little bit against
that if you can get it off on time but
we've seen time and time again in the
late game it doesn't really matter you
have like a bkb oing core and like can
refresh your orb so you can't really
deal with that so this has been a
collapse special throughout like the
entirety of this TI and he's really good
at it and it looks pretty scary here I
will say the game in lineup it looks
pretty good though so far I think
whenever you play against Dazzle having
that AA is really good if you can ever
commit on
him we have a spectre going to round it
out with the Spectre so giving some
maybe some skirmishing potential to
gaming glage a a carrier that can join
globally does this was this just a
matter of okay there's nothing left or
is the lane going to be okay is yeah
honestly I'm really worried for
gladiators I feel like every time I've
seen spear breaker have a good Lane this
hero is like the most unreal Ino of the
patch yeah Spectre a is one of the best
combinations in the game for ages and I
don't think anything changing in that
because those both Heroes complement
each other very well but at the same
time the lineup on team spe looks crazy
in late game if it's the game d ways
all right seems like we're grasping are
we grasping as draws for gaming
Gladiators is this actually going to be
that difficult of a safe plane as maybe
some sort of Hope with rotation from
maybe a a gating wherea could offset
this balance in the Top Lane can you
leave brew master alone for a minute to
try to help or do you need to get really
creative I think a lot can happen in
this game and I think A lot's going to
come from the mid lane and can Quinn get
rotations and can they abuse Laurel this
game cuz I think Laurel is very
exploitable in this game with a old spec
old and if he feeds a lot of net worth
back that could be a way back into the
game yeah I can completely see that if
one lane starts to being start getting
pressured like you have the Spector to
add on the pengle probably is going to
be the strongest hero in the game when
he gets his role so they do have a lot
of angles on Gladiator to snowball off
that so I guess I mean not to sound like
a broken record but we are uh we're very
focused on the Leaning stage as per
usual in this series um if you're in
Quinn's shoes in this game obviously
you've had a couple of games that were
did not go according to plan right are
you you let's talk a little bit about
the mentality of him going up against
what we assume will be a very
unfavorable match up against laurl and
The Dazzle what do you think Quinn is
telling his team right now is it all
right I'm going to be struggling but
I'll come back or I need help for sure
in this game it's actually not that bad
for Pango it's one of a better Heroes to
uh sustain against dazzle because he
have two jumps to jump away from its
poison attacks so I think Queen is
extremely experienced and he will be
fine all right guys gaming Gladiators
they are on the ropes I'm sure team
Spirit of feeling themselves right now
and let's see if it is the same for
their coach
silent thank you very much I am joined
by silent of team spirit where around
two years ago you were in a very similar
spot it was Grand finals TI 10 in
Bucharest you were up two games now a
lot has changed since then but hasn't
changed for your team the energy from
two years ago to now does anything feel
different uh no I think uh we feel the
same you need to be be focused and play
till the end it doesn't matter lead you
or losing same you don't like to okay we
leading to Z we can make some YOLO plays
a championship mentality through and
through but I know one thing that's
different two years ago you didn't have
a
crowd but this
time I think they're ready for a game
number three
and we are certainly ready for a game
number three though we certainly don't
want to end it here Seattle do we want
to see some more
DOTA here in the cathedral in Seattle we
may just be witnessing the final game of
the grand finals but I'm sure a lot of
us hope for so much more and that all
depends on game and gladiators I mean
they have been the ones to run the
gauntlet through all of these Majors
they were looking like the best team of
the year until they ran into team spirit
until team spirit ramped up in just the
right time shown up for championships
and they have only lost two games in
this entire tournament Avery they are 43
and seven in their last 50 this team is
looking Unstoppable is there anything
gaming Gladiators can do to Halt this
momentum even just a little bit
you have to play DotA there's no way
around it you have to meet this team on
their plane and give them a taste of
their own medicine because you came in
with a plan but everybody has a plan
until team spear punches you in the face
and right now you're laying on the
ground trying to figure out what the
hell just happened in the first two
games your plan did not work whatever
you thought it was going to happen in
the games one and two it fell flat so
right now team spirit are in control of
this draft meta they're in control of
the series and they're dictating the
pace in these games they're dictating
the team fight so you have to meet them
there and beat them you have to outplay
them you have to start winning these
team fights scaling into the late game
you are not going to run this team over
which means you got to find some more
momentum going past that 30 or 40 minute
Mark it's not been gamon's Mo this
entire low bracket run but hey you're in
a dire situation at Grand F you don't
have another chance here you are at the
total limit so figure it out fast make
the adjustments and get crank and this
is a draft that is heading in that
direction right a lot more team fight a
lot more scaling presence Spectre AA
here designed to put you in a tough
position we've seen the AA a counter to
CK for a lot of this tournament in terms
of limiting the life steal interactions
of course it can also have a huge impact
versus The Dazzle as this game
progresses into the late game so I think
these are much more even lineups in
terms of what happens past the 40 or 50
minute Mark there's not some crazy
inevitable scale outside of maybe Dazzle
Spirit breaker doing crazy Dazzle Spirit
breaker things and celer trouble in the
bottom Lane and that is going to be your
first Blood collapse claim it with a
bash of course a little luck goes a long
way a classic team Spirit strategy going
back to their first TI Victory and a c
Courier pick off as well look at that
dagio even like taking himself outside
the lane to block the hard Camp cuz this
Lane is already going a little bit
awkward for them the mid Lanes not
looking much better we 12 and four on
Laurel over this melee range versus
melee match up it's not a fun one you
should expect the Dazzle to win but
Laurel is already taking commanding lead
and then we've got your Toro 11 and two
now the brew master is keeping Pace but
he's certainly not slowing down the
carry of team spirit so gaming
Gladiators got to be able to to uh Hal
this momentum a little bit further here
bit of damage onto Ace they turning it
back around but goou is here to be able
to help him out nice shot to get the
extra bit of damage on two Heroes yeah
double proc win the war of attrition I
think these sings can go fine for gaming
over the course of the lanes they don't
look too terrifying to me I think the
Brew can fight back with the help of
morta just a very tough hero to trade
into that mid Lan is what I'm wored out
the right it's Dazzle versus melee I
mean pangle has some Escape mechanisms
but if you get some Ram going through
with the poison adding up can be deadly
every single time Cel wants to be able
to stop that hard Camp opportunity he
does risk Getting Gone on by meor and
collapse this time around he's fine The
Shard inadvertently kind of helps him
out as he's pushed underneath his Tower
just try and get as many pulls off space
as you can in this Lane boost the XP up
for both Heroes as they both really want
and need it here you're not going to be
able to shut collapse down which I mean
that's a worrying fact Factor right a
spear breaker with absolute free F it's
going to have a fast Midas is what
collapse is going to have here he's
going to have his choice and it'll be
quite powerful going into that mid game
so you got to be able to strike back in
these small skirmishes get the ults up
particularly the brew master Primal
split the Rolling Thunder here very
powerful spells if you can get them fast
and of course a blast coming in on top
of it with Vortex amping up all this
magic damage and put that mini haunt to
use on the
step real quickly when to give it a
shout out to our observers our
hardworking observers who have been
keeping us through this entire
tournament Ace may be in some trouble
here moska he's trying to dodge all of
these ghosts he doesn't want to leave
the calling he'll take that extra bit of
damage to try and risk it but he does
end up falling as a result and now Ace
he'll have some helping in from tofu
beautiful dead shot to push him back in
and gaining Gladiators a very clutch
fight there for them tofu and Ace get a
big win in their off Lane that's the
strength of the mor at the Dual Lane
that they're looking for this is her has
been a first pick for them for a lot of
these series they're very confident in
what tofu can do on it in the early game
and now he has some roam options I don't
think you can leave Ace in the one on
two but if you can get some breathing
room like this and look towards mid
maybe you can get some damage poke help
skew this Lane back in Quinn's favor cuz
he is still getting known 31 and 10 on
Laurel almost doubling Quinn up here he
got The Courier as well Quinn with a
slight misstep will hurt his regen
fairing that just means more pressure
going to build up between Laurel and his
melee foe just not much you can do
against the poison touch here yeah this
is looking like Quinn kind of needs one
of his supports to die just to refill
that bottle and celery May Grant him
that wish he's going to get a double
blood grenade before he goes so this may
be a fair tradeoff if Dau can claim his
life and he does manage to get it it
puts an early level into that desolate
and it's just the added damage they need
honestly I think celer is okay with that
solo XP for Dau on a spectre he gets to
collect all these creeps under the tower
without any
pressure pretty happy about that
exchange with a very defensive oriented
Lane where I mean you know what are you
doing aggressively with the a Spector
it's all about getting farm and XP down
here and there's that TP rotation to
fill out Quinn's bottle and try and help
with the six-minute Rune see if he's
able to do so but team spirit not going
to worry about the runes here instead
they try and win this off Lane situation
where Ace and too were doing pretty well
for themselves they bring three Heroes
to the matter to bring down Ace if they
can get him slowed down by the blood
grenade they only need a couple more
hits they've got more blood where that
came from apparently gives them over
that Lotus and that's enough
evasion with the haze enough for Ace to
just walk him off here Okay I lied they
do care about that uh that power Rune
because they brought collapse to secure
it not just that but also the kill on
Quinn that's just going to secure the
double check for L he's going to walk
all the way top and get himself a shield
Rune putting this match up to good use
giving Quinn a taste of his own medicine
here with the Rome maybe not expected
out of the off laner but that is a hell
of a rotation from collapse and gets a
lot of momentum going to this Dazzle
right now this is a pressure point
you're going to have to respond to this
is a hero that scales very hard in Dota
right
now pretty strong early game for team
spirit they're going to look to try and
play back but Quinn with a nice rotation
just eyeing yoro up here all alone will
get the hit back if you're just going to
keep dying in your lane you might as
well rotate out of it even if it means
you're doing it pre-level six so as you
can see anybody who shows up in the mid
lane is going to be run over by the
dazzel especially if you get the extra
vision of like a TS snowball or the
spirit breaker charge you just can't get
away from this poison touch hit so no
especially with these Wards behind the
tower already deep Observer for team SP
behind game in tier one claps having
chuckle about that yeah that was all
because Quinn tipped him before the
charge even completed Quinn knew what
was coming he could do nothing to stop
it
well could have picked a real
hero always an option just saying 4 to
four 7 and 1/2 minutes in did we trade
off wisdom runes yeah yes that was the
one upside of you know then going on Mid
you guarantee the wizard Moon trade
which C is definitely happy about you're
saying he's like happy to soak up XP but
it is a weird position for an AA who
rather just be pulling if nothing else
is happening Le da alone at the bottom
Lane but a really good use of the dagger
will get him over that little Cliff area
and tofu can get some damage back in
return no threat of anybody dying but a
decent punish and will allow Dau to
clean up some CS but he is being pushed
out of Lane Mira's not giving up on it
just yet and aosa even rotating down
here potentially throwing that ink swell
into the break I mean this is a
combination we also saw when breaker was
hot that last patch the team spear were
very comfortable playing the ink swell
breaker across the map giving you the
guaranteed setup this is what the CK has
designed to help facilitate push the
lanes in with CK Illusions be a ghost on
the map and all of a sudden you get one
pick off and your map just collapses
right on the flip side gaming trying to
do something similar if you can set
anything up with a primal split or the
Rolling Thunder then suddenly Dau can
come in and clean house and this is a
smoke designed to find yoro but nobody's
home Toro they Duke him out with the
fantasm he's sent it back instead Quinn
and Ace will bite down on that but it
doesn't matter too much that bait they
still get some pretty good damage onto
the tower one thing to note about that
uh ink swell combination with the spirit
breaker oh thought they we going to go
on to mea but mea's going through the
portal they don't have a stun to stop
him he gets the other side Daio pursues
dagger does hit him yeah he's pretty
damn slow and he's going to hit him with
another dagger mea he needs the help
from the spirit breaker has a snowball
to by a Moment collaps pops ultimate
immediately goes for the kill on of tofu
see if they can trade things out here
for The Shard and the calling that
actually protects him there collapse
doesn't want to trade two for one so
he's going to go ahead and give up on
that they cannot afford to give any more
kills to this Daio Spectre going to
rotate LL bottom they really want to
punish the
Rio coming back Inkwell charge in
chaining the stuns and adding up on the
damage spear breaker got that 5% buff
the movement speed as damage got buffed
up by 5% that was enough to bring him
back into the meta but then that's even
more if you add in this ink swell
movement speed buff uh it's a deadly
combination for a reason I like that
rotation from lur that's such a heads up
read there you just walk down the lane
there's no vision here they probably had
a read Because seler's been mid the
whole time right it's going to limit
where your observers are going to go
just gets a really cheeky kill on the
Spectre nice Shard to buy some time good
driving by Quinn gets a around that
little speed bump in the way hopefully
Dao can finish him up but not quite no
sh grave comes in for La per timing
there Quinn does manage to get some
decent damage Ono and here he makes the
difference he makes it so team spirit
can no longer fight bad it's an
overwhelming amount of Team fight that
he'll put to work to bring down utoro
and looks like he's going to chase down
butka Mira really trying for this one he
might just get himself kill in the
process will it be good enough but boska
still dies and sure enough mea he's
going to be in trouble as well good use
of The Shard blocking him out but he
still Falls cannot stop gaming
Gladiators as they bring all five Lear
from team spirit perhaps the only way to
beat these guys in a team fight is you
got to bring everybody to the table and
that's why I think this draft feels a
lot better for them to play they can
connect the heroes a lot faster the
Spectre facilitates that at a tremendous
rate and then Ace is just on a hero
where even if his laning phase wasn't
spectacular which it has been this game
that Primal split into a fast Radiance
is going to give him all the team fight
they need this CK does not have free
engagements where I felt like in the
first two games yoro connections were
uncounted right he goes in with a weaver
goes in with a fa for gets what he wants
and gets out this game yoro finds
himself in a pickle mid where he just
can't escape pays the price and 0 and
three start for yoro got up here perhaps
one of the rougher early games we've
seen from the entire tournament that is
a very good position for Gman to be in
going to shut down a lot of the pace
ll's going to have to to pick up that
that little bit of slack right he's
going to have to step in with this
Dazzle but the Dazzle I feel like isn't
a hero you you really want to utilize
just yet feels like that Agony sceptor
is such a key timing you can't afford to
delay that by getting into some RIS
engagement and this hero is like Tinker
in some ways I guess first item kind of
easy to get to you're a Powerhouse when
you get it but then you fall into a
valley and it's like the next two or
three you have to get through before you
really come online the ultra late and
those team fights start to become
impossible for the enemy that is a
period where gaming can strike with this
Radiance which is going to be coming out
fast on Ace this game and just take the
team fight to team spirit which is where
again you have to meet this team you
have to be willing to take the F on
fives and win them and translate it into
objectives you can't just go for the
other first
smoke across the map they failed to get
the initiation on collapse we're going
to try and join Quinn for the power run
Quinn's going to need that help too he
silenced up the poison touch the Wells
on top of him but he does manage to get
away with the swashbuckle just in time
the charge is going to complete collapse
he's got his ultimate he may not even
need it though the point touch Flo him
down so much and Mos is getting a TP out
the shot oh was so close but it runs out
it doesn't get there in time and now a
snowball to the other side to meet sario
as it is now him who is surrounded by
team spirit Heroes too many to count and
that is a mest chaos Knight coming in
and cleaning up the enemy carry there
youor gets some XP a much better
turnaround for him as opposed to the
last River fight where they're still
missing that tier one so maybe a smoke
and connection that Quinn in the gang
just didn't expect considering you know
they're missing that objective that went
down in the previous fight Tower attack
but it seems like team spirit take
advantage of that bit of an Overlook
from Quinn and now collapse highest net
worth in the game but game Gladiators
don't want to slow down just yet they
still have that Rolling Thunder didn't
use it in the last fight so tofu and
celery think to themselves that if they
can get the right kind of initiation
here with the Rolling Thunder they could
follow it up the ice blast but yoro
uh-oh he's in the staircase it's going
to be very awkward the soul bite does
actually latch onto the two of them as
Spector jumps into as well please tell
me they're going to hit him oh they
barely got it in the fountain he will go
down it wasn't even the blast it was
like an earn tick or something that got
him in the end host that grave
that was a nasty Soul bind something
they're going to have to think about
with Dau Haunting in they find theck Ace
is so close to his Radiance he could not
afford to get picked off here so at the
first side of danger he uses his Primal
split though you could see the spirit
Breakers pretty good answer to those
brings no threat of dying here something
to think about later into the game
normally the dispell and tornado is a
problem for this hero but doesn't look
like it so far and like you said
Radiance 300 off for Ace he just wants
to get his big item and get the farm
rate going still having a very good game
on this brew master yeah considering the
lone Droid game where he was so close to
the radiance for so long I don't think
he wants to risk that happening again
Radiance is an incredibly powerful item
in this meta it's better the faster you
get it in a lot of those games Ace just
didn't get it at a time where he could
take the map or the fight's over with it
this is going to be a game where he has
a very good chance to do that as yoro
still behind right this is a double mest
lineup for team spirit they have one on
the CK one on the spear breaker which
you know has become the deao build for
the XP getting to the late game Talent
is going to slow the team fight presence
down I really feel like if game can get
a fight going in the next two to 3
minutes here they're pretty favored
especially with diffusal and Radiance
coming out at the same time this is a
huge damage power Spike you want to get
something going with it and you want to
get it going now they go for it the
radiance is complete though on Ace but
they know the Primal split is on cool
down yeah this is a beefy Target to just
go into especially when you don't have
the global ability to connect how much
does collapse think he chunk through
here tofu just left him alone tofu was
needed to be able to disrupt this
combination but now Ace is left alone
speeds himself away somehow the ink
swell didn't go off in time but poka
didn't pop that one atashi was like okay
now it's my opportunity hello moska oh
almost got him with a fear shot there on
the left hand side but moska still dies
collapse still in trouble has a charge
instead Ops to the TPL up but that
doesn't make it calculations not on
point here yeah he could have just
charged the other side of the map maybe
he didn't have a good Target but there
was a midwave he will collect a 3xtra
this such an important kill too ging
Gladiators with the ice blast on top of
Laurel now collaps and Laurel who were
very much needed to be able to buy y
Toro time now they've both fallen and
now you're invading eny triangle this is
where gaming want to strike they want to
strike hard on the map right now gain a
lot of the momentum in this game they
have the supports to follow up on the
core initiations they have a crap ton of
damage in the tank as long as they can
see Heroes and with Dau able to join any
of these ghost suddenly this map has
collapsed pretty fast for team spirit
and a on the tazzle try and stem some is
bleeding but right now this crowd they
want to see a game forward they want to
see G and strike back in this game three
and they are delivering yeah I'm not
even convinced those are all gaming
Gladiators fans they might just be DOTA
fans who want to be able to see more
from a grand finals between these two
teams but it's still a long road ahead
for gaming Gladiators cuz they're only
2K net worth up they've hit some timings
yes but they still have to worry about
the double hand amas they have to play
this clean they need to be able to get
good executions but they can't afford to
use any kickoffs good roll in from Quinn
from behind though trapping team spirit
H shot goes out looking for more The
Dazzle was shown there Quinn getting in
front of him blocks him out with a swash
buckle slows him down with the inhibit
from the diffusive plate allows Daio to
do the damage he pops a shallow grave
lurl he really wants to off Quinn will
he get that kill the poison touch he's
got a regen a Lotus given over to him as
well good plays from gaming Gladiators
give him the extra bit of regen he needs
and now he can pop the Regeneration in
his bottle for a full heal Max I see
right now all team spe can do is cut
some waves with their double mest Heroes
and and go late cuz right now it is all
gaming on the momentum chart and a full
vessel was completed very fast here from
tofu that even gives you more damage
vessel plus a blast is nasty in these
team fights when you're throwing the
vortexes down particularly versus dazu
wants to just heal through with the
inverse waves and get that going yeah
you've got Dazzle You've Got The Inkwell
heal that you know would have been a
factor if it wasn't for the all the
anti- heal they have and then also the
chaos that life steal that the chaos
night is so dependent on and there is no
downtime for this lineup look at a
burned out of Mana they try and give him
over a little bit see if he can charge
his way out of there but he's silenced
up by The Calling trapped to the corner
and then they use that storm Panda to be
able to catch more Laurel is going to
die as well the Dazzle getting no
footing in this game Ace making his
presence felt and this was with a second
item boots a travel so this isn't even
some like
ear looks like he didn't have a way back
to the base so he tried to skirt on
through gaming gladi side of the map but
he was spotted and he will be brought
down this Pro Spector combination
working wonders right now is Ace is 5 Z
and 10 completely Unstoppable and you
can't bring the CK in to really help you
here the Brew is just great versus the
hero with the radiance burn the AOE Miss
he has the evasion that yoro can't
Pierce and not to mention his old you go
in start messing up the CK Illusions
yeah with Radiance and the dispel chaos
Knight's going to be so what are your I
mean you have to just wait until your
t's ready to fight I think you have to
split the map with the breaker and this
is where gaming can continue to try and
pick you off put the vessel to use put
the radiance to use and of course Daio
he's on a hero that doesn't have to you
know Farm up some crazy Stacks doesn't
have to go in the fight first he can
just Farm the defensive parts of the map
if nothing happens he's still happy I
mean you still got a
spectre drum for tofu just to buff up
the team fight even more here
SMA is doing work also having a perfect
game so far and the calling is not a
spell that these team spirit Heroes want
to fight into it's it's annoying for
Mira going in with the snowball it's
annoying for Laurel trying to run in gra
people with lowl
grave team fight is very obnoxious right
now and it's going to collect a free
tier
two so a tier two at 19 minutes for
gameing
gladiators they can actually take away
that Outpost they've got a pretty good
choke hold on the map
SC they desperately need now is just not
to slip up anywhere not allow team
spirit in opening they're building up
this net worth lead and may become
insurmountable as long as team spirit
doesn't pull anything sneaky here the
smoke up it slips right past team spirit
immediately SP moska and Dau recognizes
that that is the hero he wants to get
first and the Deadshot bounced over to
yoro and hit by the Rolling Thunder he's
trapped caught and there's nowhere to go
from there too many to save cbles on the
side of gaming Gladiators and they have
way too much damage they need the bkbs
on the side of team spirit but they're
not going to get them anytime soon he
had it oh he had it yeah was a bkb he
disassembled and body he just didn't
want to pop it he didn't have fantasm
there's no turnaround there yeah he will
choose to save it for another day that
is the fifth death for yoro here who is
yet to make a single kill in this game
hey there's The Dazzle play though 20
minutes on the dot they're going to use
the couriers to uh use the agony sh a
wave he could solo up that that's the
better Shard I think they were hoping
for oh yeah ink swell Shard for moska
going to be pretty damn nice here trying
dispel these melee Heroes when they go
in Tower still I feel like if you're
team spirit you're trying to rat this
game out right now and that is a big
Paradigm ship from games one and two
yeah how do you RP though against a
spectre and well you got this
Quinn he is running around with a banger
you're not going to be able to Solo in a
lane for very long it only takes a few
seconds for ging Gladiators to spot the
opportunity and jump onto you an ice
blast not even needed tofu has the
damage necessary to kill the support by
himself and the really nice thing about
what's happening right now for gaming is
this Spectre is doing an amazing job
protecting their Wards one of the
biggest things you have to combat when
you play against team spirit is the
vision Advantage they had it a lot in
game one with that tream protector they
abused it pretty damn well in game two
here it's moska trying to get out get
vision for the team deward these
aggressive OBS that are doing work for
gaming because they know they're there
they're getting haunted on the cool
Downs just so damn Low by the time
you're back up by the time you run there
to try and gain anything they're ready
to jump on you again and uh yeah I mean
there's always a little Spectre bias in
the win probability I think that's fair
to say but this is this is the best
gameing has looked in this series by a
large degree they're continuing to build
the momentum and he can continue to
build the single Target items since Ace
is building the or built the radiance so
he could just focus on being able to
take out a support in a second he's
going to build into an orchid up next so
now if you're spotted anywhere on the
map Daio can guarantee that the Grim
shoke dies or the tus dies or maybe even
some of the cores he's going to pop it
here looking for mea they just get the
vision on him they'll spot him now and
there it is they jump immediately
snowball tried to put to work but it
just means he going to be dragged back
in does manage to get a Shard but
unfortunately Daio doesn't care about
your blocks there the GU shards does
nothing when he has free pathing spirit
just Bleeding Out right now they have no
answer to the Spectre on the map their
supports are way too squishy they don't
have an early Aura bu there's no Beast
Master or anything to to help protect
the backline on the map or help them get
Lanes out all three of these cores are
just building for themselves right it's
damage items into bkb you have two mides
that are still trying to get the work
done kaps will try and find a Pick Off
on tofu and this will combine with moska
so they strike back a little bit on the
map much needed and finally they're
getting some deep Vision out as well you
look at these dire OBS it took MOS a
while but these are some Vision they can
play around at least though of course
the second you get
spotted it's moska somehow doesn't get
spotted by Quinn there and they have to
charge back in are they really going to
try this the second time he's got an
armor Rune H so much Shields he's got
the poha is just going to stay hidden
here the charge canceled by the spirit
breaker ring Thunder very far away he's
just going to initiate from 3,000 yeah
because at any point in time the Spectre
can join him as soon as he gets that
initiate but they don't catch him the
ice blast going to be stretched outo see
opport this yeah he's going to go foro
GE with the there's so many Heroes they
dis pull out the fantasm but yoro
himself he will bring down he will use
his own hand to take down the enemy
carry now looks to finish up these
brings if possible gam and Gladiator
trying so hard the last one is going to
die double kill for utoro and they turn
back for celery a blink away from Quinn
he cannot afford to get caught here but
he doesn't have a TP if he gets spotted
they scanned him they know of the scan
uhoh Quinn's going to be in for a rude
awakening in a second here he just needs
his blink up and he gets by the D Jo
swash will from the side but they have
the silence on him the ghost remains
with Quinn he tries to go for a roll of
play but he's got nowhere to roll away
two those have TP back but stuck in the
corner get some good damage from Buckle
too many Heroes really nice scan to
finish up that fight and I mean a little
overextension there under a tier two
gives a really good fight to yoro Ace
dispelled a lot of the illusion
instantly dealt with some of the DPS but
inkwells the shards all these little
spells adding up and of course Dao going
down first that's a lot of the damage
that's been working for you downside of
this Orchid build right the pickoff game
is where it's strong the five on five
this Orchid is not doing anything for
you into the early bkbs here team spirit
strike back and just like that somehow
yoro is top of the board with from 05 to
tus net worth this Midas and the
Illusions are doing work on the map
right now and remember this was double
minus lineup plus A Dazzle the the the h
Tinker this lineup is going to start
ramping up pretty damn quickly if you
give them the space to work with and
right now they've got three cores
farming in three different parts of the
map after a successful team fight
gameing Gladiators they cannot afford
any more slip UPS they've got Roshan
still be taken here at 25 minutes in
it's also time for moska to deward one
of the problems they were facing earlier
in this game suddenly he can run around
with his Courier place a bunch of
centuries make sure there's not the Deep
Vision that gaming were playing off of
earlier so now it shifts the onus back
on to G in terms of you got to make an
aggressive smoke get Vision back on the
map and keep setting up these pickoff
plays for Daio who's the one may getting
picked off here to just walks in blind
get pull him back in but the silence is
doing a lot of work Quinn tries to R up
but collaps off the ice blast do man
grab two of those cores roll up snowball
onto
D's in Big Time trouble they give him
the shallow
gra bkb but if be will SHP plock it on
some of these Heroes is not enough T
still Falls and now with a toss up in
the air L will come down to a hard
reality crash down he does have the bkb
and look that agon inceptor with so many
units around him it's no hotal he is not
going to die so easily gaming Gladiators
thought they had an easy target fight to
the bend he bring down toio before he
finally Falls collapse stuck though in
the silence the buyback required from
gaming Gladiators because Laurel was too
t of a nut to
crack that looked way closer than it
should have been right these inverse
heals are doing Mad work at the end of
the fight have to respect the burst that
come out from this Dazzle when that a
blast has been used earlier on but still
great keep fight from G started out with
the atoro just walking blind into their
triangle and they were ready for him
Shadow Blade did not help him out in
that type of fight and that ice blast it
was a beauty from celery landed on
pretty much everybody forces the
disengage and the calling silenced
mirror on this jump right this is the
problematic aspect of this support match
up when you go in with the tusar this
AOE silence Clips you your team fight's
just a nightmare beautiful shards on the
flip to block off the pandas from clal
another really heads up play but damn
the damage is already done at this point
and now it's just a matter of cleaning
up which sounds easier than it actually
looked like right all of those utions
and brings play against game in
Gladiator the worst way and in the end
laa living does get Daio killed so have
to think about clumping up on top of
this Dazzle in the later portions of
these fights but I mean luckily that's
all the Primal split right the second
Ace comes out he's still full he's still
got Mana Radiance he's ready to par
he's going to slap some extra kills down
for the full team wipe here just when
this game was slipping up a little bit
of momentum game and Strike Back get
themselves a full F man wipe into the
rosan we put an AIS out on Quinn here
who's slowly getting towards that a that
team fight definitely helps still 500
off here but that's going to be a large
damage ramp as the shadow step comes out
look trying to do this solo it's a bit
dangerous collapse they're going to try
and turn back around they do have the
ice blat that'll finish off here pretty
easily and collaps he's got to be
careful this damage by yoro he comes in
wies down Daio but the rest of the team
is now here from gaming Gladiators
looking for the catch but collaps
already rolled away ball taking out oh
the H shot it's not quite enough they
have no stuns collapse breaks
free straight through the man's heart he
did not care he just walks it off can't
really get much closer than that and
once more yoro he finds an angle in the
fight cleans up the rcho and gets the
hell out that is a full silver Edge
reveal done and now the AIS is going to
be taken away from Quinn ah the pickoff
game is shifting right yes it is they're
not respecting the shadow blades not
respecting the aggression but ulp are
stalls him up collaps utoro actually has
bkb they do catch the uh ancient
operation he's going to die pretty damn
quickly there roll up the brings going
to work though stalling out yoro now
that it's bkb is on cool down now their
magic damage can really go to work and
they can slice and dice through that
carry pretty damn quickly butka
obviously he doesn't have much hope of
living through this so the fight does
turn against them not the worst though
for for team spirit I would say just
purely the fact that they're continuing
to keep things a little even and their
other two cores are farming the map yes
and they've got to be happy with like
you know the next 10 minutes here this
is when The Dazzle and the breaker are
going to come online they've recovered
some of the Lost net worth differential
here these heres getting very spooky
around the third to Fourth item and
they're going to get them damn fast as
collapse is just farming up the map but
yur's aggression used against them here
they'll got the return carry kill that
was a cocky move going up that hill and
just taking the fight with his bkb he he
can bkb TV there just opted Blood for
Blood why not we're in the
arena I love that Daio still not slowing
down he may die every once in a while
but he says you know ultimately the end
game is okay with me we're still getting
some good trade-offs and fights I'm
still going to try and limit your split
Push by whereever he can doesn't want to
let it get away with a tier two for
free they stick on top of with the
silence and the stuns it's enough Quinn
is stunned up for so long and now tofu
is going to be in some trouble as well
pops his ultimate that just kind of
delays things a little bit but there's
no one coming to save him if you're
getting multiple ink SWS off in these
fights it's probably going to win you
the engagement and right now you're just
getting outnumbered at a tier two you
overextended on Courier will die as well
no brew master ultimate for that type of
fight as strong as Ace is right now with
a full AC completed on top of everything
else he does want this ult to take the
long engagement right he is the most
farmed hero in this game right now if
you're gameing you have to play around
what he wants to do where he wants to
take the fights and what he can commit
to otherwise you're just creating an
opening for Spirit to come in and pick
you off the too once more looking for
the initiation with two Heroes dead you
will get scouted on an OB Sentry this is
something that started to happen in that
game too where they managed to get like
it was that one pickoff on celery right
where it's like they used the
chronosphere picked off celery and it
was like okay Chrono for a five position
but then they kept that going you're
like okay it's four versus five then
they found another pickoff and another
pickoff and it just so quickly
snowballed against them gaming
Gladiators got beware team spirit will
keep this aggression on point if they
think they have the advantage and
another Tormentor swiftly dealt with
from laurl and the The Courier Brothers
over
here that'll just being his chaos bolt
is all the more deadly for some of these
supports and we can see how yoro wants
to take these fights right create
confusion with with his Al going through
on Lanes show up with the silver Edge
get a pickoff maybe reset he doesn't
have to commit into the full five on
five into the brew and Pango which can
control him in that type of situation oh
he got stck oh
no landed on a pebble there and as a
result moska gets a pretty free TP on
out of
there a smoke that's ruined a rolling
thunder that's used for
nothing interesting little
tree tree is just
powerful one of the Primal forces in
Dota first Cliffs then trees Quinn's
having a yeah qu's Quinn's having a
tough time with the ter he's fighting
team spirit he's fighting the the map
yeah happens to the best of us another
pickoff that they will miss which is
time for the Midas to go to work right
they have been cranking this whole time
and climbing the charts this game is a
1K net worth lead now at 32 minutes dead
even everything depends on these team
fights collapse just Char right kind of
initiation here a charge that hit
supports Quinn on the run here they be
to jump after him laurl chasing after
him with that Shard to be able to slow
him down yeah
he's not going anywhere three dead on
the side of gaming Gladiators and team
spirit have changed this game The
Narrative was supposed to be gaming
Gladiators controlling and seeing if
they can end it but team spirit have
turned this all back around in the space
of just this 5 to 7 minutes and this is
the spirit breaker problem what happens
when you enter the mid game and this
hero starts to take over the lanes get
mega farmed and suddenly one charger
down half your HP ink swell just makes
this combo even more
oppressive the only real an is you just
the fight on your terms with the Primal
split going in with a Haun and delete
the supports create a situation where
you have numbers Advantage even when the
charge comes through you don't care
because you have the longevity and Ace
to deal with it if you're just getting
caught in the open like that it's a
death sentence right now collapse is
just running the map
literally he is getting six slotted very
fast and the question is do you have
good late game answers to the spear
breaker here if you're
gaming outside of tossing him in the air
dispelling him before bkb
not really right none of those
traditional answers Like a Shadow Demon
or the soul bind which is on team spirit
Side
Y and that'll be a problem especially if
collaps is able to use that charge to
kill those
grings that charge damage
is pretty heavy 31 to 22 4,000 net worth
lead for team spirit is that managed to
turn this game around and continue to
dodge attempts by Gaming Gladiators you
can see the window been taken out of the
gaming Gladiator sale Dao is not playing
with that same kind of fearless that he
once was where anytime a hero showed up
he would just instantly jump and see if
he can get the kill yeah the map has
just gone dark you have one defensive op
of your gaming but those days of where
you were picking people off on Spirit
side of the map have come and gone
you're now entering their portion of the
game you kind of have to get around this
you can go late here Spectre plus the
brew master especially with how much
farm ases found in this game are going
to continue to scale pretty damn hard
and of course you always have this
option of like tossing the Dazzle in the
fight with the Wind Panda and taking the
fight that way it's a pretty damn good
option a pretty good way to deal with
Dazzle in a lot of the historic matchups
between these two
Heroes but you got to keep scaling on
everybody the Mora and the AA scale is
really important here for gaming if you
can get a fourth core out of this Mora
which you know tofu has a full link he's
very farmed none of it is like direct
wor the damage you know he doesn't have
like an A or me near Silver edge of his
own but can only expect so much still it
will deal a decent amount of damage you
can lock your in the calling post bkb
that's the
dream little pump fake
action next fight coming up all about
Roshan 10 seconds till that potential
spawn time and then we'll see when he's
actually get a show up also celer went
back for this ancient Apparition blink
something we've seen develop in this
meta he is looking for that a blast on
the big course The Dazzle in the CK
especially that is who he wants to hit
cannot get snowball dodged you can't
really just a some random support it's
not going to be good enough to win the
fight need to connect this ult on a big
Target and collapse he's just going to
lead the charge with bulldo here not
afraid of too much while bold carries on
the other side of the map look at him
just running in there this is a fight
without yoro oh that Ward somehow slips
past detection oh no he's got it gets
him with the dispel on the old scepter
but it is going to celerate his life he
does have a fight back he's going to
play for it Quinn off the mark there
with his blink in trying to hit some
Heroes but they've already popped their
bkb going resetting a little bit Del
he's going to try and walk back into
this fight he's got to be careful though
he may get caught by collapse he spots
him the tower yeah that ancient
Apparition got no more ice Blast for you
to be able to use Ace has to use his
ultimate he knew the atoro was gunning
for him there he could have chain
stunned up now they back away Primal
split being used if they can get
everybody out it's a dream for team SP
collapse is making that momentum though
push back by the void Panda now hit by
the orchin if they can kill collapse
that'd be great but he has so many
dispels and so many Ys jumping in going
for the back L the bango's been caught
and yoro he destroys him so instantly
now turns his damage on the D back by
collapse a Char on through tofu he do
manage to get the for St down to low
ground does get a dead shot onto
collapse but he's still pretty damn
healthy and they can't turn this one
around it is all team spirit and they
will Feast on the brew master last team
fight decision making just off the
charts here I mean the king dealing with
the ult they just make it look way too
easy right now and so many Charges going
through from collap he is looking for
the high five and he will get it here
that was a fight for Roshan but it is
now a fight to hit High
Ground for ages
uhoh what are you going to do if you
don't have the BuyBacks or you're not
willing to commit them right here you
don't even have the Primal split if a is
back he doesn't even have the buyback
you are short offensive swing short on
so many levels right now collaps even
Ting a bruing because he knew the
Lincoln was coming back up on tou just
to get back in there and get another
charge through lead is absolutely
exploding here for team spirit as they
are sensing potentially a second agis
going their
way one
more and a ran to take team spirit they
still have time on the clock 30 seconds
left on The Brew Masters revive that is
more than enough to get this Agger and a
crystallis they were winning that fight
now they've got like 10,000 more gold of
items to be able to use with an agent
and cheese and all these other items
flowing in now you've got a grim shoke
with an agon sceptor a silver Edge fully
complete they are creating too many
problems you can't deal with any of them
level 25 also coming out on collapse so
even more Bashers on top of the aegs if
you thought this spear breaker was
causing your problems before he's going
to be causing him double now just no
control for him and he's way too tanky
to try and burst Theo was just not doing
enough single Target DPS at this
point you're going to need one hell of a
long drawn out fight
team spirit crazy they're up 20 in this
series they they're down in this game
three they have a 5% chance to make it
back in sure they could just give it up
say well guys it's the best to find we
can give them one but they claw their
way back into this game are now in a
commanding position to potentially three
The Challengers and gaming Gladiators
that is what makes us team absolutely
terrifying at this point in tournaments
and we saw everybody from all these
teams talk about it right if you get
ahead of this team what does it mean it
just means when they might beat you it
feels even worse right now this game has
turned itself on the head as you said
over 20k lead AG is up for 4 minutes so
it'll be up to yoro in terms of whether
he wants to push The High Ground during
this interval and trying in this game he
feels like he needs even more there's
still a lot of room to grow here they
did finish up an A on moska as well so
now you can start to get some dark
portraits in the mix just add even more
chaos and confusion to the fight more
damage sources yoro qu blink it away no
fear can't get
caught otherwise that is welcoming team
spirit into your
base charge complete half his health
fuel scepter is going to be used nicely
breaken with that Lincoln but he didn't
use that bulldo towards the end there
and these are just free they have the
ways to get collaps out every time
there's a Lincoln there's a swell
there's four staffs
grave the to going to take his chance to
Tak first down oh man before you can
even complete the sent he's already gone
they do have an ice blast though that's
pretty well positioned Dao's already
cleaned up the grimstroke it's not too
bad but Daio he needs to get out of
there oh my God that's so much so much
damage Spectre has to win this now but
he has to be careful that Dazz they have
to be able to take away this agis at the
bare minimum surely they have to go for
more they have to risk it collapse going
to charge on through to make sure you
can't set up on utoro now utoro will
turn back around on you he's ready for
that fight he pulled back in Daio this
could be it for gaming Gladiators unless
they find a way out of it quin's Dead
next now Daio a DI back for him Falls
tofu's pulled back in he is pulled to
his death down to his grave Quinn last
man standing for gameing gladiators it
will be a oneman stand against what is
looking like the best team in the world
right now absolutely as they take a
commanding team fight Victory inside G's
base no buyback on the brew master there
they just delete the highest net worth
hero for gaming straight off the bat no
turnaround potential and you are running
out of lives you are running out of
games to play here as team spirit they
don't want to just be the best team in
the world they want to prove that they
are one of the best teams ever to Grace
this stage right now and they are
showing why they're going to go for the
megas play it safe and a finished on mea
he's about to kick this team straight
out of the tournament if he has his way
and they're going to go right for the
throne quick reactions from Quinn has to
Blink away just one little opening as
all it takes with mea lurking from
behind Ace back up we'll see what he can
do to stall this out going to need one
hell of a primal split
hereo starts pushing forward mea doesn't
quite get it there and they actually
stop the spear breaker right in front of
their base but they're locked in by the
shards quin's able to hop around it but
now this it holds him in place he can't
do anything against that but at least
the brew master can gets the thr is
explode and now he's been oh no it is
too much for gaming GL to be able to
handle they are not going to be able to
get through this they have to pray to
get out but the cathedral is merciless
it is team spirits who are unstoppable
they will take
it the best team in the whole goddamn
world without a doubt silence every
other team
3 absolutely an incredible performance
in the grand finals against the best
team in the season an undefeated Grand
Final team iname game in Gladiators a
team that has defeated an entire lower
bracket to get here they take 3 in
record time kicked them out of this
event claim a second agis for the crew
the first one for Laurel who is fit in
immaculately with this roster this is a
team everybody had on their radar but
they have slowly built it up over the
course of the year are hitting in Prime
form right now and it shows this team
has multi- generational players and now
they are absolutely cementing themselves
as one of the best teams ever to play
the game M Dota 2 how do you stop these
guys you can't beat them early you can't
beat them late even when you have the
full advantage you have full control of
the game they'll beat you on the
comeback too team Spirits did it every
way
possible nothing is left for them but
the handshakes in the end for gaming
Gladiators who had an admirable run
through the lower bracket I mean it was
the stuff of great stories but it comes
to an end here with team spirit just
being too damn
good y Toro boss this man walks out he
shaves his head he sends a mental
message before the round even
starts this is a Longo victory for them
over the course of this year theyve
built up to it and for two
times the second time in the dota's
history team spirit will claim the ages
team Spirits win the inter International
[Applause]
spe
y
[Applause]
Ladi time your International 2023
Champions Jam SP
[Applause]
all right all right sorry just a moment
of your time congratulations Laurel from
last place to first baby how are you
feeling right now you have joined the
club you have won the
international uh I feel
great thanks everyone thanks
everyone thank you thank you for an
unbelievable game moska hello I must
interview you right now congratulations
led the boys again you've joined the
two-time club did you know you had a
5% w a chance probability of winning
that game and you guys came back has it
feel to be a two-time baby it's a magic
like it's uh our team
spirit and finally I got to do it to you
ladies and gentlemen may I present to
you the undis Beed best carry player in
the
world
s what do you have to say to everybody
who has supported you this entire time
all your fans around the world any last
words for the world of DOTA coming from
you my man and team spirit thanks for
our
support let's go thank you so much and
congratulations T steam Spirit Well Done
and there you have it ladies and
gentlemen give it up one more time for
your T Champions team SP
they have done it three and0 team spirit
demolished their opponents they left no
space for gaming Gladiators in that
grand finals and this will be a moment
that will go down in history one of the
most dominant teams in Dota 2 history
gaming gladers came close but team team
spirit the ultimate raid boss selfies
need to be taken that ages will be
pictured a lot a lot tonight I joined
here by lacost Effie and TV and we're
here to talk to you about everything
that we missed if we missed anything I
don't even think we missed anything I
think team spirit lost they are amazing
absolutely this is the team that uh you
know they didn't get the chance to
experience crowd at ti1 when they wanton
it and really glad that ble is cheering
really hard for them this is the team
that had a bit of a rough year at the
start and they started to pick it up you
know going into the rad Masters Dream
League they know when to power up this
is the team that enjoys playing on the
main stage so much you can see on their
faces all the smiles that's what DOA is
about having fun and winning some big
money oh yeah but my God what a team I
mean they are magical I feel like the
only other team in the history of DOTA
that embodied this kind of resilience
and passion for the game was OG and
former run but this team spirit it's
like we haven't seen anything like them
their players have improved so much in
the last year so much I can't even speak
to the Improvement of Meera of Laurel in
particular and for them to just win this
Aegis after a year that looked Rocky for
them at the start after not placing well
in the three Majors this year for
everything to suddenly fall into place
for everything to finally click right
around the corner for TI I mean if that
isn't Magic I don't know what is t i
mean just it's the fact that they have
these systems in place to be able to
shape plow into the player to become the
mid laner you know be able to replace
Toronto Tokyo again like L mentioned the
start of the year it will shaky they
barely got in the top eight of one of
the three majors and now here they get
first place and for Toronto not Toronto
yoro sorry two time TI winner and also
second ever player to get a rampage in a
TI finals the crowd love him he's just
popping off in the game like this team
they are just incredible I mean DOTA has
not seen a player like yoro for a very
long time he was in contention for
people saying he's the best carry in the
world the goat but he has proved that
here today at TI and even earlier this
year during the Riad Masters he carried
his team to Victory he fought tooth and
nail when they looked like they were
going to lose when it looked like there
was no hope in their games he was the
one to just push them forward and here
at TI they all connected they all came
together and it was just a beautiful
team Victory here it was a great Victory
great support coming out of the climate
pledge Arena as well and for everybody
in the arena I also want to make sure
that you guys are aware that you are
allowed to stay here for the late game
show as well so you can witness that you
can witness team spirit in the late game
show with peran flax and Jenkins so just
so you're aware you don't go anywhere
there's a lot more to come team Spirits
run has been fantastic we got four new
TI double TI Champions and I I must
bring it back to Laurel because his
story has just been fantastic you heard
slack say it on the main stage he came
dead last dead last last year and it was
a rocky start but there was support from
all his teammate support from the
organization we heard on the main stage
at Toro said at reup Masters I really
want to win this Championship because I
want Laurel to experience what it's like
and that he did and then he went to take
on the international with the same Squad
and T I can't believe they did it here
as well and they just done it in such St
as well like they've played so many
different types of Gam as well like
they're not just doing one thing the
entire time they are every single time
they approach a game it's a new way
Spirit approaches to beat their
opponents and I don't know it's just the
most commendable way to win it and sure
it was a 3 but it was a 30 in style and
yeah team
spirit it just so yeah like they
believed in lurl when you know getting
that last place at the and also some big
shoes to F this guy he's nuts every
single game that he played you could see
that he's powering up throughout the
tournaments you could see that he can be
toe totoe against some of the best
midlaners in the world and now he is the
best midlaner in the world Crown
immortalized absolutely what a story and
I mean for Laurel to play in this team
like Laos mentioned the shoes were big
the nerves were there and every time
team spirit performed badly he was
blamed there was mass criticism from the
fans Mass criticism of Laurel from the
community people were begging to have
this player replaced but the other
members of team spirit refused they
believed in him they said that they
think he has the potential they said
that they trust him and they know that
he's their mid laner and here we are at
TI he's won it yeah immortalized on his
Dazzle at that I just want to take a a a
small moment to just iterate the
wallpaper every time is the heroes that
one TI we have chaos night Dazzle and
Spirit Break as our boards on that
Waller I think T that is the perfect
embodiment here oh that's so so
beautiful you know just Spirit breaker
you know just going to be next year we
going have to remember this beautiful
cow just in the oh the good
times the good times will be remembered
for a very long time to come I also know
that the average age of players here
this might be a random point the average
age of players playing at TI is around
23 years old yoro is 20 years old he won
his first International at 17 now his
second International at 20 La cost I
mean not not to think about you going he
pretty much played for only one team
Yellow Submarine which kind of turned
into team spirit the other members of
the team LL who started to play
professional DOTA in 2021 collaps he
only played for three teams Mira only
two teams one of them also being you
know just predecessor to Yellow
Submarine and the veteran moska leading
the team you know so you have this mix
of a new blood and also some veteran
player that's going to lead them to the
victory I mean the key thing here is the
future of D DOTA is bright right like
when you think about the players here
the 20 years old 22 years old like
they've only been playing competitive
DOTA for what nearly four 5 years some
of them like these are the ones lifting
the ages time and time again and it's
like yeah it's just so good to see and
also I just want to highlight the
support Duo of team spirit I mean we've
talked about Laurel we've talked about
collaps we talked about uro and these
are incredible players but moska and mea
are the heart of this team they are the
backbone of this team they play so well
every game and their praises go unsung
because it's so hard to shine on team
with someone like itoro right but
they're so consistent they're there with
the saves they're there with the lanan
they're there with the pressure they do
everything right and they have done
everything right This Ti yeah and for
moska especially we know that his first
his first recorded professional results
were in 2015 but he's been around for a
very long time La cost and this guy this
is his second TI win what a crowning
achievement at such a successful career
absolutely this guy is just amazing you
know whenever we get the chance to talk
to him like the Insight that he gives of
course he doesn't want to reveal
everything maybe after TI we're going to
see in some of these Vlogs this guy is
just a rock of the team like you can
rely on him he's going to be carrying
the game on some of his signature Heroes
when it's necessary this guy is just a
menace to play against and he has that
you know compassion that embodies a
leader in a team like this if you've
ever interacted with him or heard him
speak of his teammates he views them so
fondly he's very calm he's not the type
of person to lead with anger to lead
with a form of aggression he's he's one
of those captains that just leads
through friendship and as cliche as that
sounds that is who he is yeah and it
beds into the team as well because when
when they're even behind when they're
down they're still smiling they're still
having fun like how often do you see a
pro team when they're you know backs
against the wall they're still enjoying
the game like team spirit throughout
this entire Journey not only were they
the best team but they just enjoyed
every single moment and it's why they
able to be so successful at TI 10 they
won first two games then they lost two
games but this time around I2 they made
it look very easy two games were
complete you know obliteration coming
out from team spirit in the third game
4% and they still managed to come back
DOTA plus not really you know team
spirit they're all against the odds 4%
it was by the way yeah 4% to win that
yeah that's fantastic I mean the game
was very close it just shows a lot of
character that they were able to beat
back hey exactly I mean this is the
spirit of this of this team this is what
they embody they are determined even
when they're playing with a net worth
deficit they never play like they are
they play like they're always in the
lead they play like there's always a
means into the game and you've heard
from the teams who have lost a spirit or
won against Spirit they always say
regardless of winning against this team
they exhaust you they make you tired
they fight for the entirety of the game
for every inch of the map and I mean
that's why they're here that's why they
lifted the ages that is why they lifted
the ages through hard work they they
worked really hard this this year to get
to the point where they were on their
team Synergy and on their go of course
as well they went through the upper
bracket they only dropped this entire TI
Run Road to the international and all
they only dropped two games T only two
it's just crazy to think about and
especially like the group stage it was
so clean for them they dropped a game to
verus Pro a regional opponent dropped a
game to liquid as well and then as soon
as they went against lgd I feel like
they just leveled up and of course Yar I
me he shaved his head like do did you
expect any other result today sacrifice
was made I mean he is the most
successful to go B pro player ever in
the history people have followed in his
footsteps failed miserably he has two
times in a row done it bam two wins he's
the only one who can wield that power
okay this power exists within Yo's realm
it's not something for other mere
mortals to shave their heads and win TI
but on the topic of one more player I do
really want to give my commends and mea
his flowers because I remember after he
won TI 10 he did a few interviews where
he said that he felt like an imposter he
didn't feel good enough to be a TI
winner he didn't feel he didn't feel
like this was valid he didn't
necessarily get that sense that he was
one of the best players in the world so
now that he's a two-time TI winner I
really hope that that impostor syndrome
can go away because he's proven it not
just to himself to his fans but to us
the DOTA Community the rest of the world
yeah they need to update this picture
I'm sorry this is
unable they do I mean to be honest I
don't think but we've seen other Pros
attempt to shave their head to embody a
Toro's power but let's be real that
power is his own and it it works for him
it works for the team they have done it
they have taken the ages for the second
time round which is an incredible
achievement so congratulations once
again to team spirit for having their
Victory I feel like we also need to give
a little bit of light there to gaming
Gladiators because they also had a
fantastic run they came second at this
International and that is not something
to be ashamed of it might feel really
rough right about now especially after
that third game which was a game they
were very close Laos to be able to to
force out a absolutely I mean gaming
Gladiators they were the team to beat
throughout this year like all three
Majors were won by them throughout the
upper bracket and they did look they
look like a team that's not going to
stop but unfortunately for them team
spirit they did power up at the right
time and also gaming Gladiators they
also had really really good tournament
so far you know dropping down to lower
bracket and making the magical run
unfortunately team spirit they were too
strong today they were very much too
strong today and while we witness team
spirits ictory a lot of people around
the world were able to cheer them on and
reel in their Victory this is Moscow we
have so many pop stops happening around
the world I also want to say once again
late game is coming right after this so
you don't even have to leave I know a
lot of people were having their time
slot booked out for a full best of five
we might not have gotten that but there
is still more content coming on this
very Channel and in the climate pledge
Arena as well oh so much love coming
from around the world here for Dota 2
and its World Championship the
international was taken by team spirit
but truly the real winners are all the
fans and I know I know that there are so
many people already that can wait for
2024 when there's a new hero in the mix
I also think that we learned a lot at
this International that we can all
incorporate in our own games and I'm not
talking about Des mid though I think we
might see that as well your head for up
some
pubs oh no there's new ways to take the
the Tormentor down that's something that
uh that that I learned you can do it
with Bristol back with his agon you just
turn your back you can do it with Dazzle
if you just have cers around and you
heal the cers and get the armor low and
everything I'm just I just realized well
technically Tor he also won the ages but
he also won the most death torment of
This Ti he so congratulations
yay another win win if that's true then
that proves that the Tormentor is the
ultimate villain it's the hardest thing
in Dota to beat because it beat yoro
there it is the only thing that could
beat him the Tormentor yeah Tori is too
strong too Nerf Tormentor op op now I
know I've said it a couple times but
I'll say it again there is a late game
show and it will feature all of team
spirit you can watch it at home if you
want to that's fine you can watch it in
the arena if you want to or you can
watch maybe in Charlotte Martin theater
in Seattle if you can find a seat which
I'm sure going to be highly coveted but
if you get there in time then uh kudos
to you but there is there's a lot of
content in that one and it will be a
fantastic late game so you better you
better make sure you watch that one and
take your time to do that oh my
gosh oh deep breaths everyone I mean we
still got all the confetti here and the
memories that we'll stay with us for a
very long time but it's about that time
it is about that time T you want to go
first
DOTA is a beautiful game connects the
world and yeah thank you everyone for
doing it without the fans we wouldn't
have all this so yeah good job thank you
DOTA is a part of me D is part of my
life for good 20 years now and I just
want to say thank you to every each one
of you who attended thank you Seattle
thank you for each and every player each
and every person who managed to you know
stay up till 2 300 a.m. to do the work
every single person behind the scenes to
make this possible because it's the most
beautiful event especially this one
we've ever had yeah and nothing can
match The Prestige of the international
we've seen it today it was special
watching the audience is special seeing
everybody unite coming from all over
special and yeah DOTA is magical game
I'm forever grateful to be part of this
community I'm grateful for the game for
introducing me to all of my new friends
and meeting everyone in the audience is
an incredible people have been so kind
and so passionate and what an experience
what an experience inde need it's uh
it's it's TI Vibes and we say that we
say that a lot I mean especially
backstage cuz T Vibes there is something
special because it's just it's in the
air it's the people you see everybody is
happy and passionate T go there is just
nothing like it yeah nothing can replace
it and and it's simple as that and
that's the joy of TI and I look forward
to the next TI and the next one and the
next one and the next players that come
in and try and take the ages away from
team spirit like yeah it's just it's in
a class of its own it's in a class of
its own and I I just want to give a
massive shout out to everyone that's
tuning in from around the world I know I
mean very special to be in Seattle I
mean I also think back in Seattle that
in itself is amazing but so many people
tuning in from around the world and N
Laos set time zones ah who cares
everybody tuning in at awkward times
just to make sure that they can witness
the greatest Doja to have ever been
graced losta what were your favorite
moments of this
International hard to choose you put on
the
spot ah I don't know it it feels like
you know we just had so many things that
you know made this tournament special
like there's like the shift in meta
where we see like shifting each day
pretty much especially during the main
event it's what makes this game so
beautiful you'll think you know what it
is then someone shows you like a couple
of hours later that you don't know what
you're actually playing even these like
top tier teams they lose in 20 minutes
because the other team is just better
like they prepare they don't sleep and
they you know show you how it's done
yeah it's also just really fun to watch
the Players come out on stage and really
feel the energy energy and you can see
them just basking in their you know own
enthusiasm and they're left for the game
you see them clapping and smiling and
they feel like they're on top of the
world there and you can see that and
that is a special thing to see but I
guess my favorite moment would have to
be VP versus bed boom that really long
75 minute game where kir toch TPS to the
rocks and dies there and woo that was
that was one of the good ones a wild one
for sure the fo of Western European DOTA
finally we get a bit of China love we
get a bit of what else we got we Eastern
Europe and then also this guy the entire
time he's been pretty good oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh there we go very very very much
a lot of dedication coming out from
there we go I will tell you mine as well
because uh I was walking around before
the road to the international playoffs
walking around and I took the wrong turn
we went for coffee we did you and me T
we went for coffee and I told you that I
knew the way I did not know the way we
went exactly the wrong way but that did
mean we were right in front of B Hall
when we found out we were in the wrong
place and Ben Roy Hall the place of ti2
and ti3 a lot of special memories so for
me that was very special and then I must
if you're talking about donta the best
donta 2 I mean the finals were fantastic
but I must must highlight team spirit
versus lgd game one yesterday upper
bracket finals that was intense insane I
I loved every second of that and that
was uh that was I think my favorite
moment I got to watch the last minutes
also in the arena cuz we thought it was
over obviously you know 20 minutes ago
so that uh that was very special and
seeing team spirit win here again it's
just there are so many so many wholesome
moments that this team has and they have
captured all of them as well they
capture everything we saw already the
moment that they won we saw moska FY
standing with camera in his hand they
Vlog everything I mean actually if you
go on their YouTube channel you could
probably learn every detail that you
wanted to about any of the players but I
I do love that about them that they're
such an immersive team like if you're a
fan of theirs there's so much content to
consume you can get familiar with all of
them so I I do think that's why they
have one of the strongest fan bases in
Dota outside of just playing
solo yeah oh ladies and gentlemen I know
that there's still a lot of people here
waiting for late game good is to you
there's a lot of people waiting in the
crowd still already for the actual late
game to watch it live there's a lot of
people still watching here because
they're waiting for late game to watch
it from their homes or from the comfort
of PB Stomps uh but we're wait we're
just getting getting ready with late
game we want to make make sure that the
moment we tune out you're entertained
with late game so we we're we're holding
the four down here as uh well this
entire tournament we talk about regions
a little bit there TV I feel like we
have to continue talking a little bit
more mostly in regards to the Chinese
region because I felt like compared to
last year last year they came top four
uh fourth with as and that was the only
team that really did uh incredibly well
we had lgd still doing okay as well but
of course that was was a different LTD I
felt like this was a Resurgence of the
region no for sure and I think it was
refreshing throughout the entire year at
the Mages and stuff we had this like
kind of just Western European dominance
the entire time it's why I was happy you
know that they uh maybe didn't do so
well this time around cuz I think once
TI sets a statement to what region to
look at then the Western European fans
and the the kind of Western audience
need to look elsewhere to to absorb
their DOTA content so uh I think for
China specifically lgd and then the Old
Guard of Azu being able to show up at TI
both get top four was incredible just
for interational DOTA and also they
produced one of the my favorite memes
that DOTA has ever seen you know Lam
talking about his tee that everything is
fine against gaming Gladiators and start
of like this is this is fine and
everything's burning in the back there's
like four people dying it's just like
you know it's going to be one of those
things I I I was I was watching that
yesterday and I was spinning water out
of my mouth through my nose as well but
we got to give credit to them because
they played some amazing DOTA reaching
top four without even trying too hard
you know we talked about the teams that
have practiced throughout the year they
formed and they're like you know what
we're going to show up at TI and do well
and they reach top four the Old Guard
plus some of the new generation of the
players they did extremely well yeah but
on the topic of that imagine being Lam
in that moment I mean you're doing an
interview and everyone's cheering so
loudly so you're thinking to yourself W
love and the cheering gets really louder
and he go oh I'm on a roll here with my
answers you he walks down back to the
Green Room he's looking at the screen
and just goes 4 and0 ah what we did see
we did we did hear barle Chala said uh
on his social media that they were they
were all laughing at it they were all
running away from the fight and as
someone goes kill that
bear turns around oh this I mean there
there's going to be a lot of memories
from this year's International one of
course I mean that one is a great one
but the biggest memory will be that we
have for the second time in Dota 2
history a two-time champion four new
players are getting that award and of
course now also a TI champion and team
spirit with their Championship a clean
sweep 3 and0 there's only two other
times that happened in the history of
Dota 2 so team spirit will go down in
history it's one of the most dominant
teams of all time we'll see if they can
repeat it next year I know that the
hunger for these players it just doesn't
seem to cease at all but that is it
ladies and gentlemen we're ready for a
late game so without further Ado I mean
we we've loved every second of it and
we've hoped that that we were able to
convey those feelings to you at home to
you at the arena we've we've loved it
and we hope to be back here in Seattle
some other time to experience the same
thing because it's something special and
I I can't even put it into words but um
I'm I'm going to have to so thank you so
much from everybody in front of the
camera everybody behind the camera I
know everybody cares a whole
lot and it is amazing to feel the love
from everyone in the arena and online so
thank you so much for that on behalf of
everyone in involved and ladies and
gentlemen your ti champions of 2023 team
spirit congratulations and we'll see you
for the next
one all eyes on the prize
[Music]
Corner
es to his against lgd doing that Holding
Out for a
resp he's de for
seconds
the will take this game
one jir Tak it out short of the Mone on
you also the they don't have gaming
Gladiators taking them down one by one
over the wall nothing to say he's
also the exposed looking it's over
is take one two we'll be moving on to
the Grand finals what a display of
dominance this
[Music]
last there are many Earths but only one
earthshaker
[Music]
team spirit they are absolutely
outplaying gameing Gladiators right now
on the map they just know all of these
heroes are getting picked apart there's
just seems to be no response whatsoever
from these Gladiators pkb turns around
oh man that damage is just building up
so quickly Quinn's got it an in so is
the bear Dao battling up against Laurel
but the big bad boss of the the fight is
definitely a Toro and once he turns his
eye on a hero
disar game over for this one the team
Spirits making absolutely no qualms
about shutting gaming Gladiators out in
their own style 33 minutes and it's done
a gaming Gladiators they are all going
to fall they're going to throw their
damage around the ke's actually getting
popped as collaps got a little bit low
but in the foul tomorrow
goes a rampage maybe a double no to's
going to deny him that they're going to
call the
[Music]
GG right now it is all gameing on the
momentum chart a full vessel was
completed very fast here from T to in
time trouble to
the bkb but a beautiful SHP PL out some
of these is not enough to still Falls
and now with the top the air will come
down to a hard reality crash down does
have the bkb and look that acept with so
many units around him it's no he is not
going to die so easily ging Gladiators
thought they had an easy target the
bring down to before and finally fall
three dead on the side of gaming
Gladiators and team spirit have changed
this game The Narrative was supposed to
be gaming Gladiators controlling and
seeing if they get ended but team spirit
have turned this all back around exp and
now he's been
oh no it is too much for GL to be able
to handle they are not going to be able
to get through this they have to pray to
get out but the cathedral is merciless
and is team spirits who are unstoppable
they will take it
[Music]
s
[Applause]
[Music]
a
live from the Charlotte Martin theater
in beautiful Seattle Washington it's
late game with your hosts peran flax and
jenin
[Music]
[Applause]
there we
go how's it going
[Music]
wow wow thank you guys so much for
coming out I realized we just
had we all love
Jenkins we we spread this event by word
of mouth so I'm surprised we have a
packed crowd all right let me try slime
I want do okay okay who's ready for the
light
show I want to I want to do another one
okay who's ready for a new DOTA
patch all right hold on hold on we don't
know anything about a new we don't know
anything about a new DOTA patch
I'm just kidding I don't know yeah
there's no announcements there's no
reveals it's just us and some guests who
wants to see team spirit out
here well we we got bad news we got bad
news have yeah they're way over there
they winding down they just had just had
a really long series you know really
hard long series it's been a long day
long day five games let's so let's have
a seat we'll get some guests out here
how about
that ah
[Music]
thank you very much that's our banned
for this evening by the way Eldridge
gravy and the Court
Supreme phenomenal phenomenal all right
uh should we get some guests out here
let's do it let's just get into it let's
get our guest out here do you guys like
uh sunsfan and cerin you guys fans
well we we didn't get them we didn't get
them no we did get them they're coming
out son fan of
[Applause]
cerin somewhere
[Music]
[Applause]
keep
[Music]
playing they're coming keep playing keep
[Applause]
[Music]
playing thank you
thank you brother have a sh
[Music]
down all right I know this is the late
game but you didn't have to be quite
that
late sorry about that that's it that's
the bit that's the bit wait left us
waiting for there really enjoying the
band so oh no they are great yeah yeah
that's fair enough what did you think
about TI great you you've been to a few
you've been to a ton did you enjoy it
yeah I had a great time I think it was a
great tournament I loved the arena I
loved the Vibes that was that was
good you know three and a half hour
flight for me that's sweet Seattle that
was the highlight that is his highlight
is it was a short flight so it was a
good TI yeah I think that's about right
let's just talk about the thing you want
to talk about let's put all the cards on
the table here the new hero Shannon what
do you think about it Suns fan
yes what do you think about this new
hero is this puppet master or is it no
okay I see a a belch sign in the
audience I appreciate you back
there we get a belch no he can't he
can't I don't want to get fired with
they've already uh denounced my voice
line many a time anyway uh yeah a lot of
people seem to think it's Puppet Master
but the reason they think that is
because in the files it was called
Puppet Master but the skills are nowhere
near the same as for people that don't
know the heroes of new Earth her
named Puppet Master which was really
cool but I do have some inside
information that's definitely fake go on
then uh the quote unquote leaked ability
from years ago is actually a Sur action
slack ability that he created in our
custom game called Community hero and
item project he made basically a virus
in our game that just destroyed the
custom game called
parasite and his ult was to take over
another hero okay like you take over an
enemy hero and you can just waste ravage
but that's not that's not just for the
that is not anything to do with this new
hero that's just something that's that
is a theory no that's your theory there
is a theory that that is what it is that
would be a bit strong a lot of theories
turn out to be true peran that's
true and a lot of dumb that makes
it into the game turns out to be a
Slack's idea like Centaur cart or pocket
Ricky you know all this stuff wait was
was a centur cart actually something he
came up
he did Lykan EGS oh it was the lyan EGS
yeah yeah the one where you bite an ally
and turn them into a wolf a w a wolf as
he call thank you thank you so waiting
for the Ursa where you get little baby
Ursa to walk around with that was also
his
idea thank God he's not in charge
honestly I do love him but uh thank God
he's not in charge
uh Jenkins do you have any questions for
these boys are you guys really hit
bottom the barrel getting us for the
shut up it's a set up for a bit you
jackass yes of course I've got a
question he was staring at the crowd
looking at the signs about himself by
the way no I wasn't I'm looking at that
Pudge sign all right clearly they don't
have any questions do you guys I got a
question for you guys I got
a I don't know what he just said I got a
question we asked when we're doing grand
finals and we did already it's called
Captain's draft 3.0 there you
go we're here to announce the moonduck
2.0 no we're not doing that you guys
when you guys are casting Grand finals
when you're in well when you whenever
you guys are casting on the non- grand
finals days of course okay group stage
yeah are you in character do you feel
like you're playing a character and the
guy the guy that's at home is different
from the guy that's on the
screen not that much he's very stupid
I'm very smart we kind of just do the
normal thing I don't think I believe I
can't who was it we were talking we were
having a conversation backstage oh yeah
it was your financial advisor right so
we met we met Shannon's financial
adviser what yeah he was here for some
reason they were having pizza it must
have been a really good deal so I feel
like getting scammed they were having
pizza and his financial advisor is there
and we have a convers we talked to each
other for like one minute I've never met
his financial adviser before and he
immediately says okay you guys are
exactly the same as in your cast CU we
were just going at each other so well I
don't know if I believe that I don't
know if I believe that and we've got a
way to prove oh no whether you guys are
telling the truth uh so while we set
that up we're going to have a little uh
bit of music from The Wonderful House
band and uh they're going to play for us
while we get that set up you guys don't
worry you sit tight all right take it
away you don't get to keep sitting get
up yeah where're ELD gravy in the Court
Supreme if you didn't catch up before
this one's called exceptional
and what you need what you need and what
you have and what you have are two
different things that you hold into
[Music]
separate when you bring them together
just like brains of
sand well you will see what you have
it's truly exceptional
man all
[Music]
[Applause]
right all
right oh
come
[Music]
on don't keep it a
secret we're all compelled to
share do you surround yourself with many
friends and still
despair You' got to reach out and hold
our to one
another look around see the smiling
faces your sisters your brothers come
[Music]
on
uh you got to keep on Holding
[Music]
On Come
On hey why don't you take them all
[Music]
up all right come
on ladies and
gentlemen it's that time we're here for
a celebration here tonight y'all so clap
[Music]
[Applause]
that's right y'all get
[Music]
up all right we know what you came here
to do to have a good time
[Music]
see everybody in the house tonight let's
have a party
[Music]
everybody we're going to need your help
one more time you know what it's for B
stack what's it time for time that Soul
clap s clap Soul clap s clap Soul clap
one more time
[Music]
[Applause]
wow thank you so much guys thank you
that was amazing are you guys ready for
this this is a genuine Acme lie detector
oh okay that we have acquired using
valve money uh you can't don't look
inside the Box this is all extremely
elaborate equipment as you can see
uh and we're now going to ask you
questions Jenkins will be The Question
Master and I will we'll do we'll do a
test a test run what's your name oh yeah
let's do we got to set it up my real
name yes your real name
Shannon that's true that's true that is
correct are you just pressing a button
randomly this is a genuine lie detector
read look at what it says on the box lie
detector Li DET gotcha okay okay all
right you got to you got to make sure
that he's on the level should we
calibrate his what's your name
Shannon that's a lie
can I say his name for him and then you
hit you're making this very confusing
for me pressing the buttons
PS that is just not true
so yeah hey I'm very good no whatever
all right uh Jenkins um ask them a
question question number one I'm gonna
ask him two in a row ask him to do you
listen to ASMR hell
yes disgusting
it gets more disturbing each time too
which is kind of sad but that's
different story what stage are you on
now uh you don't want to
know when we're doing business meetings
and he screen shares he forgets I can
hear I just hear you're a good
boy I'm so sick of
this that leads me to my second question
second question are there erotic
undertones to the ASMR that you listen
to yeah
okay I I mean I I didn't say I listen to
them for that reason but yeah of course
they got to sell somehow you think I Lie
by the way ever he telling the this was
not he's not a good guy to choose to do
know he's too honest he'll lie he'll lie
we we'll we'll we'll do him next all
right all right get
trolls do you have a belt
reflex
no that is true he does not have a he
cannot belch I cannot
belch so
sad you can't do it so sad was that the
guy with the Bel I lost the genetic
Lottery that was so unfortunate I really
wish oh no do you want me to talk about
the crop dusting on air
no that's
true my kind of show I'm not going to
lie I
won't you can talk about it though yeah
uh I'll pass cuz he's uncomfortable well
he'll pass he'll pass gas
later not not not early next question
Jenkins
okay sunsfan do you believe you carry
the sunsfan and Cinder and duo in
casting
[Music]
[Applause]
no hit the other button
Jenkins that is awkward okay very
awkward yeah
cerin you often decline events because
you're playing World of
Warcraft are you ever playing wow and
you just tell somebody I'm busy I can't
do
something am I ever playing wow you lie
do you lie about it
[Music]
no
okay moving on next question I didn't we
think that far ahead what were you
expecting shut up you're not you're not
the guy anymore it's him when is the
last time you
sharded like eight years ago it's
[Music]
actually eight minutes
ago
yeah that's why I come equipped with
diapers now right it's part of my
contract that's why they were like
getting on stage that's why it's on your
Rider because it rides
up do you ever get upset that he keeps
mentioning he used to be a CS:GO
professional no
[Music]
yes yeah well done the machine does the
work chares you don't need to fill this
in this is 100% what patch wasn't on the
Euro Pro not csgo I didn't say csgo
beta yeah people call me that but what
patch
CS I was going to go more into that but
we'll leave it for another day we it
we'll leave it all right last question
seven is the answer great really
interesting
uh you guys get to ask each other a
question first so you can ask him a
question anything you've ever wanted to
know that he can now not lie
about wow could have maybe given me a
little bit of a warning on this this is
ask him anything ask him
anything is Jenkins a good business
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
partner yes
[Music]
oh uh does Jenkins make you feel very
uncomfortable in
[Music]
general no but sometimes yeah that's a
lie all right okay that's it that's all
I got give a round of
applause all right we're going to get
this taken down so while we do that
we'll have another fantastic musical
number from Eldridge gravy in the Court
Supreme
[Applause]
[Music]
a pi pupil Ino school I always did what
my head Master told me to but you know
some boys wrote a be young men and got
to see the exterior of these walls again
got the mainland and up got to hop a
ship and go you know I need to find
another place to squish my toes in the
sand I got to get back home
again in the wind I got to
get to
R back chin I got to get
back oh you
know got to get back home
w w wherever that may
[Music]
be now backing some child hood HS I find
a pair of brilliant sing away in some Hy
you know women and the pass the time and
get the red legs out of the swaps the
three of us playing and shook the floor
I fanging at the back door ring in the
bill never got to go before he take me
straight back to hell to get back home
again train
[Music]
my I
got sit on some
need I know you're calling me it's time
to go but all I want to hear is
someone saxophone
[Music]
[Applause]
all right mixing up some sass FR smoke
some grass and get your
back H training feel my hair fre flowing
in the wind I got to
get Space Room some
hot
hot calling me out now but
[Music]
I'm sipping from the hip of old Jack I
got give me some more
that on some need some
all right
[Music]
now thank you so much that was
amazing uh Jenkins we got to get these
two yahoos out of here because uh
frankly they've overstay they're welcome
we want to get team spirit out here at
some point but I'm thinking we need an
expert to do like an exit interview with
these boys well there's one
guy there's one guy there's one there's
two guys but it'll be the other one yeah
that you didn't
say shall we get him out here shall we
get him famous for his out of breath
exit interviews at TI 10 uh let's get
avvo plus out here avvo
[Applause]
[Music]
plus you AB
you know I noticed you hugged him but
not me any reason for that I really like
him is it because I'm carrying a Kleenex
box that might have been part of it yeah
okay just checking yeah AO we need your
expertise I ran here by the way I know
you did that's good unrelated to the
show that's but but you've had a bit of
time backstage to catch your breath um
we have some apparatus on hand
that we'll be able to recreate the ti 10
situation so you can do exit interus
with these guys Jenkins if you would
please fetch the
[Applause]
[Music]
equipment other way around going to be
the other way around
[Music]
that's good all
right the plan is you're going to sit on
this exercise bike it's all right
Jenkins will hold your mic for you get a
get a good sweat going get get out of
breath and then you're going to exit
interview these guys uh if you chaps
could come and stand up here please and
arvo will interview you come on let's
get that cardio going let's go let's go
yeah all right Jenkins you're going to
have to hold the mic for him let's do
Suns famam
first God damn it he I can already feel
a
sweat sunpan
yes what's going on through your mind
after losing a million dollars that
you're riding a bike and asking me
questions if you have to
describe the emotions that you were
feeling oh you can slow down a little
bit
would you say your burning sensation
right now is higher than my
thighs probably I would hope
so are you going to stay with your team
next year what team God you're as bad as
interview in the
pros come on all right do cinder in next
this man's this is a this is a real Pro
interview they get two Word answers
right that's true exactly trying to keep
it realistic okay uh I'm still intering
oh okay yeah you're really in character
oh my God this is Hell fly I mean
sunvan fat
fly can you think of your best moment of
the year and describe it to the audience
so we can end on a very good note and I
this moment right here you in
agony all right that's good that's
enough alvo thank
you should I leave yeah you guys can all
right goodbye hell yeah I dodged the
thank
[Music]
youo see you soon brother get this man a
glass of water drenched
oh bye alvo
[Music]
wait wait wait stop stop there stop
there what it's the problem stop stop
there at TI 10 no ti8 I I did a show
like this with DJ weat and when we
brought the pro players out there was
nowhere for me to sit so I had to sit on
a little desk extension we couldn't get
that but we've got something better no
no you can't use a SOA this year can we
bring out the tiny tiny desk for for
Jenkins
[Applause]
there you go look I'll give you a few
Little Bits of Paper as well D I got H
man I'm an old man now well well uh
that's Jenkins sat down I sat down uh
who's ready to see the winning team with
ti2 all right let's get him out here
your ti2 Champions team spirit
[Applause]
[Music]
well first of all guys congratulations
on a insanely dominant performance uh
throughout the
tournament were you guys in a hurry
today or something cuz that was a very
quick Grand
Final
no what was the
question why why was it so fast it was a
joke don't don't worry about it okay so
okay okay so they're too strong bro
they're just like um too strong right
now they just we are too strong right
now much too strong that is
true you said you guys were was it a six
out of 10 at Dream League mhm what what
are you now are you 10 out of 10 team
spirit no uh not yet I think like uh
nine like out of 10 nine out of
10 what else is there to
improve maybe third ages maybe like U
maybe um like we'll play better next
tournament so it will be 10 of 10
you've got the Bold buff yo you shaved
your head they call it the Bold buff
you're not actually bold but we'll take
it uh I got I got to host this I'm
obviously bold there is some power there
SVG got to cast The Grand Final because
he's bold There's real power and
boldness isn't there I want to hear it
from you yes yes
yes that means a lot to me thank
you I got a question for you TOR as well
you said said Laurel is your son he's
your baby
boy did he do it did he finally make you
proud are you a proud
father uh yes yes I I think I'm not his
son to be
honest I think we need a DNA test
ladies I I think yat more sound than me
so okay I've been watching you guys do
these uh Vlogs on on YouTube and they're
very very detailed and you do a lot of
stuff with your team coms and talking
backstage and all the rest of it are you
ever worried that you're giving too much
information to other teams
no honestly I don't think we are giving
a lot of informations for other teams
because we are
like uh just like um like if uh what we
need
to them to know right we give them just
a part of our like information they
think about it but we have like a lot
more so we don't give something special
like and anyway I think we could give
more but it's uh I understand it's very
important for fans right if I would be a
fan I would like to know how things
Works uh know much more about team so I
think it's important thing but you can't
R everything true of course
okay speaking of the
content you guys did smells like team
spirit Nana was anybody actually playing
their
instrument every
well we get the lie detector back out we
can get the lie detector we have
instruments actually yeah we do that's
true team spirit take over for the band
that would be
something all right let's talk about
your guys team
because you always look to be when when
we were I was just watching the just the
Grand Final even you guys never seem to
be that far apart you seem to know
exactly what each other's doing how much
practice does that take or is it just
you just play together long enough it
just becomes second
nature yeah I think like your second
version is right like we played a lot
like for one year and at the start of
our roster we no our games was not
really good and we did kind of B
but now we got a lot of practice and
probably some good PCH and also we
found really good ideas how we should
play with each other how we should use
each other and yeah yeah fair enough
Quinn said and I don't remember if this
is public or not but whatever new be
this be new patch he doesn't give a
um you guys are a team that you kind of
no matter what the patches you play like
the same roles of in the game you know
collaps is playing like the Mars type
Heroes you get in there you do like
no matter what the patch is you kind of
do the same thing and when the patch is
yours you're like really really strong
on it do do you think that this is one
of those patches for you like first of
all is he right about that that you guys
just fit the same kind of mold on every
patch uhuh I think's probably playing
Ina Heros so if he his role has Ina
Heros we will
win like Mars Spirit breaker that's a
fair
breakdown brist as you can see as coach
I can say we're trying to use the
strongest sides from our players just
that's it okay well honestly I mean
yeah you think that applies to all DOTA
pubers out there that you should just
play to your strengths or should I
should I go you know learn how to be
position five cuz I'm too scared to
carry the
game yes um you should actually like if
you're scared just don't play so I
should go play position five yeah for
sure okay who wants to be supported by
Jets that's a actually I'm being
supported by been a wonderful thank you
uh want to play carry you should like
have no fear like in the game because if
you're scared like of something you're
going to lose for sure so what are you
scared of
yoro spiders shampoo
so I wanted to talk to collapse very
quickly uh your
Magnus uh in most of those games that I
saw you're off Lane in general but how
often are you thinking can we fit a
Magnus into this draft is that something
you're thinking can we do that does that
ever
occur I mean it was like the 10
every time I just say pick me Magus
already and they just speak it and
you're always happy playing it yeah of
course
fantastic I got a real one here for my
boy
Laurel when you first joined you were
replacing a legend everybody was saying
Laurel the new guy you know he's the
reason team Spirits not This Ti winning
team well you did it man you did
it how how did you go from
Laurel you know a year and a half back
or whatever it was to to Laurel today
how did you improve TI winning Laurel to
be TI winning
Laurel I mean I think it's just time
just need to wait I always know I'm
going to be the best so I just need to
wait
and you guys have faith in him too right
you didn't listen to the noise so I
think you need to wait if you know
you're going to win you're going to win
yeah I wanted to say just just briefly
collaps just between you and me thanks
for getting my voice line buddy I really
appreciated that that made me very very
happy a to winner used my voice line
that's hype who used yours mirror Ed
mine oh yeah yeah you're one like um
good meme you have thank you thank you
that's very kind I don't know why
they're thanking me we should be
thanking them you guys were amazing um
absolutely uh amazing to win it twice
for those of you who have won it twice
um wh which which was more important to
win sorry L which felt better to win the
first one or the second
one first one I think first one because
it was like the first time like in our
life first L we won so I think that was
like the most important like point uh
since when we will be just uh more
stronger like as a team and now we have
to win four times because like if you
win like three times he will have like
only
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
to I wanted to go through you guys for
those of you that watch anime which I'm
pretty sure is all of you maybe minus a
couple what what anime character
everybody's got an anime character right
that's like I'm that I'm that guy like
this is the guy that I'm going to like
model my like dotta play after you know
like I'm never going to give up Etc
what's the anime character for you youor
we go left to right that you're that
you're just like you're trying to be
that guy to to have the motivation to
win twice once I think it's Tanger
kamada from Demon
Slayer all
right to be honest I don't know I I
didn't think about this but I think
uh like my opinion just need to be
better than you in your previous day
like better with every day so I need to
be it
[Applause]
myself my character I guess it's humorin
from samur
[Applause]
yeah no idea but uh I would say it's
mugan from Samurai
champ I'm not watching Anye yes you
are
yes as a guy who is also not watching
anime I
can explain how I feeling like this team
is already anime for me I'm not watching
and and I'm feeling like we are I hope
so I hope we are me main personage who
can uh I'm feeling like we can struggle
and lose to not the best team some
middle teams but when our enemies become
very powerful very strong we like we are
main character of anime we are going to
win it
fantastic well as is
tradition uh especially on late game the
ti winners have to open some
champagne so we're going to bring some B
actually of course and you're going to
pop the corks and we're going to
celebrate so can we bring the champagne
out here for team spirit
[Applause]
please you guys want to stand up this is
the fun part good luck let's go down the
front
here if you're in the first few rows you
may get
wet all right are you guys ready is your
ti2 grand final Champions team
[Applause]
[Music]
spirit it
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
w
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
a